let questions = [{
    "stem": "The revelation of -- which God gave unto Him - ",
    "answer": "Jesus Christ 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name of Hosea's father - ",
    "answer": "Beeri 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was John given that was like unto a rod - ",
    "answer": "a reed 11:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose apostle did Paul say he was - ",
    "answer": "Jesus Christ 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the pure river of water of life clear as - ",
    "answer": "crystal 22:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Put them in mind to be subject to principalities and -- to obey -- to be ready to every good work - ",
    "answer": "powers, magistrates 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Which church was told they have left their first love - ",
    "answer": "Ephesus 2:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Boaz went up and sat him down in this place - ",
    "answer": "the gate 4:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To which church were these words written , I know thy works, that thou has a name that thou livest and art dead - ",
    "answer": "Sardis 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "My daughter shall I not seek -- for thee that it may be well with thee - ",
    "answer": "rest 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John said he looked and behold a door was open in heaven, how does he describe the first voice he heard - ",
    "answer": "of a trumpet 4:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was Naomi's kinsman of the family of Elimelech - ",
    "answer": "Boaz 2:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when was there a famine in the land - ",
    "answer": "in the days when the judges ruled 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In which hand of Him that sat on the throne did John see a book - ",
    "answer": "right hand 5:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what noise did John hear when the Lamb opened one of the seals - ",
    "answer": "thunder 6:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But speak thou the things which become -- - ",
    "answer": "sound doctrine 2:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When the seventh seal was opened there was silence in heaven what was the duration of the silence - ",
    "answer": "half an hour 8:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \" Ho, such a one! turn aside sit down here - ",
    "answer": "Boaz to the kinsman 4:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what fell from heaven unto the earth when the fifth angel sounded - ",
    "answer": "a star 9:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and a certain man of -- went to sojourn in the country of -- - ",
    "answer": "Bethlehem-Judah, Moab 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John describe seeing a mighty angel come down from heaven, what was this angel clothed in - ",
    "answer": "a cloud 10:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Boaz was described as a mighty man of this - ",
    "answer": "wealth 2:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did John see four angels standing - ",
    "answer": "on the four corners of the earth 7:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "behold he -- barley tonight in the threshingfloor - ",
    "answer": "winnoweth 3:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "There appeared a great wonder in heaven, what was the woman clothed with - ",
    "answer": "the sun 12:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To speak -- of no man - ",
    "answer": "evil 3:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John saw another angel come down from heaven, having great power what was lightened with his glory - ",
    "answer": "the earth 18:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who's servant did Paul say he was - ",
    "answer": "God's 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many heads did the beast which rise up out of the sea have - ",
    "answer": "seven heads 13:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which group is this referring to, be sober, grave, temperate, sound in faith, in charity in patience - ",
    "answer": "the aged men 2:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The angel that came down from heaven had the key to the bottomless pit and what great object in his hand - ",
    "answer": "a great chain 20:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The word of the Lord came to Hosea in the days of these kings - ",
    "answer": "Uzziah, Jotham, Ahaz, Hezekiah, Jeroboam 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And after these things I heard a great voice of much people in heaven, saying alleluia, --, and glory and -- and power unto the Lord our God. - ",
    "answer": "salvation, honour 19:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Hosea was a prophet in the days of five kings, which one was king of Israel - ",
    "answer": "Jeroboam son of Joash 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And I saw a new -- and a new -- for the first -- and the first -- were passed away and there was no more -- - ",
    "answer": "heaven, earth, heaven, earth, sea 21:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the aged women should be in behavior as becometh -- - ",
    "answer": "holiness 2:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose judgment did one of the seven angels which had the seven vials show John - ",
    "answer": "the great w**** that sitteth upon many waters 17:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Paul said he was an apostle of Jesus Christ according to the faith of God's -- and the acknowledging of the truth which is after -- - ",
    "answer": "elect, godliness 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to be no brawlers but -- - ",
    "answer": "gentle 3:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the first angel poured out his vial upon the earth what fell upon men which had the mark of the beast and upon them which had worshipped his image - ",
    "answer": "noisome and grievous sore 16:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and I saw another sign in heaven -- and marvellous seven -- having seven last -- for in them is filled up the -- of God - ",
    "answer": "great, angels, plagues, wrath 15:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many men of the elders of the city did Boaz take - ",
    "answer": "ten 4:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John said he looked and behold a lamb stood on this mount - ",
    "answer": "mount Sion 14:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Naomi tell Ruth to do before going down to the threshingfloor - ",
    "answer": "wash thyself, anoint thee, put thy raiment upon thee 3:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was under the woman's feet - ",
    "answer": "the moon 12:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Ruth say to Naomi before she went to glean - ",
    "answer": "let me now go to the field, and glean ears of corn after him in whose sight I shall find grace 2:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To Ephesus, I know thy -- and thy -- and thy -- - ",
    "answer": "works, labor, patience 2:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who went with the man to sojourn in the country of Moab - ",
    "answer": "his wife and his two sons 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Sardis told to strengthen - ",
    "answer": "the things which remain that are ready to die 3:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when did Naomi tell Ruth to make herself known to the man - ",
    "answer": "after he had done eating and drinking 3:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The voice told John come up and I will show thee things which must be -- - ",
    "answer": "hereafter 4:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of Elimelech's wife - ",
    "answer": "Naomi 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Naomi's response when Ruth asked to go and glean in the field - ",
    "answer": "go my daughter 2:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did John describe the book He saw in the right hand of Him that sat on the throne - ",
    "answer": "written within on the backside sealed with seven seals 5:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the Lamb opened one of the seals who said \"come and see\" - ",
    "answer": "one of the four beasts 6:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what should aged women be teachers of - ",
    "answer": "good things 2:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the seven angels that stood before God given - ",
    "answer": "seven trumpets 8:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Boaz tell the kinsman Naomi was selling and who did he say it belong to - ",
    "answer": "a parcel of land, our brother Elimelech's"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was given to the star that fell from heaven to the earth - ",
    "answer": "the key of the bottomless pit 9:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Paul writes God cannot do this - ",
    "answer": "lie 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was upon the mighty angel's head - ",
    "answer": "a rainbow 10:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Go take unto thee a wife of -- and children of -- - ",
    "answer": "whoredom, whoredom 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the angel tell John to measure with the reed - ",
    "answer": "the temple of God, the altar and them that worship therein 11:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "showing all meekness unto all -- - ",
    "answer": "men 3:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"I thought to advertise thee, saying buy it before the inhabitants\" - ",
    "answer": "Boaz 4:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the four angels holding - ",
    "answer": "the four winds of the earth 7:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many horns did the beast out of the sea have - ",
    "answer": "ten horns 13:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "after whom did Ruth glean in the field - ",
    "answer": "reapers 2:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For true and -- are His judgments - ",
    "answer": "righteous 19:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Naomi tell Ruth to do when Boaz lieth down - ",
    "answer": "mark the place where he shall lie, go in and uncover his feet, and lay thee down 3:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many were with the lamb that stood on mount Sion - ",
    "answer": "144,000, 14:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of Elimelech's two sons - ",
    "answer": "Mahlon and Chilion 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To what did John liken the holy city new Jerusalem coming down from God out of heaven - ",
    "answer": "prepared as a bride adorned for her husband 21:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Paul says to Titus for we ourselves were sometimes these - ",
    "answer": "foolish, disobedient, deceived, serving divers lusts and pleasures, living in malice and envy, hateful and hating one another 3:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he laid hold on the dragon that old -- which is the -- and satan - ",
    "answer": "serpent, devil 20:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when did God promise the hope of eternal life - ",
    "answer": "before the world began 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from where was the pure river of water of life proceeding - ",
    "answer": "throne of God and the Lamb 22:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "aged women should not be false accusers or be given to much -- - ",
    "answer": "wine 2:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the Lord say the land hath committed great whoredom - ",
    "answer": "departing from the Lord 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he cried mightily with a strong voices saying, Babylon the great is fallen, is fallen and is become the habitation of -- and the hold of every -- spirit, and the cage of every -- and hateful bird - ",
    "answer": "devils, foul, unclean 18:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God gave Jesus the revelation to show unto His servants things which must - ",
    "answer": "shortly come to pass 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "At the Lord's command who did the Hosea take as a wife - ",
    "answer": "Gomer 1:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what have the kings of the earth committed with the great w**** - ",
    "answer": "fornication 17:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what should the aged women teach the young women - ",
    "answer": "sober, love their husbands, love their children, discreet, chaste, keepers at home, obedient to their own husbands 2:4-5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the second angel pour out his vial - ",
    "answer": "upon the sea 16:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In due times how hath God manifested His word - ",
    "answer": "through preaching 1:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the sea of glass mingled with - ",
    "answer": "fire 15:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Not by works of righteousness which we have done but according to His -- He saved us - ",
    "answer": "mercy 3:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Those at Ephesus tried them which said they were apostles and found them to be this - ",
    "answer": "liars 2:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the kinsman response when Boaz told him about the land - ",
    "answer": "I will redeem it 4:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the church, for I have not found thy works perfect before God - ",
    "answer": "Sardis 3:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And she went down unto the floor, and did according to all that her mother in-law -- her - ",
    "answer": "bade 3:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Like what stones did John describe the look of the one that sat on the throne - ",
    "answer": "jasper and sardine 4:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and her -- was to light on a part of the field belonging unto Boaz - ",
    "answer": "hap 2:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is worthy to open the book and to loose the seals thereof, who did John say was proclaiming those words and with what kind of voice - ",
    "answer": "a strong angel, with a loud voice 5:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Elimelech, Naomi and their sons Mahlon and Chilion were -- of Behtlehem-Judah - ",
    "answer": "Ephrathites 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the color of the first horse - ",
    "answer": "white 6:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Boaz had eaten and drunk and his heart was merry where did he go to lie down - ",
    "answer": "at the end of the heap of corn 3:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The four angels were holding the winds that they should not blow on these - ",
    "answer": "earth, sea or any tree 7:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who died first in Naomi's family - ",
    "answer": "her husband Elimelech 1:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the angel with the golden censer come and stand - ",
    "answer": "at the altar 8:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Boaz come from when he saluted the reapers - ",
    "answer": "Bethlehem 2:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what arose out of the bottomless pit when it was opened - ",
    "answer": "smoke 9:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "that the word of God be not -- - ",
    "answer": "blasphemed 2:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the mighty angel was described as the sun - ",
    "answer": "his face 10:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Boaz told the kinsman the day he buy the field of the hand of Naomi he must buy it also of this person and for this purpose - ",
    "answer": "Ruth the Moabitess the wife of the dead, to raise up the name of the dead upon his inheritance 4:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was John told to leave out of the measuring - ",
    "answer": "the court that is without the temple 11:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Paul refer to as his own son after the common faith - ",
    "answer": "Titus 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the beast from the sea have on each horn - ",
    "answer": "crowns 13:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of the father of Gomer - ",
    "answer": "Diblaim 1:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the woman have on her head - ",
    "answer": "a crown of twelve stars 12:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "That being justified by His grace we should be made heirs according to the hope of -- life - ",
    "answer": "eternal 3:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how long did the angel bound satan - ",
    "answer": "a thousand years 20:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did the kinsman say he cannot redeem the land for himself - ",
    "answer": "lest he mar his own inheritance 4:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was written in the foreheads of the 144,000 - ",
    "answer": "His ( the lamb) Father's name 14:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what words did Boaz greet the reapers - ",
    "answer": "The Lord be with you 2:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with respect to the river where was the tree of life - ",
    "answer": "in the midst and on either side 22:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ruth came in this manner and uncovered Boaz's feet and laid her down - ",
    "answer": "softly 3:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From whom did Naomi's sons take them wives - ",
    "answer": "of the women of Moab 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold the -- of God is with men, and He will dwell with them - ",
    "answer": "tabernacle 21:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and He sent and signified by His angel unto His servant -- - ",
    "answer": "John 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Paul tell Titus to avoid - ",
    "answer": "foolish questions, genealogies, contentions and striving about the law 3:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what did the great w**** corrupt the earth - ",
    "answer": "with her fornication 19:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "--, -- and -- from God the Father and the Lord Jesus Christ our Saviour - ",
    "answer": "grace, mercy, peace 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the -- of the earth are waxed rich through the abundance of her delicacies - ",
    "answer": "merchants 18:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Young men likewise exhort to be -- minded - ",
    "answer": "sober 2:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who have been made drunk with the wine of the fornication of the great w**** - ",
    "answer": "the inhabitants of the earth 17:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of the first son Gomer bare to Hosea - ",
    "answer": "Jezreel 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what became of the sea when the second angel poured out his vial upon it - ",
    "answer": "it became as the blood of a dead man, and every living soul died in the sea 16:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Upon whose house did the Lord say He would avenge the blood of Jezreel - ",
    "answer": "house of Jehu 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "those that stood on the sea of glass had gotten the victory over who/what - ",
    "answer": "the beast, his image, his mark, number of his name 15:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which group is this directed to, in all things showing thyself a pattern of good works - ",
    "answer": "young men 2:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and she being with child cried, -- in birth and pained to be -- - ",
    "answer": "travailing, delivered 12:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in which place did Paul leave Titus - ",
    "answer": "Crete 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The church at Ephesus has labored and not -- - ",
    "answer": "fainted 2:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Paul give Titus a list of things to avoid, one reason for doing was that they were unprofitable what was the other - ",
    "answer": "vain 3:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Like whom did Jesus tell Sardis He will come on them - ",
    "answer": "like a thief 3:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who to whom \" redeem thou my right to thyself\" - ",
    "answer": "the kinsman to Boaz 4:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with respect to the throne where was the rainbow - ",
    "answer": "round about 3:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what time did Boaz discover a woman laid at his feet and what was his reaction - ",
    "answer": "at midnight, afraid 3:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "No man in these places was able to open the book neither to look thereon - ",
    "answer": "heaven, earth, under the earth 5:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the reapers respond to Boaz greeting - ",
    "answer": "the Lord bless thee 2:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did he that sat on the white horse have - ",
    "answer": "a bow 6:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which daughter in-law of Naomi was first mentioned by name in the book of Ruth. - ",
    "answer": "Orpah 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Mahlon and Chilion dwell in the land of Moab before they died - ",
    "answer": "about ten years 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was given to the angel with the golden censer - ",
    "answer": "much incense 8:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "describe the smoke that arose out of the pit - ",
    "answer": "smoke of a great furnace 9:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"whose damsel is this\" - ",
    "answer": "Boaz to his servant that was set over the reapers 2:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the mighty angel was described as pillars of fire - ",
    "answer": "his feet 10:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ruth asked Boaz to spread this over thine handmaid for thou art near kinsman - ",
    "answer": "thy skirt 3:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why was John told not to measure the court without the temple - ",
    "answer": "for it is given unto the gentiles 11:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of man did Paul say to reject after the first and second admonition - ",
    "answer": "a man that is a heretic 3:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From which direction did John see another angel ascending - ",
    "answer": "the east 7:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Now this was the manner in former time in Israel concerning -- and concerning -- - ",
    "answer": "redeeming, changing 4:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what name did the beast that arose out of the sea have on his heads - ",
    "answer": "blasphemy 13:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In doctrine showing uncorruptness, gravity -- - ",
    "answer": "sincerity 2:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and hath -- the blood of His servants at her hand - ",
    "answer": "avenged 19:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "avenging the blood of Jezreel what kingdom did the Lord say He will cause to cease - ",
    "answer": "kingdom of the house of Israel 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Give the reasons why Paul says he left Titus in Crete - ",
    "answer": "to set in order the things that are wanting, and ordain elders in every city 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and I heard a voice from heaven, as the voice of many -- and as the voice of great -- and I heard the voice of -- harping with their harps - ",
    "answer": "waters, thunder, harpers 14:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God shall wipe away all -- from their eyes, and there shall be no more --, neither sorrow nor -- neither shall there be anymore -- for the former things are passed away. - ",
    "answer": "tears,death, crying, pain 21:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to confirm all things what did a man do - ",
    "answer": "plucked off his shoe and gave it to his neighbor 4:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to where did the angel cast satan - ",
    "answer": "bottomless pit 20:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and she said I pray you let me glean and gather after the reapers among the -- - ",
    "answer": "sheaves 2:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many manner of fruits did the tree of life bear - ",
    "answer": "twelve 22:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Blessed be thou of the Lord, my daughter for thou has shown more -- in the latter end than at the beginning inasmuch as thou followedst not -- men whether -- or -- - ",
    "answer": "kindness, young, poor, rich 3:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "come out of her my people that ye be not partakers of her -- and that ye receive not of her -- - ",
    "answer": "sins, plagues 18:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and woman was left of her two -- and her -- - ",
    "answer": "sons, husband 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who bare record of the word of God and of the -- of Jesus Christ and of all things he saw - ",
    "answer": "testimony 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Paul told Titus he will send two men to him name them - ",
    "answer": "Artemas, Tychicus 3:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Paul want Titus to ordain elders - ",
    "answer": "in every city 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "so he carried me away in the spirit into the -- - ",
    "answer": "wilderness 17:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the third angel pour out his vial and what was the result - ",
    "answer": "upon the rivers and fountains of water and they became blood 16:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "sound speech that cannot be condemned that he that is on the -- part may be ashamed having no evil thing to say of you. - ",
    "answer": "contrary 2:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what instrument did those that stood on the sea of glass have - ",
    "answer": "harps of God 15:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the Lord say He would break the bow of Israel - ",
    "answer": "in the valley of Jezreel 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ephesus was told except they do this their candlestick will be removed - ",
    "answer": "repent 2:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Gomer's second child she bare to Hosea what was her name - ",
    "answer": "Loruhamah 1:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said they have a few names in Sardis that have not done this - ",
    "answer": "defile their garments 3:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Exhort -- to be obedient to their own -- and to please them well in all things, not answering again - ",
    "answer": "servants, masters 2:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the sight of the rainbow round about the throne was described by John to be like this precious stone - ",
    "answer": "emerald 3:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If any be blameless the husband of one -- having faithful -- not accused of riot or -- - ",
    "answer": "wife, children,unruly 1:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did John say he did because no man was found worthy to open and read the book neither to look thereon - ",
    "answer": "wept much 5:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Paul told Titus to be diligent to come unto him to this place where he has decided to winter - ",
    "answer": "Nicopolis 3:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and this was a testimony in -- - ",
    "answer": "Israel 4:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was given to him that sat on the white horse - ",
    "answer": "a crown 6:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the angel ascending from the east have - ",
    "answer": "the seal of the living God 7:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Boaz tell Ruth all the city of the people know of her - ",
    "answer": "that thou art a virtuous woman 3:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why was the angel with the golden censer given much incense - ",
    "answer": "that he should offer it with the prayers of all the saints upon the golden altar which was before the throne 8:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from when did the servant say Ruth had been gleaning - ",
    "answer": "from the morning 2:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was darkened by reason of the smoke of the pit - ",
    "answer": "sun and air 9:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Namoi arose with her daughters in-law that she might return from this place - ",
    "answer": "country of Moab 1:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did the mighty angel have in his hand - ",
    "answer": "a little book open 10:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Boaz told the people ye are witnesses this day that I have bought all that was -- and all that was -- and -- of the the hand of Naomi - ",
    "answer": "Elimelech's, Chilion's, Mahlon's 4:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long shall the holy city be tread under foot by the gentiles - ",
    "answer": "forty two months 11:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "according to the servant Ruth tarried a little in this place - ",
    "answer": "the house 2:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The beast which John saw arise out of the sea was like unto what animal - ",
    "answer": "a leopard 13:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Boaz told Ruth that he was the nearest kinsman - ",
    "answer": "false, there is a kinsman nearer than I 3:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John said there appeared in heaven another wonder a great dragon of this color - ",
    "answer": "red 12:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Naomi hear in the country of Moab - ",
    "answer": "how that the Lord had visited His people in giving them bread 1:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the angel set a seal upon satan that he should do this no more till the thousand years be fulfilled - ",
    "answer": "deceive the nations 20:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Zenas profession - ",
    "answer": "lawyer 3:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "before who/what did the 144,000 sing a new song - ",
    "answer": "the throne, the four beast, elders 14:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord instructed Hosea to call his daughter Loruhamah saying He will no more have this upon the house of Israel but will utterly take them away - ",
    "answer": "mercy 1:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how often did the tree of life yield her fruit - ",
    "answer": "every month 22:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For a bishop must be blameless as the -- of God - ",
    "answer": "steward 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who will be given of the fountain of the water of life freely - ",
    "answer": "him that is athirst 21:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Not purloining but showing all -- that they may adorn the doctrine of God our Savior in all things - ",
    "answer": "fidelity 2:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- is he that readeth and they that -- the words of this prophecy and -- those things which are written therein for the time is at -- - ",
    "answer": "blessed, hear, keep, hand 1:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Tarry this night and it shall be in the morning that if he will perform unto thee the part of a --, well, let his do the -- part, but if he will not do the part of a -- to thee, then will I do the part of a -- to thee as the Lord liveth. lie down until the morning - ",
    "answer": "kinsman, kinsman''s, kinsman, kinsman 3:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And a voice came out of the throne, saying Praise our God, all ye His servants, and ye that fear Him both small and -- - ",
    "answer": "great 19:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Naomi went forth from the place where she was with her two daughters in-law and they went on the way to return to this land - ",
    "answer": "land of Judah 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For her sins are reached unto -- and God hath remembered her iniquities - ",
    "answer": "heaven 18:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"go not to glean in another field\" - ",
    "answer": "Boaz to Ruth 2:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what colored beast did John see the woman sitting upon - ",
    "answer": "scarlet colored 17:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by whom did the Lord say He would save the house of Judah - ",
    "answer": "by the Lord their God 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which angel said these words \"thou art righteous, O Lord which art, and wast and shall be, because thou has judged thus\" - ",
    "answer": "the angel of the waters 16:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ruth was the wife of which son of Naomi - ",
    "answer": "Mahlon 4:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what song did those that stood on the sea of glass sing - ",
    "answer": "song of Moses and the Lamb 15:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "a bishop must not soon be this - ",
    "answer": "angry 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the Nicolaitans does the church of Ephesus hate - ",
    "answer": "their deeds 2:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What of God did Paul say hath appeared to all men - ",
    "answer": "grace of God that brings salvation 2:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "they shall walk with me in white for they are -- - ",
    "answer": "worthy 3:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what two men did Paul tell Titus to bring - ",
    "answer": "Zenas, Apollos 3:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and all the people that were in the gate and the elders said we are -- - ",
    "answer": "witnesses 4:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many seats were round about the throne - ",
    "answer": "twenty four 3:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who told John to, weep not - ",
    "answer": "one of the elders 5:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by whom did Boaz tell Ruth to abide - ",
    "answer": "by his maidens 2:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did he that sat on the white horse went forth to do - ",
    "answer": "conquering and to conquer 6:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To whose house did Naomi tell her daughters in-law to return - ",
    "answer": "mother's house 1:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did the angel ascending from the east cry with a loud voice to - ",
    "answer": "the four angels to whom it was given power to hurt the earth and sea 7:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what must a bishop not be given to - ",
    "answer": "wine, filthy lucre 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Before whom did the smoke of the incense which came with the prayer of the saints ascend - ",
    "answer": "God 8:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Teaching us that denying ungodliness and worldly lust we should live --, -- and godly in this present world. - ",
    "answer": "soberly,righteously 2:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what came out of the smoke - ",
    "answer": "locusts 9:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "By what things did the Lord say He would not save Judah - ",
    "answer": "bow, sword, battle, horses, horsemen 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did the mighty angel set his right foot - ",
    "answer": "upon the sea 10:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with respect to Boaz where did Ruth lay until morning - ",
    "answer": "at his feet 3:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord say He would give unto His two witnesses - ",
    "answer": "power 11:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happned when Gomer had weaned Loruhamah - ",
    "answer": "she conceived and bare a son 1:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the feet of the beast that arose out of the sea - ",
    "answer": "a bear 13:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "looking for that -- hope, and the glorious appearing of the great God and our Saviour Jesus Christ - ",
    "answer": "blessed 2:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many heads did the great red dragon have - ",
    "answer": "seven heads 12:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "A bishop must be a lover of these - ",
    "answer": "hospitality, good men 1:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "after the thousand years for how long must satan be loosed - ",
    "answer": "a little season 20:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord make the woman that is come into thine house like -- and like -- which two did build the house of Israel - ",
    "answer": "Rachel, Leah 4:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what could no man but the 144,000 learn - ",
    "answer": "the new song 14:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what time did Ruth rise up from the threshingfloor - ",
    "answer": "before one could know another 3:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the leaves of the tree of life for - ",
    "answer": "the healing of the nations 22:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Boaz say he charged not to touch Ruth - ",
    "answer": "the young men 2:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"the Lord deal kindly with you, as ye have dealt with the dead, and with me\" - ",
    "answer": "Naomi 1:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who will have their part in the lake of fire which burneth with fire and brimstone which is the second death - ",
    "answer": "fearful, unbelieving, abominable, murderers, whoremongers, sorcerers, idolaters, all liars 21:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John wrote to the seven churches located in this place - ",
    "answer": "Asia 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he said let it not be known that a -- came into the floor - ",
    "answer": "woman 3:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And I heard as it were the voice of a great -- and the voice of many -- and the voice of mighty -- saying alleluia for the Lord God omnipotent reigneth - ",
    "answer": "multitude, waters, thunderings 19:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In whose house did Naomi hope her daughters in-law would find rest - ",
    "answer": "house of their husband 1:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Reward her even as she -- you, and double unto her -- according to her works in the -- which she had filled fill to her double - ",
    "answer": "rewarded, double cup 18:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Boaz tell Ruth to do when she is athirst - ",
    "answer": "go unto the vessel and drink which the young men have drawn 2:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the scarlet colored beast was full of names of blasphemy having -- heads and -- horns - ",
    "answer": "seven, ten 17:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "sober, just, holy -- - ",
    "answer": "temperate 1:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for they have shed the blood of -- and -- thou has given them blood to drink, for they are -- - ",
    "answer": "saints, prophets, worthy 16:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and do thou worthily in Ephratah and be famous in -- - ",
    "answer": "Bethlehem 4:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the song what of the Lord God Almighty are great and marvellous - ",
    "answer": "His works 15:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who gave Himself for us that He might redeem us from all -- and purify unto Himself a -- people zealous of good -- - ",
    "answer": "iniquity, peculiar, works 2:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the second son Gomer bare to Hosea was called Loammi, what statment accompanies this name - ",
    "answer": "for ye are not my people and I will not be your God 1:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Rev 2:7 where is the tree of life located - ",
    "answer": "in the midst of the paradise of God"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Him that overcometh Jesus promises he shall be clothed in white and this will not be blot out of the book of life - ",
    "answer": "his name 3:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord says the number of the children of Israel shall be as the sand of the sea which cannot be -- or -- - ",
    "answer": "measured, numbered 1:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was sitting on the four and twenty seats - ",
    "answer": "four and twenty elders 3:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "These things speak and exhort and rebuke with all -- let no man despise thee - ",
    "answer": "authority 2:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the elder tell John hath prevailed to open the book and to loose the seven seals thereof - ",
    "answer": "the Lion of the tribe of Judah, the Root of David 5:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "holding fast the faithful word he has been taught that a bishop may be able to do these two things to the gainsayers - ",
    "answer": "exhort, convince 1:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the second seal was opened who said come and see - ",
    "answer": "the second beast 6:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and let thy house be like the house of -- which Tamar bare unto Judah of the seed which the Lord shall give thee of this woman - ",
    "answer": "Pharez 4:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The angel ascending out of the east told the four angels to hurt not the earth, neither the sea nor the trees till this - ",
    "answer": "till we have sealed the servants of our God in their foreheads 7:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Boaz place in Ruth's veil - ",
    "answer": "six measures of barley 3:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "according to Ruth 2:10, what did Ruth do after Boaz spoke to her - ",
    "answer": "she fell on her face and bowed herself to the ground 2:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did the angel fill the censer with - ",
    "answer": "fire of the altar 8:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was given unto the locusts - ",
    "answer": "power 9:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then she -- them and they lifted up their -- and wept - ",
    "answer": "kissed, voice 1:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the mighty angel set his left foot - ",
    "answer": "on the earth 10:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Naomi asked her daughters in-law are there any yet sons in this place - ",
    "answer": "my womb 1:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long shall the two witnesses prophesy - ",
    "answer": "1260 days 11:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"why have I found grace in thine eyes, that thou should take knowledge of me, seeing I am a stranger\" - ",
    "answer": "Ruth 2:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the mouth of the beast that arose out of the sea - ",
    "answer": "a lion 13:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"who art thou my daughter\" - ",
    "answer": "Naomi to Ruth 3:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the great red dragon had ten of these - ",
    "answer": "horns 12:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Paul writes they are many unruly and vain talkers and deceivers specially they of the -- - ",
    "answer": "circumcision 1:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was given unto them that sat on the thrones - ",
    "answer": "judgment 20:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the place where it is said ye are not my people there it shall be said unto them ye are the -- of the -- God - ",
    "answer": "sons, living 1:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who gave Ruth conception - ",
    "answer": "the Lord 4:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "These are they which were not defiled with women for they are -- - ",
    "answer": "virgins 14:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they shall need no -- neither the light of the sun - ",
    "answer": "candle 22:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then shall the children of Judah and the children of Israel be gathered together and appoint themselves one -- and they shall come up out of the land, for great shall be the day of Jezreel - ",
    "answer": "head 1:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I will shew thee the -- the Lamb's wife - ",
    "answer": "bride 21:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose mouths must be -- who subvert -- , teaching things they ought not for -- sake - ",
    "answer": "stopped, whole houses, filthy lucre 1:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "grace be unto you and peace from Him which -- and which -- and which -- - ",
    "answer": "is, was, is to come 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the women told Naomi, he shall be unto thee a -- of thy life and a -- in thine old age - ",
    "answer": "restorer, nourisher 4:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Revelation 19:7 whose marriage is come - ",
    "answer": "marriage of the lamb 19:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in giving her the six measures of barley how did Boaz not want Ruth to go unto her mother in-law' - ",
    "answer": "empty 3:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much she had glorified herself and lived deliciously so much torment and -- give her - ",
    "answer": "sorrow 18:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who and what did Boaz say Ruth had left to come unto a people which she knew not heretofore - ",
    "answer": "father, mother, land of her nativity 2:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the woman that sat on the scarlet colored beast arrayed in - ",
    "answer": "purple and scarlet color 17:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Naomi say she was too old to have - ",
    "answer": "a husband 1:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the Lord did another out of the altar say are true and righteous - ",
    "answer": "His judgments 16:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Boaz to Ruth, the Lord -- thy work and a full -- be given thee of the Lord God of Israel under whose -- thou art come to -- - ",
    "answer": "recompense, reward, wings trust 2:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the King of saints are described as just and true - ",
    "answer": "His ways 15:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "would ye -- for them till they were grown - ",
    "answer": "tarry 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what attire shall the two witnesses prophesy - ",
    "answer": "sackcloth 11:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the women told Naomi thy daughter in-law which loveth thee is better to thee than this many sons - ",
    "answer": "seven 4:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To which church, I know thy works and tribulation and poverty (but thou art rich) - ",
    "answer": "Smyrna 2:8,9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then she said sit -- my daughter, until thou know how the matter will fall, for the man will not be in -- until he have -- the thing this day - ",
    "answer": "still, rest, finished 3:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to him that overcometh Jesus promise to confess his name before His Father and before His -- - ",
    "answer": "angels 3:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who said this about the Cretians, are always liars, evil beasts, slow bellies - ",
    "answer": "one of themselves a prophet of their own 1:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the elders clothed in - ",
    "answer": "white raiment 4:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what word did Paul use to describe the witness of the Cretian prophet - ",
    "answer": "true 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who/what did John see in the midst of the throne, and of the four beasts and in the midst of the elders - ",
    "answer": "a Lamb as it had been slain, having seven horns and seven eyes 5:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Naomi take the child and laid him - ",
    "answer": "in her bosom 4:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the color of the second horse - ",
    "answer": "red 6:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ruth told Boaz he has comforted her and has spoken to her this way - ",
    "answer": "friendly 2:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was number of them that were sealed from all tribes of the children of Israel - ",
    "answer": "144, 000 7:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "nay my daughters for it grieveth me much for your sakes that the -- of the Lord is gone out against me - ",
    "answer": "hand 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the angel cast the censer after he filled it with fire - ",
    "answer": "into the earth 8:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Paul tell Titus to rebuke the Cretians - ",
    "answer": "sharply 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the locust power was described as the power of these - ",
    "answer": "scorpions of the earth 9:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Naomi become unto the child - ",
    "answer": "nurse 4:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How was the cry of the mighty angel described - ",
    "answer": "as when a lion roareth 10:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "at what time did Boaz tell Ruth to come and eat of the bread and dip thy morsel in the vinegar - ",
    "answer": "mealtime 2:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the wife of the lamb arrayed in - ",
    "answer": "fine linen, clean and white 19:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the bible says that Orpah kissed her mother in-law but Ruth did this - ",
    "answer": "clave unto her 1:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold thy sister in-law is gone back unto her -- and unto her -- - ",
    "answer": "people, gods 1:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many crowns did the great red dragon have on his head - ",
    "answer": "seven 12:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and from the seven spirits which are before His -- - ",
    "answer": "throne 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "besides whom did Ruth sit - ",
    "answer": "the reapers 2:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the dragon give to the beast that arose out of the sea - ",
    "answer": "power, seat, great authority 13:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Paul tell Titus to rebuke them sharply - ",
    "answer": "that they may be sound in the faith 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "so he can see the Lamb's wife, to where was John carried in the spirit - ",
    "answer": "a great and high mountain 21:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who named the child of Ruth and Boaz - ",
    "answer": "the women the neighbors of Naomi 4:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they lived and reigned with Christ a -- - ",
    "answer": "thousand years 20:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Paul writes not giving heed to Jewish fables, and commandments of men, what did he say these do - ",
    "answer": "turn from the truth 1:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did the angel tell John seal not the sayings of the prophecy of the book - ",
    "answer": "for the time is at hand 22:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "There is a son born to Naomi and they called his name -- - ",
    "answer": "Obed 4:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for she saith in her heart I sit a -- and am no --and shall see no -- - ",
    "answer": "queen, widow, sorrow 18:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and she did eat and was -- and left - ",
    "answer": "sufficed 2:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the woman upon scarlet colored beast decked with - ",
    "answer": "gold, precious stones and pearls 17:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Ruth said, -- me not to leave thee or to return from -- after thee, for wither thou goest I will -- where thou lodgest I will -- thy people shall be my -- and thy God my -- - ",
    "answer": "entreat, following, go, lodge, people, God 1:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the fourth angel pour out his vial - ",
    "answer": "upon the sun 16:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Unto whom are all things pure - ",
    "answer": "the pure 1:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the song what of the Lord are made manifest - ",
    "answer": "His judgments 15:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "he is the father of Jesse the father of -- - ",
    "answer": "David 4:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "These are they which follow the -- whither soever He goeth - ",
    "answer": "Lamb 14:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Ruth rose up to glean what did Boaz command his young men - ",
    "answer": "let her glean even among the sheaves and reproach her not, and let fall some of the handfuls of purpose for her that she may glean among the sheaves and reproach her not 2:15,16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the dragon drew a third part of the stars of heaven with this - ",
    "answer": "his tail 12:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where thou diest, will I die and there will I be -- - ",
    "answer": "buried 1:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To Philadelphia it is written, these things write He that is holy, He that is true He that hath the key of -- - ",
    "answer": "David 3:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "until what time did Ruth glean in the field - ",
    "answer": "even 2:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \" the Lord do so to me and more also if aught but death part thee and me\" - ",
    "answer": "Ruth 1:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the elders have on their heads - ",
    "answer": "crowns of gold 4:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John said the seven horns and seven eyes of the ",
    "answer": ""
  },
  {
    "stem": "Lamb are the seven Spirits of God sent forth into this place - ",
    "answer": "all the earth 5:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Pharez begat -- - ",
    "answer": "Hezron 4:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Power was given to him that sat on the red horse to take this from the earth and that they should kill one another - ",
    "answer": "peace 6:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "unto whom is nothing pure - ",
    "answer": "unto them that are defiled and unbelieving 1:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "First tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Judah 7:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "unto them that are defiled and unbelieving Paul writes even these are defiled - ",
    "answer": "mind, conscience 1:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when the censer was cast into the earth - ",
    "answer": "there was voices, thundering, lightnings and earthquake 8:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Hezron begat -- - ",
    "answer": "Ram 4:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the locusts commanded not to hurt - ",
    "answer": "grass of the earth, any green thing, any tree 9:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how much was it after Ruth beat out that she had gleaned - ",
    "answer": "about and ephah of barley 2:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What happened when the mighty angel cried with a loud voice - ",
    "answer": "seven thunders uttered their voices 10:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Naomi do when she saw Ruth was stedfastly minded to go with her - ",
    "answer": "she left speaking unto her 1:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "They profess that they know God, but in -- they deny Him, being abominable and -- and unto every good works -- - ",
    "answer": "work, disobedient, reprobate 1:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "These are the two -- trees, and the two -- standing before the God of the earth - ",
    "answer": "olive, candlesticks 11:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To Smyrna it was told I know the blasphemy of them which say they are Jews and are not, but are - ",
    "answer": "the synagogue of satan 2:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and Ram begat -- - ",
    "answer": "Amminadab 4:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "One of the heads of the beast was wounded unto death , what happened to the deadly wound - ",
    "answer": "it was healed 13:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and her mother in-law said unto her where has thou gleaned today? and where -- thou - ",
    "answer": "wroughtest 2:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but the rest of the dead lived not till the thousand years were finished this is the -- resurrection - ",
    "answer": "first 20:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when Naomi and Ruth came to Bethlehem - ",
    "answer": "all the city was moved about them, and they said is this Naomi 1:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "These were redeemed from among men being the -- unto God and to the Lamb - ",
    "answer": "first fruits 14:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and Amminadab begat -- - ",
    "answer": "Nashon 4:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "he that is -- let him be -- still, and he which is -- let him be -- still, and he that is -- let him be -- still and he that is -- let him be -- still - ",
    "answer": "unjust/unjust, filthy/filthy, righteous/righteous, holy/holy 22:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"blessed be he of the Lord who hath not left off his kindness to the living and to the dead\" - ",
    "answer": "Naomi 2:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Naomi not want the city to call her - ",
    "answer": "Naomi 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Like what stone was the light of Jerusalem - ",
    "answer": "jasper stone, clear as crystal 21:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Rev 1:5 what kind of witness is Jesus Christ - ",
    "answer": "faithful"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Naomi tell the city to call her - ",
    "answer": "Mara 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what does the fine linen of the Lamb's wife represent - ",
    "answer": "the righteousness of the saints 19:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Nashon begat -- - ",
    "answer": "Salmon 4:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Therefore shall her plagues come in one day -- and -- and -- and she shall be utterly burned with fire, for strong is the Lord God who judgeth her - ",
    "answer": "death, mourning, famine 18:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ruth kept fast by the maidens of Boaz to glean until they end of these two harvest - ",
    "answer": "barley harvest, wheat harvest 2:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the golden cup in the woman's hand full of - ",
    "answer": "abomination and filthiness of her fornication 17:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Salmom begat -- - ",
    "answer": "Boaz 4:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was given to the fourth angel to scorch men with fire - ",
    "answer": "power 16:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Naomi say had dealt very bitterly with her - ",
    "answer": "the Almighty 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did John say happened to the temple of the tabernacle of the testimony in heaven - ",
    "answer": "it was opened 15:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Boaz begat -- - ",
    "answer": "Obed 4:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I went out -- and the Lord hath brought me home again -- - ",
    "answer": "full, empty 1:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who would cast some of Smyrna into to prison and for what purpose - ",
    "answer": "the devil, that they may be tried 2:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He that openeth and no man -- and shutteth and no man -- - ",
    "answer": "shutteth, openeth 3:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Obed begat -- - ",
    "answer": "Jesse 4:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what proceeded out of the throne - ",
    "answer": "lightnings, thundering, voices 4:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why then call ye me Naomi, seeing the Lord hath -- against me and the Almighty hath -- me - ",
    "answer": "testified, afflicted 1:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who fell down before the Lamb after He had taken the book out of the right hand of Him that sat on the throne - ",
    "answer": "the four beasts and the four and twenty elders 5:7-8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and Jesse begat -- - ",
    "answer": "David 4:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was given to him that sat on the red horse - ",
    "answer": "a great sword 6:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what nationality was Ruth - ",
    "answer": "Moabitess 1:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Second tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Reuben 7:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many chapters in Ruth - ",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the seven angels which had the seven trumpets prepared themselves to -- - ",
    "answer": "sound 8:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when did Ruth and Naomi come to Bethlehem - ",
    "answer": "beginning of the barley harvest 1:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who were the locusts commanded to hurt - ",
    "answer": "those men which have not the seal of God in their foreheads 9:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Last word in Ruth - ",
    "answer": "David 4:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John stated he was about to do this when the seven thunders uttered their voices - ",
    "answer": "write 10:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what proceed out of the mouth of the two witnesses - ",
    "answer": "fire 11:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who wondered after the beast - ",
    "answer": "all the world 13:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the dragon cast the stars he drew - ",
    "answer": "to the earth 12:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Blessed and -- is he that hath part in the first resurrection on such the -- death hath no power but they shall be -- of God and Christ and shall reign with Him a thousand years - ",
    "answer": "holy, second, priests 20:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And in their mouth was found no --, for they are without -- before the throne of God - ",
    "answer": "guile, fault 14:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "blessed are they that do His commandments that they may have -- to the tree of life and may enter in through the -- of the city - ",
    "answer": "right, gates 22:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the city had twelve gates who was at the gates - ",
    "answer": "twelve angels 21:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus is the first begotten of this group - ",
    "answer": "the dead 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what are they said to be which are called to the marriage supper of the Lamb - ",
    "answer": "blessed 19:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the kings of the earth who have committed fornication and lived deliciously with her shall bewail her and -- for her when they shall see the smoke of her burning - ",
    "answer": "lament 18:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was written upon the woman's forehead - ",
    "answer": "mystery, Babylon the great, the mother of harlots and abominations of the earth 17:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "men were scorched with great heat, what did they do to the name of God - ",
    "answer": "blasphemed 16:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the seven angels with the seven plagues clothed in - ",
    "answer": "pure and white linen 15:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the dragon stood before the woman for this purpose - ",
    "answer": "to devour her child as soon as it was born 12:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To Philadelphia it is written behold I set before thee an -- door - ",
    "answer": "open 3:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the seven lamps burning before the throne represent - ",
    "answer": "the seven Spirits of God 4:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what musical instrument did the four and twenty elders have - ",
    "answer": "harps 5:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the third beast say when the third seal was opened - ",
    "answer": "come and see 6:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Third tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Gad 7:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When the first angel sounded what was the hail and fire mingled with - ",
    "answer": "blood 8:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The locust were commanded not to kill but do this to those which had not the seal of God in their foreheads - ",
    "answer": "torment them five months 9:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Regarding what the seven thunders uttered what did the voice from heaven tell John to do - ",
    "answer": "seal them up and write them not 10:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who will the fire that proceed out of the mouth of the two witnesses devour - ",
    "answer": "their enemies 11:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long would Smyrna have tribulation - ",
    "answer": "ten days 2:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV and they worshipped the beast saying ... - ",
    "answer": "who is like unto the beast, who is able to make war with him 13:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from what will satan be loosed when the thousand years expires - ",
    "answer": "his prison 20:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John saw another angel flying in the midst of heaven having the everlasting gospel to preach unto these groups - ",
    "answer": "nation, kindred, tongue, people 14:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who are without the city - ",
    "answer": "dogs, sorcerers, whoremongers, murderers, idolaters and whosoever loveth and maketh a lie 22:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what names are written on the twelve gates - ",
    "answer": "names of the twelve tribes of the children of Israel 21:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the prince of the kings of the -- - ",
    "answer": "earth 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he saith unto me these are the true sayings of -- - ",
    "answer": "God 19:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "standing a far off for the fear of her torment saying --, -- that great city Babylon that mighty city for in one -- is thy judgment come - ",
    "answer": "alas,alas, hour 18:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the woman upon the beast drunken with - ",
    "answer": "blood of the saints, blood of the martyrs of Jesus 17:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they repented not to give Him -- - ",
    "answer": "glory 16:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the seven angels with the seven plagues breasts girded with - ",
    "answer": "golden girdles 15:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Smyrna was promised a crown of life if they were faithful unto this - ",
    "answer": "death 2:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the church, thou has a little strength, and has kept my word and has not denied my name - ",
    "answer": "Philadelphia 3:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was the sea of glass like unto crystal located - ",
    "answer": "before the throne 4:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what are the golden vials full of odors - ",
    "answer": "the prayers of the saints 5:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the third seal was open what color was the horse John saw - ",
    "answer": "black 6:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Fourth tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Asher 7:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the hail and fire mingled with blood was cast upon the earth what was burnt up - ",
    "answer": "the third part of trees and all green grass 8:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How was the torment of the locust described - ",
    "answer": "as the torment of a scorpion when he striketh a man 9:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Towards where did the angel which stood upon the sea and earth lift up his hand - ",
    "answer": "toward heaven 10:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "These have power to shut -- that it rain not in the days of their -- - ",
    "answer": "heaven, prophecy 11:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Unto the beast from the sea was a mouth given what was it speaking - ",
    "answer": "great things and blasphemies 13:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of child did the woman bring forth - ",
    "answer": "man child 12:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he shall go out to deceive the nations which are in the four quarters of the earth -- and -- to gather them to battle - ",
    "answer": "gog, magog 20:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what hour did the angel say has come - ",
    "answer": "the hour of His (God's) judgment 14:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I Jesus have sent my angel to testify unto you these things in the -- - ",
    "answer": "churches 22:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many foundations did the wall of the city have - ",
    "answer": "twelve 21:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what has Jesus washed us from our sins - ",
    "answer": "in His own blood 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And I fell at his -- to worship him and he said unto me see thou do it not, I am thy -- , and of thy -- that have the testimony of Jesus - ",
    "answer": "fellow servant, brethren 19:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the merchants of the earth shall weep and mourn over her for no man buyeth their --anymore - ",
    "answer": "merchandise 18:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did John say he did when he saw the woman upon the scarlet colored beast - ",
    "answer": "he wondered with great admiration 17:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the fifth angel pour out his vial - ",
    "answer": "upon the seat of the beast 16:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did one of the beast give to the seven angels - ",
    "answer": "seven golden vials full of the wrath of God 15:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what death shall not hurt he that overcometh - ",
    "answer": "the second 2:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold I will make them of the -- of satan which say they are Jews and do lie - ",
    "answer": "synagogue 3:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and in the midst of the throne, and round about the throne were -- beasts - ",
    "answer": "four 4:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they sung a -- song - ",
    "answer": "new 5:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did he that sat on the black horse have in his hand - ",
    "answer": "a pair of balances 6:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Fifth tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Nephthalim 7:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the second angel sounded what was cast into the sea - ",
    "answer": "a great mountain burning with fire 8:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will happen in those days when men shall seek death - ",
    "answer": "they shall not find it 9:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, and sware by Him that liveth for ever and ever who created heaven and the things that therein are and the earth and the things that therein are, and the sea and the things that therein are, that there should be .. - ",
    "answer": "time no longer 10:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and have power over waters to turn them into -- - ",
    "answer": "blood 11:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Power was given to the beast to continue how many months - ",
    "answer": "forty two months 13:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what was the woman's child to rule all nations - ",
    "answer": "a rod of iron 12:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the number that satan gathers from the four quarters of the earth is described as - ",
    "answer": "the sand of the sea 20:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and worship Him that made heaven and earth and the sea and the -- of waters - ",
    "answer": "fountains 14:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I am the -- and -- of David and bright and morning star - ",
    "answer": "root, offspring 22:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose names were in the twelve foundation - ",
    "answer": "twelve apostles of the Lamb 21:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and has made us kings and -- unto God and His Father - ",
    "answer": "priests 1:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the angel tell John to worship - ",
    "answer": "God 19:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "list the merchandise - ",
    "answer": "gold, silver, precious stones, pearls, fine linen, purple, silk, scarlet, thyine wood, vessels of ivory, vessels of most precious wood, brass,iron, marble, cinnamon, odours, ointments, frankincense, wine, oil, fine flour, wheat, beasts, sheep, horses, chariots, slaves, souls of men 18:12-13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the angel said unto me, wherefore didst thou --, I will tell thee the mystery of the woman and of the beast that carrieth her which had the seven heads and ten horns - ",
    "answer": "marvel 17:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and his kingdom was full of -- and they gnawed their -- for pain - ",
    "answer": "darkness, tongues 16:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the temple was filled with -- from the glory of God - ",
    "answer": "smoke 15:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Which church was said to dwell where satan's seat is - ",
    "answer": "Pergamos 2:12,13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "those which say they are Jews but are not will be made to worship at Philadelphia's feet and will also know this of them - ",
    "answer": "that they are loved by Jesus 3:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the four beasts full of before and behind - ",
    "answer": "eyes 4:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and thou has redeemed us to God by the blood out of every -- and tongue and -- and nation - ",
    "answer": "kindred, people 5:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the voice John heard, say was for a penny - ",
    "answer": "a measure of wheat 6:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Sixth tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Manasses 7:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when the great mountain burning with fire was cast into the sea - ",
    "answer": "third part of the sea became blood, third part of creatures which were in the sea and had life died, and the third part of the ships were destroyed 8:8-9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Men shall desire to die, but what will death do - ",
    "answer": "flee from them 9:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But in the days of the -- of the seventh angel when he shall begin to sound, the -- of God should be finished as He hath declared to His servants the -- - ",
    "answer": "voice, mystery, prophets 10:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and to smite the earth with all -- as often as they will - ",
    "answer": "plagues 11:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The beast opened his mouth in blasphemy against God to blaspheme three things name them - ",
    "answer": "God's name, His tabernacle, and them that dwell in heaven 13:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was the woman's child caught up to - ",
    "answer": "to God and to His throne 12:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they went up on the -- of the earth and compassed the camp of the saints and the beloved city - ",
    "answer": "breadth 20:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which angel proclaimed \"if any man worship the beast and his image and receive his mark in his forehead or in his hand\" - ",
    "answer": "third angel 14:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the Spirit and the -- say come - ",
    "answer": "bride 22:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John said he that talked with me had this instrument to measure the city, the gates and the wall - ",
    "answer": "a golden reed 21:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to Him be -- and dominion - ",
    "answer": "glory 1:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the testimony of Jesus - ",
    "answer": "the spirit of prophecy 19:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the fruits that thy soul lusted after are departed from thee, and all things which were --and goodly are departed from thee, and thou shalt find them no more at all - ",
    "answer": "dainty 18:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the angel told John the beast will ascend out of the bottomless pit and go into -- - ",
    "answer": "perdition 17:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And blasphemed the God of heaven because of their -- and their -- and repented not of their deeds - ",
    "answer": "pains, sores 16:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "no man was able to enter the temple until this occurred - ",
    "answer": "the seven plagues of the seven angels were fulfilled 15:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which faithful martyr was slain among them at Pergamos - ",
    "answer": "Antipas 2:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because Philadelphia has kept the word of His patience what did Jesus promise to keep them from - ",
    "answer": "the hour of temptation 3:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the first beast like - ",
    "answer": "a lion 4:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And has made us unto our God kings and -- - ",
    "answer": "priests 5:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the voice said three measures of this grain for a penny - ",
    "answer": "barley 6:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Seventh tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Simeon 7:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what fell from heaven when the third angel sounded - ",
    "answer": "a great star 8:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will happen to the two witnesses when they have finished their testimony - ",
    "answer": "the beast that ascend out of the bottomless pit will make war against them, overcome them and kill them 11:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was John commanded by the voice from heaven to take out of the hand of the angel that stood upon the sea and earth - ",
    "answer": "the little book which is open 10:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the locusts was described as horses prepared unto battle - ",
    "answer": "the shapes 9:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to what place did the woman flee - ",
    "answer": "the wilderness 12:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "as they compassed the city fire came down from God and did this to them - ",
    "answer": "devoured them 20:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And it was given unto him to make -- with the saints and overcome them - ",
    "answer": "war 13:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and whosoever will how may he take of the water of life - ",
    "answer": "freely 22:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the city lieth -- - ",
    "answer": "foursquare 21:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold He cometh with -- - ",
    "answer": "clouds 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was He that sat on the white horse called - ",
    "answer": "faithful and true 19:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The -- of these things, which were made rich by her, shall stand a far off for the fear of her torment, weeping and wailing - ",
    "answer": "merchants 18:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what do the seven heads of the beast represent - ",
    "answer": "seven mountains 17:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the sixth angel pour out his vial - ",
    "answer": "upon the great river Euphrates 16:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the following angel proclaimed Babylon is fallen is fallen because she made all nations drink of this - ",
    "answer": "the wine of the wrath of her fornication 14:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where will the dead bodies of the two witnesses lie - ",
    "answer": "in the street of the great city 11:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To which church was this directed, and thou holdest fast my name, and has not denied my faith - ",
    "answer": "Pergamos 2:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who will the hour of temptation try - ",
    "answer": "them that dwell upon the earth 3:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the second beast like - ",
    "answer": "a calf 4:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the number of them was ten thousand times ten thousands and -- of -- - ",
    "answer": "thousands, thousands 5:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the voice say must not be hurt - ",
    "answer": "the oil and wine 6:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Eighth tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Levi 7:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John said the great star that fell from heaven when the third angel sounded was burning as - ",
    "answer": "a lamp 8:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were on the heads of the locusts - ",
    "answer": "crowns like gold 9:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"give me the little book\" - ",
    "answer": "John 10:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who prepared a place for the woman in the wilderness - ",
    "answer": "God 12:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the bible says every eye shall see and they also that did this to Him - ",
    "answer": "pierced Him 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how is the wine of the wrath of God poured out - ",
    "answer": "without mixture 14:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the waters of the river Euphrates was dried so that this many happen - ",
    "answer": "that the way of the kings of the east might be prepared 16:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and there are seven kings -- are fallen and one is and the other is yet to come, when he cometh he must continue a short -- - ",
    "answer": "five, space 17:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And saying --, -- that great city that was clothed in fine linen, and purple and scarlet and decked with gold and precious stones and pearls - ",
    "answer": "alas, alas 18:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in righteousness He doth judge and make -- - ",
    "answer": "war 19:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what fled away from the face of Him that sat on the great white throne - ",
    "answer": "the earth and heaven 20:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the length and the -- and the -- of it are all equal - ",
    "answer": "breadth, height 21:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "if any man shall add unto these things God shall add unto him the -- that are written in this book - ",
    "answer": "plagues 22:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and power was given him over all -- and -- and -- - ",
    "answer": "kindreds, tongues, nations 13:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who said come and see at the opening of the fourth seal - ",
    "answer": "the fourth beast 6:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How are the faces of the locusts described - ",
    "answer": "faces of men 9:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Upon what did the great star fall when the third angel sounded - ",
    "answer": "third part of the rivers upon the fountains of waters 8:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ninth tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Issachar 7:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "spiritually what is the great city called where the bodies of the two witnesses lie - ",
    "answer": "Egypt and Sodom 11:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The thousands of voices round about the throne states the Lamb is worthy to receive these - ",
    "answer": "power,riches, wisdom, strength, honor, glory, blessing 5:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "describe the face of the third beast - ",
    "answer": "face of a man 4:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He that overcometh will I make a pillar in the -- of my God - ",
    "answer": "temple 3:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Pergamos had among them they that hold the doctrine of this man - ",
    "answer": "Balaam 2:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the angel tell John to do with the book - ",
    "answer": "take it and eat it up 10:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long should the woman be fed in the wilderness - ",
    "answer": "1260 days 12:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will all kindreds of the earth do because of Him - ",
    "answer": "wail 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where is the wine of the wrath of God poured out - ",
    "answer": "into the cup of His indignation 14:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to what does John liken the unclean spirits he saw come out of the mouth of the dragon, and the mouth of the beast and out of the mouth of the false prophet - ",
    "answer": "like frogs 16:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the beast that was and is not, even he is the -- and is of the seven and goeth into perdition - ",
    "answer": "eighth 17:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For in one -- so great riches is come to nought and every shipmaster, and all the company in ships, and sailors as many as trade by sea, stood afar off - ",
    "answer": "hour 18:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "describe the eyes of Him that sat on the white horse - ",
    "answer": "flame of fire 19:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and I saw the -- small and great stand before -- and the books were opened and another book was opened which was the book of -- and the dead were -- out of those things which were written in the books, according to their -- - ",
    "answer": "dead, God, life, judged, works 20:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the measure of the city - ",
    "answer": "twelve thousand furlongs 21:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and if any man shall take away the words of the book of this prophecy God shall take away his part out of the -- and out of the holy city and from the things which are written in this book - ",
    "answer": "book of life 22:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "all that dwell upon the earth shall worship the beast whose name are not written in this book - ",
    "answer": "the book of life of the lamb slain from the foundation of the world 13:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How does John describe the fourth horse he saw - ",
    "answer": "pale 6:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How was the hair of the locusts - ",
    "answer": "hair of women 9:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of the great star that fell when the third angel sounded - ",
    "answer": "wormwood 8:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Tenth tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Zabulon 7:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the war in heaven who fought - ",
    "answer": "Michael and His angels fought against the dragon and his angels 12:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Blessing, and honor, glory and --be unto Him that sitteth on the throne and unto the Lamb forever and ever - ",
    "answer": "power 5:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the fourth beast - ",
    "answer": "like a flying eagle 4:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the name of the city of God - ",
    "answer": "New Jerusalem 3:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Balaam taught Balac to cast this before the children of Israel and what other two things - ",
    "answer": "stumbling block, to eat things sacrificed unto idols, and to commit fornication 2:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the angel tell John the little book would do to his belly - ",
    "answer": "make it bitter 10:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for they are the spirits of -- working miracles which go forth unto the kings of the earth and of the whole world to gather them to -- to the great day of God Almighty - ",
    "answer": "devils, battle 16:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who shall see the dead bodies of the witnesses - ",
    "answer": "they of the people, kindreds, tongues 11:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If any man have an -- let him -- - ",
    "answer": "ear, hear 13:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he shall be tormented with -- and -- in the presence of the -- and in the presence of the -- - ",
    "answer": "fire, brimstone, holy angels, Lamb 14:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what do the ten horns of the beast represent - ",
    "answer": "ten kings 17:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and cried when they saw the smoke of her burning saying... - ",
    "answer": "what city is like unto this great city 18:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was upon the head of Him that sat on the white horse - ",
    "answer": "many crowns 19:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the sea gave up the dead which were in it, and -- and -- delivered up the dead which were in them - ",
    "answer": "death, hell 20:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the measurement of the wall - ",
    "answer": "144 cubits according to the measure of a man 21:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He which testifieth these things saith, surely I come quickly amen, even so .. - ",
    "answer": "come Lord Jesus 22:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I am -- and -- the beginning and the ending - ",
    "answer": "Alpha, Omega 1:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was name of him that sat on the pale horse - ",
    "answer": "death 6:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the locusts was described as a lion's - ",
    "answer": "their teeth 9:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how much of the waters became wormwood - ",
    "answer": "third part 8:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Eleventh tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Joseph 7:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long shall the dead bodies of the witnesses be seen - ",
    "answer": "three and a half days 11:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the four beasts said -- - ",
    "answer": "amen 5:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The four beast each had six of these - ",
    "answer": "wings 4:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the church, I know thy works that thou art neither cold nor hot, I would thou wert cold or hot - ",
    "answer": "Laodicea 3:14-15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Pergamos also had them that hold the -- of the Nicolaitans - ",
    "answer": "doctrine 2:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Like what did the angel tell John would be the taste of the book in his mouth - ",
    "answer": "sweet as honey 10:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did He that sat on the white horse have written that no man knew, but He Himself - ",
    "answer": "a name 19:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and -- not, neither was their place found anymore in heaven - ",
    "answer": "prevailed 12:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I John who also am your -- and -- in tribulation - ",
    "answer": "brother, companion 1:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will happen to he that leadeth into captivity - ",
    "answer": "shall go into captivity 13:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the building of the wall of city made of - ",
    "answer": "jasper 21:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what death is it, when death and hell are cast into the lake of fire - ",
    "answer": "second death 20:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many chapters in Revelation - ",
    "answer": "22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they cast -- on their heads, and cried, weeping and wailing - ",
    "answer": "dust 18:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the ten kings receive no kingdom as yet, but receive power as kings one -- with the beast - ",
    "answer": "hour 17:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold I come as a --, blessed is he that watcheth and keepeth his -- lest he walk naked and they see his -- - ",
    "answer": "thief, garments, shame 16:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the -- of their torment ascendeth up for ever and ever and they have no rest day nor night - ",
    "answer": "smoke 14:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where will they not suffer the dead bodies of the two witnesses to be put - ",
    "answer": "in graves 11:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Repent or else I will come unto thee quickly and will fight against them with the sword of my -- - ",
    "answer": "mouth 2:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did the Lord say He will do to Laodicea because they are neither cold nor hot but lukewarm - ",
    "answer": "spew them out of His mouth 3:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The four beasts rest not day nor night what were they saying - ",
    "answer": "Holy, holy, holy, Lord God Almighty which was, and is, and is to come 4:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what followed with death - ",
    "answer": "hell 6:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Twelfth tribe mentioned in the sealing - ",
    "answer": "Benjamin 7:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did many men die of the waters when wormwood fell - ",
    "answer": "because they were made bitter 8:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the breastplates of the locusts made of - ",
    "answer": "iron 9:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he said unto me thou must prophesy before many -- and nations and -- and kings - ",
    "answer": "peoples, tongues 10:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "he that killeth with the -- must be killed with the -- - ",
    "answer": "sword, sword 13:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the dragon was cast out that old --, called the -- and -- which deceiveth the whole world - ",
    "answer": "serpent, devil, satan 12:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and He was clothed with a vesture dipped in -- and his name is called the -- of God - ",
    "answer": "blood, Word 19:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the isle John placed on called - ",
    "answer": "Patmos 1:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the city was like unto pure gold like clear -- - ",
    "answer": "glass 21:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whosoever was not found written in the book of life was cast into this lake - ",
    "answer": "lake of fire 20:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Last word in Revelation - ",
    "answer": "amen"
  },
  {
    "stem": "wherein where made rich all that had -- in the sea by reason of her costliness, for in one hour is she made desolate - ",
    "answer": "ships 18:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "These have one mind and shall give their power and strength unto the -- - ",
    "answer": "beast 17:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he gathered them together into a place called in the Hebrew tongue -- - ",
    "answer": "Armageddon 16:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Here is the patience of the saints here are they that keep the -- of God and the faith of Jesus - ",
    "answer": "commandments 14:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who shall rejoice over the two witnesses, and make merry and send gifts one to another and why - ",
    "answer": "they that dwell on the earth, because the two prophets tormented them 11:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To him that overcometh will I give to eat of the hidden -- - ",
    "answer": "manna 2:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Laodicea says I am rich and increased with -- and have need of nothing - ",
    "answer": "goods 3:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the four and twenty elders cast before the throne - ",
    "answer": "their crowns 4:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Power was given to him that sat on the pale horse over the fourth part of the earth to kill with these - ",
    "answer": "sword, hunger, death, beasts of the earth 6:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many were sealed from each individual tribe - ",
    "answer": "twelve thousand"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when the fourth angel sounded - ",
    "answer": "third part of the sun was smitten, third part of the moon, third part of the stars, so that they were darkened, the day shone not for a third part and the night likewise 8:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the sound of the locusts wings - ",
    "answer": "sound of chariots of many horses running to battle 9:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the seventh angel pour out his vial - ",
    "answer": "into the air 16:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to what place was the devil and his angels cast out - ",
    "answer": "the earth 12:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Here is the patience and the -- of the saints - ",
    "answer": "faith 13:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what are those that die in the Lord said to be - ",
    "answer": "blessed 14:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "These shall make war with the -- and the Lamb shall overcome them for He is Lord of -- and King of --and they that are with Him are called -- and faithful - ",
    "answer": "Lamb, lords, kings, chosen 17:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Rejoice over he, thou heaven and ye holy -- and -- for God hath avenged you on her - ",
    "answer": "apostles, prophets 18:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who followed Him that sat on the white horse - ",
    "answer": "armies in heaven 19:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "first foundation of the city - ",
    "answer": "jasper 21:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did John say he was in the isle of Patmos - ",
    "answer": "for the word of God and for the testimony of Jesus Christ 1:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will be written on the white stone - ",
    "answer": "a new name 2:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and knowest not that thou art -- and miserable and -- and blind and -- - ",
    "answer": "wretched, poor, naked 3:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \" thou art worthy o Lord to receive glory and honor and power, for thou has created all things for thy pleasure they are and were created - ",
    "answer": "the four and twenty elders 4:10-11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did John see under the altar when the fifth seal was opened - ",
    "answer": "the souls of them that were slain for the word of God and for the testimony which they held 6:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The great multitude which no man could number stood before the throne and before the Lamb, clothed with white robes what was in their hands - ",
    "answer": "palms 7:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "--, --, -- to the inhabiters of the earth by reason of the voices of the trumpets of the three angels which are yet to sound. - ",
    "answer": "woe, woe,woe"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what part of the locusts were like scorpions - ",
    "answer": "their tails 9:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what entered the two witnesses after three and a half days and what did they do - ",
    "answer": "Spirit of life from God, they stood upon their feet 11:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the loud voice said the accuser of the brethren accuse them before God how often - ",
    "answer": "day and night 12:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John beheld another beast from where was it coming up out of - ",
    "answer": "the earth 13:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "yea, saith the Spirit that they may rest from their -- and their works do follow them - ",
    "answer": "labours 14:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the seventh angel poured out his vial into the air what did the great voice out of the temple of heaven from the throne say - ",
    "answer": "it is done 16:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what does the water where the w**** sit represent - ",
    "answer": "peoples, multitudes, nations and tongues 17:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How is the angel described that took up a stone, like a great millstone and cast it into the sea - ",
    "answer": "mighty angel 18:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the armies in heaven that followed Him that sat on the white horse clothed in - ",
    "answer": "fine linen, white and clean 19:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the second foundation - ",
    "answer": "sapphire 21:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John wrote he was in the Spirit on the Lord's day and heard behind him a great voice described as - ",
    "answer": "of a trumpet 1:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who will know the new name written on the white stone - ",
    "answer": "he that receiveth it 2:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To be rich what did the Lord counsel Laodicea to buy of Him - ",
    "answer": "gold tried in the fire 3:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "name one of the two ways they overcame the devil - ",
    "answer": "blood of the lamb, word of their testimony 12:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who cried with a loud voice saying \"how long o Lord holy and true dost thou not judge and avenge our blood on them that dwell on the earth\" - ",
    "answer": "the souls of them that were slain for the word of God 6:9-10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who asked John this question, what are these that are arrayed in white robes and whence came they - ",
    "answer": "one of the elders 7:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the locusts have in their tails - ",
    "answer": "stings 9:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what fell upon them which saw the two witnesses when they stood upon their feet - ",
    "answer": "great fear 11:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the four beast give glory, honor and thanks who fell down before the throne and worship Him that liveth forever and ever - ",
    "answer": "the four and twenty elders 4:9-10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the beast that came up from the earth had two horns like this animal - ",
    "answer": "a lamb 13:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And there were voices and -- and lightnings and there was a great -- - ",
    "answer": "thunders, earthquake 16:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will hate the w****, make her desolate and naked and shall eat her flesh and burn her with fire - ",
    "answer": "the ten horns on the beast 17:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what did the mighty angel say the great city Babylon be thrown down and shall be found no more at all - ",
    "answer": "with violence 18:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "upon what did the armies of heaven follow Him that sat on the white horse - ",
    "answer": "white horses 19:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "third foundation - ",
    "answer": "chalcedony 21:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where was John told to write what he saw and where was he to send it - ",
    "answer": "in a book, to the seven churches in Asia 1:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "upon the white cloud sat one like unto the Son of man having on his head a golden crown what was in his hand - ",
    "answer": "a sharp sickle 14:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they loved not their lives unto the -- - ",
    "answer": "death 12:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To be clothed and that the shame of their nakedness do not appear what did the Lord counsel Laodicea to buy of Him - ",
    "answer": "white raiment 3:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the beasts give glory, honor and thanks to - ",
    "answer": "Him that sat on the throne who liveth forever and ever 4:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were given to souls of them under the altar - ",
    "answer": "white robes 6:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was John's response to this question, what are these that are arrayed in white robes and whence came they - ",
    "answer": "sir thou knowest 7:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For how long was the locusts power to hurt men - ",
    "answer": "five months 9:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the great voice from heaven say to the two witnesses - ",
    "answer": "come up hither 11:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "List five things of Thyatira that was known according to Rev 2:19 - ",
    "answer": "works, charity, service, faith,patience"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the beast that came up from the earth did this as a dragon - ",
    "answer": "spake 13:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "another angel came out of the temple crying with a loud voice to Him that sat on the cloud, -- in thy sickle and -- for the -- is come for thee to reap, for the -- of the earth is -- - ",
    "answer": "thrust, reap, time, harvest, ripe 14:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Into how many parts was the great city divided - ",
    "answer": "three 16:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the woman which thou sawest is that great -- which reigneth over the kings of the earth - ",
    "answer": "city 17:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose voices will no more be heard in the great Babylon - ",
    "answer": "harpers, musicians, pipers, trumpeters 18:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and out of His mouth goeth a sharp sword, that with it He should -- the nations and He shall rule them with a -- of iron and He treadeth the -- of the fierceness and wrath of Almighty God - ",
    "answer": "smite, rod, winepress 19:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "fourth foundation - ",
    "answer": "emerald 21:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "List the churches in Asia - ",
    "answer": "Ephesus, Smyrna, Pergamos, Thyatira, Sardis, Philadelphia, Laodicea 1:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the last to be -- than the first - ",
    "answer": "more 2:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To see Laodicea is counseled to anoint their eyes with this - ",
    "answer": "eyesalve 3:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the four and twenty elders fall down before - ",
    "answer": "Him that sat on the throne 4:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long were the souls under the altar told to rest - ",
    "answer": "for a little season 6:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The elder told John those arrayed in white robes have came out of this - ",
    "answer": "great tribulation 7:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they had a -- over them which was the -- of the bottomless pit - ",
    "answer": "king, angel 9:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the two witnesses ascend up to heaven - ",
    "answer": "in a cloud 11:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Therefore -- ye heavens and ye that dwell in them, -- to the inhabiters of the earth and of the sea for the -- is come down to you having great -- because he knoweth he hath but a -- time. - ",
    "answer": "rejoice, woe, devil, wrath, short 12:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he -- all the power of the first beast before him, and causeth the -- and them which dwell therein to worship the first beast whose deadly wound was -- - ",
    "answer": "exerciseth, earth, healed 13:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and He that sat on the cloud thrust in his sickle on the earth and the earth was -- - ",
    "answer": "reaped 14:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what came into remembrance before God to give unto her the cup of the wine of the fierceness of His wrath - ",
    "answer": "great Babylon 16:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and no -- of whatsoever craft he be , shall be found any more in thee - ",
    "answer": "craftsman 18:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and He hath on His vesture and on His thigh a name written - ",
    "answer": "King of kings and Lord of lords 19:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the fifth foundation - ",
    "answer": "sardonyx 21:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was the voice John heard - ",
    "answer": "behind him 1:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who beheld the two witnesses as they ascended up to heaven - ",
    "answer": "their enemies 11:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who called Jezebel a prophetess - ",
    "answer": "Jezebel 2:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As many as I love I rebuke and -- be zealous therefore and -- - ",
    "answer": "chasten, repent 3:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the four and twenty elders worship - ",
    "answer": "Him that liveth forever and ever 4:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The souls were told to rest until who be killed as they were - ",
    "answer": "their fellow servants and their brethren 6:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what have they that came out of great tribulation washed their robes and made them white in - ",
    "answer": "the blood of the Lamb 7:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the king over the locust called in the Hebrew tongue - ",
    "answer": "Abaddon 9:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "another angel came out of the temple which is in heaven what tool did he also have - ",
    "answer": "a sharp sickle 14:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the dragon do when he saw he was cast unto the earth - ",
    "answer": "he persecuted the woman which brought forth the man child 12:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many golden candlesticks did John see - ",
    "answer": "seven 1:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and every -- fled away, and the -- were not found - ",
    "answer": "island, mountains 16:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what sound will no more be heard in the great Babylon - ",
    "answer": "sound of a millstone 18:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "on which two places was the name King of kings and Lord of lords written - ",
    "answer": "vesture, thigh 19:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "sixth foundation - ",
    "answer": "sardius 21:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the second beast doeth great wonders so that he makes this come down from heaven on the earth in the sight of all men - ",
    "answer": "fire 13:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was given to the woman that she might fly into the wilderness into her place - ",
    "answer": "two wings of a great eagle 12:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold I stand at the door and -- - ",
    "answer": "knock 3:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what great event occurred at the opening of the sixth seal - ",
    "answer": "a great earthquake 6:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Therefore are they before the throne God and serve Him -- and --in His temple - ",
    "answer": "day, night 7:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Apollyon is the name of the king over the loucust was tongue is this name derived from - ",
    "answer": "Greek 9:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the same hour the two witnesses ascended up to heaven there was a great earthquake what part of the city fell and how many were slain of men - ",
    "answer": "tenth part of the city fell, seven thousand 11:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did they of Thyatira allow Jezebel to do - ",
    "answer": "seduce God's servants, commit fornication, eat things sacrificed unto idols 2:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by what means does the second beast deceive them that dwell on the earth - ",
    "answer": "by means of the miracles 13:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the angel that had power over fire come out from - ",
    "answer": "the altar 14:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the weight of every stone of the hail - ",
    "answer": "about the weight of a talent 16:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what light will no more in the great Babylon - ",
    "answer": "light of the candle 18:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was the angel standing that summoned the fowls that fly in the midst of heaven to come and gather unto the supper of the great God - ",
    "answer": "in the sun 19:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "seventh foundation - ",
    "answer": "chrysolite 21:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did John see in the midst of the seven golden candlesticks - ",
    "answer": "one like unto the Son of man 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Jezebel given to repent of her fornication but did not - ",
    "answer": "space 2:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said if any man hear my voice and open the door He will come in and do this thing - ",
    "answer": "and sup with him and he with me 3:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the sun become when the sixth seal was opened - ",
    "answer": "black as sackcloth of hair 6:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "They shall hunger no more neither -- - ",
    "answer": "thirst 7:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When the sixth angel sounded what did John hear from the four horns of the golden altar which is before God - ",
    "answer": "a voice 9:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the remnant were -- and gave glory to the God of heaven - ",
    "answer": "affrighted 11:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the second beast want them that dwell on the earth to make - ",
    "answer": "an image to the beast which had the wound by a sword and did live 13:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For how long is the woman nourished in the wilderness - ",
    "answer": "for a time, times, and half a time 12:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the angel that had power over fire tell the angel that had the sharp sickle to thrust in his sickle and gather - ",
    "answer": "clusters of vine of the earth 14:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did men do to God because of the plague of the hail - ",
    "answer": "blasphemed God 16:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the bride and bridegroom will no more be heard in Babylon - ",
    "answer": "voice 18:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the beast and kings of the earth and their armies gathered together to make against Him that sat on the horse and His armies - ",
    "answer": "war 19:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "eighth foundation - ",
    "answer": "beryl 21:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The one like unto the Son of man was clothed with a garment down to his foot where was the golden girdle - ",
    "answer": "girt about His paps 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jezebel will be cast into a bed and them that commit adultery with her into this - ",
    "answer": "great tribulation 2:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The second woe is past and behold the -- woe cometh quickly - ",
    "answer": "third 11:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did Jesus say He will grant he that overcometh to sit - ",
    "answer": "with Him in His throne 3:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what became as blood when the sixth seal was opened - ",
    "answer": "the moon 6:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Neither shall the -- light on them, nor any heat - ",
    "answer": "sun 7:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The voice told the sixth angel to do this to the four angels which are bound in the great rive Euphrates - ",
    "answer": "loose them 9:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "ninth foundation - ",
    "answer": "topaz 21:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the serpent cast out of his mouth after the woman and why - ",
    "answer": "water as a flood, that might cause her to be carried away of the flood 12:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what state did the angel say the grapes were in - ",
    "answer": "fully ripe 14:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how was the plague of hail described - ",
    "answer": "exceeding great 16:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for thy merchants were the -- men of the earth, - ",
    "answer": "great 18:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose flesh did the angel summon the fowls of heaven to come and eat at the supper - ",
    "answer": "kings, captains, mighty men, horses, them that sit on them, flesh of all men free and bond, great and small 19:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is being described like wool, white as snow - ",
    "answer": "His head and His hairs 1:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he had power to give -- unto the image of the beast, that the image of the beast should both -- and cause that as many as would not -- the image of the beast should be -- - ",
    "answer": "life, speak, worship, killed 13:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what helped the woman - ",
    "answer": "the earth 12:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what would prevent them that commit adultery with Jezebel from being cast into great tribulation - ",
    "answer": "repent of their deeds 2:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For the Lamb which is in the midst of the throne shall feed them and shall lead them unto -- - ",
    "answer": "living fountains of water 7:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For how long were the four angels prepared - ",
    "answer": "an hour, a day, a month, a year 9:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the seventh angel sounded there were great voices in this place - ",
    "answer": "heaven 11:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the sixth seal was opened the stars of heaven fell unto the earth as this - ",
    "answer": "as a fig tree casteth her untimely figs when she is shaken of a mighty wind 6:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he causeth all both small and --, rich and --, free and -- to receive a mark in their right hand or in their -- - ",
    "answer": "great, poor, bond, foreheads 13:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for by thy sorceries were all nations -- - ",
    "answer": "deceived 18:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Into what was the beast, false prophet and them that received the mark of the beast cast alive - ",
    "answer": "into a lake of fire burning with brimstone 19:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "His eyes were as a - ",
    "answer": "flame of fire 1:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "tenth foundation - ",
    "answer": "chrysoprasus 21:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the angel thrust in his sickle into the earth and gathered the vine of the earth into where did he cast it - ",
    "answer": "into the great wine press of the wrath of God 14:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The kingdoms of this world are become the kingdoms of our -- and His --and He shall reign forever and ever - ",
    "answer": "Lord, Christ 11:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And I will kill her children with -- - ",
    "answer": "death 2:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what departed as a scroll when it is rolled together - ",
    "answer": "the heaven 6:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- shall wipe away all tears from their eyes - ",
    "answer": "God 7:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much men were the four angels prepared to slay - ",
    "answer": "third part 9:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was the wine press trodden - ",
    "answer": "without the city 14:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the earth help the woman - ",
    "answer": "opened her mouth and swallowed up the flood which the dragon cast out of his mouth 12:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "no man might do these save he that had mark, or the name of the beast or the number of his name - ",
    "answer": "buy or sell 13:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose blood was found in the great Bablyon - ",
    "answer": "prophets, saints and all that were slain upon the earth 18:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and all the fowls were filled with their -- - ",
    "answer": "flesh 19:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "eleventh foundation - ",
    "answer": "jacinth 21:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "His feet were like unto fine brass as if they were burned in a -- - ",
    "answer": "furnace 1:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did the twenty four elders say were angry - ",
    "answer": "the nations 11:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "every mountain and every -- were moved out of their places - ",
    "answer": "island 6:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the number of the army of the horsemen - ",
    "answer": "two hundred thousand thousand 9:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and all the churches shall know that I am he which searcheth the reins and -- - ",
    "answer": "hearts 2:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Give the reference, \"and the dragon was wroth with the woman, and went to make war with the remnant of her seed, which keep the commandments of God and have the testimony of Jesus Christ\" - ",
    "answer": "Revelation 12:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what came out of the wine press - ",
    "answer": "blood 14:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "twelfth foundation - ",
    "answer": "amethyst 21:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and His voice as the sound of - ",
    "answer": "many waters 1:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Here is wisdom, let him that hath understanding count the number of the beast for it is the number of a man and his number is -- hundred, -- score and -- - ",
    "answer": "six, threescore, six 13:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the breastplate of them that sat on the horses - ",
    "answer": "fire, Jacinth and brimstone 9:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord promise not to put on them of Thyatira who have not the doctrine, nor known the depths of satan - ",
    "answer": "none other burden 2:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who hid themselves in the dens and in the rocks of the mountains - ",
    "answer": "kings of the earth, great men, rich men, chief captains, mighty men, every bondman, and every free man 6:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The twenty four elders which sat before God said the time is come that these should be judged - ",
    "answer": "the dead 11:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "blood came out of the wine press even unto the horse bridles by the space of how many furlongs - ",
    "answer": "1,600 furlongs 14:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the twelve gates were twelve -- - ",
    "answer": "pearls 21:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did He have in His right hand - ",
    "answer": "seven stars 1:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what went out of His mouth - ",
    "answer": "a sharp two edged sword 1:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the street of the city was pure gold, as it were -- glass - ",
    "answer": "transparent 21:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The twenty four elders declared the time is come for God to reward these groups - ",
    "answer": "servants the prophets, the saints, them that fear God's name small and great 11:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The heads of the horse were like what animal - ",
    "answer": "lions 9:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did they ask the rocks and mountains to do to them - ",
    "answer": "fall on them, hide them from the face of Him that sitteth on the throne, and from the wrath of the Lamb 6:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what kind of rod will he that is given power over the nations rule - ",
    "answer": "rod of iron 2:26-27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "as the vessels of the potter shall they be broken to -- - ",
    "answer": "shivers 2:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For the great day of His wrath is come and who shall be able to -- - ",
    "answer": "stand 6:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what issued out of the mouth of the horses - ",
    "answer": "fire, smoke and brimstone 9:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The twenty four elders declare the time is come for God to destroy them that destroy this place - ",
    "answer": "the earth 11:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was described as the sun shineth in his strength - ",
    "answer": "His countenance 1:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and I saw no temple therein, for the Lord God Almighty and the -- are the temple of it - ",
    "answer": "Lamb 21:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John states and when I saw I, fell at His feet as -- - ",
    "answer": "dead 1:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the city John saw have no need of shine in it - ",
    "answer": "sun, neither moon 21:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the temple of God was opened in heaven what was seen - ",
    "answer": "the ark of His testament 11:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "By these three were the -- part of men -- by the fire and by the smoke and by the brimstone which -- out of their mouths - ",
    "answer": "third, killed, issued 9:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Which hand did the Son of man lay on John - ",
    "answer": "His right 1:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what lighten the city John saw - ",
    "answer": "glory of God and the Lamb 21:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and there were lightnings and -- and thunderings and an -- and great hail - ",
    "answer": "voices, earthquake 11:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The horses had power in their mouth and in their -- - ",
    "answer": "tails 9:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For their tails were like unto -- and had heads and with them they do hurt - ",
    "answer": "serpents 9:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What keys did the Son of man possess - ",
    "answer": "keys of hell and death 1:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for there is no night there what of the city shall not be shut - ",
    "answer": "gates 21:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I am He that liveth and was -- and behold I am alive forevermore - ",
    "answer": "dead 1:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and there shall no wise enter into it anything that defileth, neither whatsoever worketh abomination or maketh a -- - ",
    "answer": "lie 21:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The rest of the men which were not killed by plagues repented not of the works of their hands that they should not worship these - ",
    "answer": "devils, idols of gold, silver, brass, stone, wood 9:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is missing, write the things which thou has seen, and the things which are .. - ",
    "answer": "and the things which shall be hereafter 1:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "besides not seeing what other things that are the object of men's worship not able to do - ",
    "answer": "hear , walk 9:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the seven stars represent - ",
    "answer": "the angels of the seven churches 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Neither repented they of their -- nor their sorceries nor their -- nor their thefts - ",
    "answer": "murders, fornication 9:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the seven candlestick represent - ",
    "answer": "the seven churches 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Luke writes from the beginning they were eyewitnesses and this of the word",
    "answer": "ministers 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose house did Jesus enter on the Sabbath day to eat bread when He encountered a man with dropsy",
    "answer": "one of the chief Pharisees 14:1,2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was the decree sent out by Caesar Augustus",
    "answer": "that all the world should be taxed 2:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did they come bringing to the sepulchre upon the first day of the week",
    "answer": "spices they had prepared 24:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From the council to whom was Jesus led",
    "answer": "to Pilate 23:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The feast of unleavened bread is also known as this",
    "answer": "Passover 22:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the rich men casting into the treasury",
    "answer": "gifts 21:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who spake these words to Jesus \"tell us by what authority doest thou these things? or who is he that gavest thee this authority?\"",
    "answer": "chief priest, scribes, elders 20:1-2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In which city did Jesus meet Zacchaeus",
    "answer": "Jericho 19:1-2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who to whom \"it is impossible but that offences will come, but woe unto him through whom they come\"",
    "answer": "Jesus to His disciples 17:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the story of the rich man and the steward, what was the steward accused of",
    "answer": "he had wasted his goods 16:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then drew near all the publicans and -- for to hear Him",
    "answer": "sinners 15:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And He spake a parable unto them to this end, that men ought always to pray and not to --",
    "answer": "faint 18:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who mingled the Galilaeans blood with their sacrifices",
    "answer": "Pilate 13:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Jesus had ended all His sayings in the audience of the people He entered into this place",
    "answer": "Capernaum 7:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the multitude of people gathered were so innumerable that they began to do this one upon another",
    "answer": "trode one upon another 12:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Returning from Jordan to where was Jesus led",
    "answer": "into the wilderness 4:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As the people pressed upon Jesus to hear the word of God He stood by the lake of --",
    "answer": "Genesaret 5:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The second Sabbath after the first Jesus went through this place",
    "answer": "corn fields 6:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "It was in the 15th year of this man's reign that John came preaching",
    "answer": "Tiberius Caesar 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And it came to pass afterward, that he went throughout every city and -- preaching and -- the glad tidings of the kingdom of God and the -- were with Him.",
    "answer": "village, showing, twelve 8:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "over who/what did Jesus give the twelve power and authority",
    "answer": "all devils, to cure diseases 9:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After these things the Lord appointed other -- also, and sent them -- and -- before His face into every -- and place whither He Himself would come",
    "answer": "seventy, two, two,city 10:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what had John taught his disciples to do",
    "answer": "pray 11:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "suppose ye these Galilaeans were -- above all the Galilaeans , because they suffered such things.",
    "answer": "sinners 13:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what time of day did they come to the sepulchre",
    "answer": "very early in the morning 24:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "we have found this fellow -- the nation and forbidding to give -- to Caesar saying that He Himself is -- a king",
    "answer": "perverting, tribute, Christ 23:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who entered into Judas Iscariot",
    "answer": "satan 22:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much did the poor widow cast into the treasury",
    "answer": "two mites 21:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The baptism of John was it from -- or of men",
    "answer": "heaven, 20:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides being rich, Zacchaeus was chief among this group",
    "answer": "publicans 19:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Jesus pronounce against him whom the offences come",
    "answer": "woe 17:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "give account of thy -- for thou mayest be no longer steward",
    "answer": "stewardship 16:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who murmured saying this man receiveth sinners and eateth with them",
    "answer": "scribes and pharisees 15:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the response of the lawyers and pharisees when Jesus asked, is it lawful to heal on the Sabbath day",
    "answer": "they held their peace 14:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the judge in the parable feared not -- neither regarded --",
    "answer": "God, man 18:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell His disciples the leaven of the Pharisees was",
    "answer": "hypocrisy 12:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the disciples do as they went through the corn fields",
    "answer": "plucked the ears of corn, eat them, rubbing them in their hands 6:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and forgive us our sins, for we also forgive every one that is -- to us.",
    "answer": "indebted 11:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What ruling title did Pontius Pilate have and what was his domain",
    "answer": "governor, Galilee 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who led Jesus into the wilderness",
    "answer": "the Spirit 4:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many ships did Jesus see by the lake",
    "answer": "two 5:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The taxing was first made when this individual was governor",
    "answer": "Cyrenius 2:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what state was the centurion's servant in",
    "answer": "sick and ready to die 7:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Forasmuch as many have taken in hand to set forth in order a -- of those things which are most surely believed among us",
    "answer": "declaration 1:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many devils went out of Mary Magdalene",
    "answer": "seven 8:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus sent the twelve to heal the sick and to preach this",
    "answer": "the kingdom of God 9:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How does Jesus describe the harvest",
    "answer": "great 10:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was rolled away from the sepulchre",
    "answer": "the stone 24:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Pilate asked, art thou the king of the Jesus, Jesus response was",
    "answer": "thou sayest it 23:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "With whom did Judas commune concerning betraying Jesus unto them",
    "answer": "chief priests and captains 22:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus say had cast more into the treasury than all",
    "answer": "the poor widow 21:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "They reasoned if they were to state the baptism of John was from heaven, Jesus would ask",
    "answer": "why then believed ye him not 20:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Due to the press, Zacchaeus could not see Jesus because of this physical condition",
    "answer": "he was of little of stature 19:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the widow in the parable come to judge saying",
    "answer": "avenge me of mine adversary 18:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "rather than offend one of the little ones Jesus said it were better for that person that this be hanged about his neck and he be cast into the sea",
    "answer": "millstone 17:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what shall I do for my lord taketh away from me my stewardship, I cannot -- to beg I am --",
    "answer": "dig, ashamed 16:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to go seek for the lost sheep, where does the one leave the ninety nine",
    "answer": "in the wilderness 15:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and He took him and -- him and let him go",
    "answer": "healed 14:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for there is nothing covered that shall not be -- neither hid that shall not be --",
    "answer": "revealed, known 12:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus told the people except this is done they shall all likewise perish.",
    "answer": "they repent 13:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the fishermen were gone out of the ships, what were they doing to their nets",
    "answer": "washing 5:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Jesus' illustration one will go to a friend at this hour and ask for a loan of three loaves",
    "answer": "midnight 11:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What territory was Cyrenius governor of",
    "answer": "Syria 2:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Herod was Tetrach of this place",
    "answer": "Galilee 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "While in the wilderness for how many days was Jesus tempted by the devil",
    "answer": "forty 4:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the gospel of Luke addressed to",
    "answer": "Theophilus 1:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the disciples plucked and ate the ears of corn who accused Jesus of doing that which is not lawful to do on the Sabbath days",
    "answer": "Pharisees 6:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And a certain centurion's servant who was -- unto him",
    "answer": "dear 7:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides evil spirits what had certain women been healed of",
    "answer": "infirmities 8:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell the twelve to take for their journey",
    "answer": "nothing 9:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How does Jesus describe the laborers",
    "answer": "few 10:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Upon how many did the tower in Siloam fall",
    "answer": "eighteen 13:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did they not find in the sepulchre",
    "answer": "the body of Jesus 24:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"I find no fault in this man\"",
    "answer": "Pilate to the chief priest and people 23:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the chief priests and captain feel about Judas communing with them to betray Jesus",
    "answer": "they were glad 22:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For all these have of their -- cast in unto the offering of God, but she of her -- hath cast in all the -- that she had.",
    "answer": "abundance, penury, living 21:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "they reasoned if they said John's baptism was of men, the people would do this to them",
    "answer": "stone them 20:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what tree did Zacchaeus climb in order to see Jesus",
    "answer": "sycamore 19:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say to do if thy brother trespass against thee",
    "answer": "rebuke him 17:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I am resolved what to do, that when I am put out of the stewardship, they may receive me into their --",
    "answer": "houses 16:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when found where does one lay the lost sheep",
    "answer": "on his shoulders 15:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus asked if they had an ox or ass fall into this on the Sabbath day if they will not straightway pull him out",
    "answer": "pit 14:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Yet because this widow troubleth me I will -- her, lest by her continual coming she -- me",
    "answer": "avenge, weary 18:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "that spoken in darkness will be heard where",
    "answer": "in the light 12:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what physical state did Jesus say David and they that were with him was in",
    "answer": "hungered 6:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV for a friend of mine is his journey is come to me and I have nothing to ..",
    "answer": "set before him 11:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Herod and Philip's relationship",
    "answer": "they were brothers 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Jesus eat while in the wilderness",
    "answer": "nothing 4:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Into who's ship did Jesus enter",
    "answer": "Simon's 5:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did everyone go to be taxed",
    "answer": "into their own city 2:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the centurion send unto Jesus beseeching him to come and heal his servant",
    "answer": "the elders of the Jews 7:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did Luke tell Theophilus he was writing to him",
    "answer": "that he may know the certainty of those things wherein he has been instructed 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of Herod's steward",
    "answer": "Chuza 8:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus specifically tell the twelve not to take for their journey",
    "answer": "staves, scrip, bread, money, two coats 9:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said we should pray that this person would send forth laborers into His harvest",
    "answer": "the Lord of the harvest 10:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the garment of the two men",
    "answer": "shining 24:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they were the more -- saying He stirreth up the people teaching throughout all -- beginning from Galilee to this place.",
    "answer": "fierce, Jewry 23:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the chief priest and captains covenant to give Judas",
    "answer": "money 22:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what was the temple adorned",
    "answer": "goodly stones and gifts 21:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the chief priest, scribes and elders knew that the people were persuaded of this concerning John",
    "answer": "persuaded that he was a prophet 20:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Zacchaeus, make -- and come down, for today, I must -- at thy house",
    "answer": "haste, abide 19:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And shall not God avenge His own -- which cry -- and -- unto Him though He bear long with them",
    "answer": "elect, day, night 18:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If thy brother -- forgive him",
    "answer": "repents 17:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the steward call unto him",
    "answer": "everyone of his lord's debtors 16:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who does one call to rejoice that the lost sheep is found",
    "answer": "friends and neighbors 15:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To whom did Jesus put forth a parable when He marked how they chose out the chief rooms",
    "answer": "to those which were bidden 14:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "that which was spoken in the ear in the closets shall be proclaimed in this location",
    "answer": "upon the housetops 12:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus asked if the eighteen that were slain were sinners above all the men that dwelt in this place",
    "answer": "Jerusalem 13:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus enter Simon's ship what did He pray or ask him to do",
    "answer": "thrust out a little from the land 5:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he from within shall answer and say, -- me not, the door is -- and my children are with me in --, I cannot -- and give thee.",
    "answer": "trouble, shut, bed, rise 11:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what city did Joseph depart from to go to be taxed",
    "answer": "Galilee of Nazareth 2:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Philip was Tetrach of these places",
    "answer": "Ituraea, Trachonitis 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After the forty days in the wilderness what physical state was Jesus in",
    "answer": "hungered 4:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was king Herod's domain",
    "answer": "Judaea 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did David go an eat of the shewbread and gave to them that were with him",
    "answer": "house of God 6:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the elders of the Jews say of the centurion to Jesus",
    "answer": "that he was worthy, he love their nation, and had built them a synagogue 7:4-5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name Chuza's wife",
    "answer": "Joanna 8:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and whatsoever house ye enter in there -- and thence depart",
    "answer": "abide 9:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "we are sent forth as these among wolves",
    "answer": "lambs 10:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was their reaction to seeing the two men, and what did they do",
    "answer": "afraid, bowed their faces to the earth 24:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Having heard He was a Galilaean to whose jurisdiction did Jesus belong",
    "answer": "Herod's 23:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he promised and sought opportunity to betray Him unto them in the absence of the --",
    "answer": "multitude 22:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "ftv, there shall not be left one stone upon another which shall not be ..",
    "answer": "thrown down 21:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they -- that they could not tell whence it was",
    "answer": "answered 20:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Zacchaeus receive Jesus",
    "answer": "joyfully 19:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I tell you that He will avenge them --",
    "answer": "speedily 18:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And if he -- against thee seven times in a --, and seven times in a -- turn again to thee saying I --, thou shalt forgive him.",
    "answer": "trespass, day, day, repent 17:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for the debtor that owed a hundred measures of oil what did the steward tell him to take the bill and write",
    "answer": "fifty 16:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- with me for I have found my sheep which was lost",
    "answer": "rejoice 15:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jesus say not to sit down when thou art bidden to a wedding",
    "answer": "in the highest room 14:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said do not be afraid of them that kill this and after that they have no more what they can do",
    "answer": "the body 12:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of tree did a certain man plant in his vineyard",
    "answer": "fig tree 13:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "as He sat what did Jesus do to the people out of the ship",
    "answer": "taught them 5:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Not because he is his friend, but for this reason Jesus says he will rise and give him as many as he needeth",
    "answer": "his importunity 11:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To what city did Joseph go to be taxed",
    "answer": "city of David 2:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was Terach of Abilene",
    "answer": "Lysanias 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In His state of hunger what did the devil first command Jesus to do",
    "answer": "command the stone to be made bread 4:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Zacharias' role",
    "answer": "priest 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who alone could lawfully eat the shewbread",
    "answer": "the priests 6:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Jesus was not far from the centurion's house, who did he send with a message to Jesus",
    "answer": "his friends 7:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what other woman was mentioned by name besides Joanna in Luke 8:3 as having ministered unto Jesus of their substance",
    "answer": "Susanna"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus told the twelve that whosoever will not receive you, when you go out of the city shake off the dust from your feet for this purpose",
    "answer": "testimony against them 9:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "carry neither purse, nor scrip, nor shoes and -- no man by the way.",
    "answer": "salute 10:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what question did the two men ask them at the sepulchre",
    "answer": "why seek ye the living among the dead 24:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was Herod when Jesus was sent to Him",
    "answer": "in Jerusalem 23:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is killed on the day of unleavened bread",
    "answer": "the Passover 22:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "many shall come in my name saying ,I am --",
    "answer": "Christ 21:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Neither tell I you by what -- I do these things",
    "answer": "authority 20:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the people murmured saying, that He was gone to be guest with a man that is a --",
    "answer": "sinner 19:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Nevertheless when the Son of man cometh will He find -- on the earth",
    "answer": "faith 18:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the apostles said unto the Lord, increase our --",
    "answer": "faith 17:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for the debtor that owed a hundred measures of wheat, what did the steward tell him to write on the bill",
    "answer": "fourscore 16:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how is the joy in heaven when one sinner repents compared to ninety just persons which need no repentance",
    "answer": "more 15:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who might he that bade to the feast ask that place be given for",
    "answer": "a more honorable man 14:8-9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said fear him which after he hath killed hath power to cast into this place",
    "answer": "hell 12:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when the man came and sought fruit from the fig tree",
    "answer": "he found none 13:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- out into the -- and let down your nets for a --",
    "answer": "launch, deep, draught 5:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- and it shall be given you, -- and ye shall find, -- and it shall be opened unto you",
    "answer": "ask, seek, knock 11:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What is the city of David also called",
    "answer": "Bethlehem 2:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who were the high priests",
    "answer": "Annas and Caiaphas 3:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Jesus' response to the devil's first temptation",
    "answer": "It is written, that man shall not live by bread alone, but by every word of God 4:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Of what course was Zacharias",
    "answer": "Abia 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus say was Lord also of the Sabbath",
    "answer": "Son of man 6:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The centurion sent a message to Jesus saying he was not worthy that Jesus should come under this",
    "answer": "his roof 7:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "of what did the women minister to Jesus",
    "answer": "their substance 8:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they departed and went through the -- preaching the gospel and healing everywhere",
    "answer": "towns 9:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what should first be said to every house entered",
    "answer": "peace be to this house 10:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with the shame the person that sought out the highest room would have to go to this room",
    "answer": "lowest room 14:8-9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And returned from the sepulchre and told all these things unto the --and to all the rest",
    "answer": "eleven 24:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Herod's reaction to seeing Jesus",
    "answer": "exceeding glad 23:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus sent to prepare the Passover",
    "answer": "Peter and John 22:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said when you hear of these be not terrified one is war the other is",
    "answer": "commotions 21:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did a certain man plant",
    "answer": "a vineyard 20:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much of his goods did Zacchaeus pledge to give to the poor",
    "answer": "half 19:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And He spake this parable unto certain which trusted in -- that they were -- and despised others",
    "answer": "themselves, righteous 18:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If they had faith as a grain of mustard seed, what tree did Jesus tell the apostles they would say, be thou plucked up by the roots and be thou planted in the sea and it should obey",
    "answer": "sycamine tree 17:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the lord -- the unjust steward because he had done --",
    "answer": "commended, wisely 16:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many pieces of silver does the woman have",
    "answer": "ten 15:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "as Jesus entered the synagogue and taught on the Sabbath, there was a man whose right hand was in this condition",
    "answer": "withered 6:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then he said unto the -- of the behold these -- years I come seeking fruit on this -- tree and fine none, cut it down why -- it the ground",
    "answer": "dresser, three, fig, cumbereth 13:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name Zacharias' wife",
    "answer": "Elisabeth 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many sparrows are sold for two farthing",
    "answer": "five 12:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did the word of God come to John",
    "answer": "in the wilderness 3:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From where did the devil show Jesus all the kingdom of the world in a moment of time",
    "answer": "a high mountain 4:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "identify the speaker, Master we have toiled all the night and have taken nothing, nevertheless at thy word I will let down the net",
    "answer": "Simon 5:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did Joseph go to Bethlehem to be taxed",
    "answer": "because he was of the house and lineage of David 2:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The centurion did not come to Jesus for he considered himself to be this",
    "answer": "not worthy 7:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when much people were gathered together and were come to Him from every city by what figurative language did Jesus speak",
    "answer": "parable 8:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Having heard what was done by Jesus Herod the tetrach was in this state, because it was said of some, that John was risen from the dead",
    "answer": "perplexed 9:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And if the son of peace be there, your peace shall -- upon it, if not it shall -- to you again",
    "answer": "rest, return 10:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For everyone that asketh --, and he that seeketh -- and to him that knocketh it shall be --",
    "answer": "receiveth, findeth, opened 11:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Finding no fruit on the fig tree three years what did the man command the dresser of the vineyard to do to it",
    "answer": "cut it down 13:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Herod was desirous to see Jesus a long season because he had heard many things of Him and he hoped to see this",
    "answer": "some miracle done by Jesus 23:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus instructed the disciples to follow a man when they enter the city, what was the man bearing and to where were they to follow the man",
    "answer": "a pitcher of water, into the house where he entereth 22:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Nation shall rise against nation and -- against --",
    "answer": "kingdom, kingdom 21:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the man let forth the vineyard to",
    "answer": "husbandmen 20:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If he has taken any thing from any man by this means, Zacchaeus pledged to restore him fourfold",
    "answer": "false accusation 19:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Jesus' parable two men went up to the temple to pray, to what group did the men belong",
    "answer": "one a pharisee, other publican 18:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But which of you having a servant -- or feeding -- will say unto him by and by, when he is come in from the --, go and sit down to --",
    "answer": "plowing, cattle, field, meat 17:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for the children of this -- are in their generation wiser than the children of --",
    "answer": "world, light 16:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what does the woman do when she loses one piece of sliver",
    "answer": "light a candle, sweep the house, and seek diligently till she find it 15:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when bidden to a wedding which room did Jesus say to go and sit down",
    "answer": "the lowest room 14:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the women mentioned by name that came and told the eleven what they encountered at the sepulchre",
    "answer": "Mary Magdalene, Joanna, Mary the mother of James 24:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by whom are none of the sparrows forgotten",
    "answer": "God 12:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "they enclosed a great multitude of fishes and this happened to the net",
    "answer": "it brake 5:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If a son shall ask a bread of you that is a father, will ye give him a --, or if he ask for a fish,will ye for a fish give him a --, or if he shall ask an egg, will he offer him a --",
    "answer": "stone, serpent, scorpion 11:11-12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How does the scripture describe Mary's physical condition in Luke 2:5",
    "answer": "great with child"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did John come preaching",
    "answer": "all the country about Jordan 3:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The devil promise to give Jesus all the power and glory of the kingdom, if Jesus did this",
    "answer": "worship him 4:5-7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was the lineage of Elisabeth",
    "answer": "daughters of Aaron 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did the Scribes and Pharisees watch Jesus whether He would heal on the Sabbath day.",
    "answer": "that they might find an accusation against Him 6:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "spoken by the centurion, but say in a -- and my servant shall be healed",
    "answer": "word 7:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who went out to sow his seed",
    "answer": "a sower 8:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "some said of Jesus that He was John risen from the dead, others said of Him",
    "answer": "Elias had appeared, one of the old prophets was risen again 9:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and in the same house remain -- and -- such things as they give",
    "answer": "eating, drinking 10:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the words of the women seem to the apostles",
    "answer": "idle tales 24:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what did Herod question with Jesus",
    "answer": "many words 23:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Once they followed the man into the house, who were the disciples to address in the house",
    "answer": "the goodman of the house 22:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "besides great earthquakes in divers places what else did Jesus speak of",
    "answer": "famines, pestilences, fearful sights, great signs from heaven 21:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Having let forth the vineyard where did the man go and for how long",
    "answer": "into a far country, for a long time 20:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say, came to Zacchaeus' house",
    "answer": "salvation 19:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Pharisee stood and prayed thus, Lord I thank thee, that I am as not other men are --, unjust, -- or even as this publican",
    "answer": "extortioners, adulterers 18:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And will not rather say unto him, make ready wherewith I may --, and gird thy self and -- me, till I have eaten, and -- and then afterward thou shall -- and drink.",
    "answer": "sup, serve, drunken, eat 17:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I say unto you make to yourselves -- of the mammon of unrighteousness, that when they -- they may receive you into everlasting --",
    "answer": "friends, fail, habitation 16:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "besides her neighbors who does the woman call to rejoice with her when she finds the piece of silver",
    "answer": "her friends 15:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If you sit in the lowest room, what may he that bade to the feast say to thee",
    "answer": "friend go up higher 14:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of our head did Jesus say is all numbered",
    "answer": "the very hairs 12:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Asking the fig tree be given another year, what did the dresser of the vineyard propose to do to it",
    "answer": "dig about it and dung it 13:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did they beckon to, to come and help them with the fishes",
    "answer": "their partners 5:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If ye then being evil know how to give good gifts unto your children, how much more shall your heavenly Father give the -- to them that ask",
    "answer": "Holy Spirit 11:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to be taxed with Mary his -- wife",
    "answer": "espoused 2:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did John preach",
    "answer": "the baptism of repentance for the remission of sins 3:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Jesus' response to the devil's second temptation",
    "answer": "get thee behind satan, for it is written thou shalt worship the Lord thy God and Him only shalt thou serve 4:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they were both -- before God walking in all the -- and ordinances of the Lord --",
    "answer": "righteous, commandments, blameless 1:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But Jesus knew their --",
    "answer": "thoughts 6:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For I also am a man set under -- having under me soldiers, I say unto one go and he -- and to another -- and he cometh and to my -- do this and he doeth it.",
    "answer": "authority, goeth, come, servant 7:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "First location some seed fell",
    "answer": "by the way side 8:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Herod said, John have I --, but who is this, of whom I hear such things, and he -- to see Him",
    "answer": "beheaded, desired 9:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is worthy of his hire",
    "answer": "the laborer 10:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and if it bear fruit, -- and if not then after that thou shalt cut it down",
    "answer": "well 13:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what word describes how the chief priest and scribes accused Jesus",
    "answer": "vehemently 23:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the disciples to say to the good man of the house",
    "answer": "the Master saith unto thee where is the guest chamber where I shall eat the Passover with my disciples 22:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "they shall lay their hand on you and -- you delivering you up to synagogues and into -- being brought before kings and -- for my name's sake",
    "answer": "persecute, prisons, rulers 21:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when did the man send a servant to the husbandmen",
    "answer": "at the season 20:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's son did Jesus say Zacchaeus was",
    "answer": "Abraham 19:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How often during the week did the pharisee state he fasted",
    "answer": "twice 18:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "*Doth he thank the servant, because he did the things that were commanded him? I -- not",
    "answer": "trow 17:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He that is faithful in that which is -- is faithful also in --",
    "answer": "least, much 16:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In whose presence is there joy when one sinner repents",
    "answer": "angels of God 15:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "then thou shall have worship in the -- of them that sit at meat with thee",
    "answer": "presence 14:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who arose and ran to the sepulchre",
    "answer": "Peter 24:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "ye are of more -- than many sparrows",
    "answer": "value 12:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "they filled both the ships so that they began to --",
    "answer": "sink 5:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when Jesus cast out the dumb devil",
    "answer": "the dumb spake11:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "While Joseph and Mary were in Bethlehem what days were accomplished",
    "answer": "that she should be delivered 2:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The voice of one crying in the wilderness, prepare ye the way of the Lord, make His paths straight, is a quote from the words of this prophet",
    "answer": "Esaias 3:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The devil brought Jesus to Jerusalem and set Him on this",
    "answer": "on a pinnacle of the temple 4:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did Zacharias and his wife have no child",
    "answer": "because Elisabeth was barren and they were now well stricken in years 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus first command the man with the withered hand to do",
    "answer": "rise up and stand forth in the midst 6:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Jesus' reaction to centurion after hearing his message from his friends",
    "answer": "He marvelled at him 7:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "besides being trodden down what else happened to the seed that fell by the wayside",
    "answer": "the fowls of air devoured it 8:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus privately took His disciples aside to a desert place belonging to this city",
    "answer": "Bethsaida 9:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "go not from -- to --",
    "answer": "house, house 10:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Stooping down, Peter beheld this when he came to the sepulchre",
    "answer": "the linen clothes laid by themselves 24:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Herod along with his men do to Jesus",
    "answer": "set Him at nought, mocked Him, arrayed Him in gorgeous robe and sent Him again to Pilate 23:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he will show you a -- upper room, -- ,there make ready",
    "answer": "large, furnished 22:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and it shall turn to you for a --",
    "answer": "testimony 21:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when did the man send a servant to the husbandmen",
    "answer": "at the season 20:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For the Son of man is come to -- and to -- that which was lost",
    "answer": "seek, save 19:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Of what did the pharisee praying say he gave tithes",
    "answer": "of all that he possess 18:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "So likewise ye, when ye shall have done, all those things which are commanded you, say we are -- servants, we have done that which was our -- to do.",
    "answer": "unprofitable, duty 17:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV and he that is unjust in the least ..",
    "answer": "is unjust also in much 16:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which son said this to his father, \"give me the portion of goods that falleth to me\"",
    "answer": "the younger 15:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For whosoever exalteth himself shall be --",
    "answer": "abased 14:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said he that does this the Son of man shall also confess before the angels",
    "answer": "confess Him before men 12:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As He was teaching in the synagogue Jesus met a woman that had this for eighteen years",
    "answer": "a spirit of infirmity 13:10-11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "seeing the miracle of the fishes what did Simon fall down Jesus' knees and say",
    "answer": "depart from me, for I am a sinful man o Lord 5:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by which chief did some accuse Jesus of casting out devils",
    "answer": "Beelzebub chief of the devil 11:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what did Mary wrap her firstborn son",
    "answer": "swaddling clothes 2:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Every -- shall be filled",
    "answer": "valley 3:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while on the pinnacle of the temple what did the devil tempt Jesus to do",
    "answer": "cast Himself down from it 4:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Zacharias' lot to do when he went into the temple of the Lord",
    "answer": "burn incense 1:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I will ask you one thing, is it -- on the Sabbath days to do good or to do -- to save life or to --it",
    "answer": "lawful, evil, destroy 6:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Regarding the centurion what did Jesus say to the people that followed him",
    "answer": "I say unto you, I have not found so great faith, no not in Israel 7:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the second location some seeds fell",
    "answer": "upon a rock 8:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The people followed Jesus into the desert place, and He received them and spake unto them of the kingdom of God, who did He heal among them",
    "answer": "them that had need of healing 9:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "of what is the laborer worthy",
    "answer": "his hire 10:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How far is Emmaus from Jerusalem?",
    "answer": "threescore furlongs 24:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the same day Herod and Pilate were made -- together for before they were at -- between them selves",
    "answer": "friends, enmity 23:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "With -- I have -- to eat this Passover with you before I suffer",
    "answer": "desire, desired 22:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where should it be settled not to meditate before what ye will answer",
    "answer": "in your heart 21:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For what purpose did a man send a servant to the husbandmen at the season",
    "answer": "that they should give him of the fruit of the vineyard 20:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "two reasons were given why Jesus added and spoke a parable one was He was nigh to Jerusalem the other was they thought that this should immediately appear",
    "answer": "the kingdom of God 19:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the publican standing a far off would not even lift this up unto heaven",
    "answer": "his eyes 18:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As Jesus went to Jerusalem it is said He passed through the midst of two places name them",
    "answer": "Samaria, Galilee 17:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If therefore ye have not been faithful in the unrighteous mammon who will commit to your trust the true --",
    "answer": "riches 16:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Not many days after receiving his portion the younger son gathered all together, to where did he journey",
    "answer": "into a far country 15:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he that humbleth himself shall be --",
    "answer": "exalted 14:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He that denieth me before men shall be denied before the -- of God.",
    "answer": "angels 12:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the woman with the spirit of infirmity was bowed together what could she in no wise do",
    "answer": "lift up herself 13:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the reaction of Simon and all that were with him at the draught of fishes which they had taken",
    "answer": "astonished 5:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "others tempting Him sought from Him a sign from --",
    "answer": "heaven 11:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because there was no room for them in the inn, the child was laid in this",
    "answer": "a manger 2:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and every mountain shall be brought --",
    "answer": "low 3:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For it is written He shall give His angels -- over thee to keep thee",
    "answer": "charge 4:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "At what time was the whole multitude praying without",
    "answer": "at the time of incense 1:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say to the man with the withered hand to heal him",
    "answer": "stretch forth thy hand 6:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "They that were sent, returning to the house what condition did they find the servant who had been sick",
    "answer": "whole 7:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to the seed that fell on the rock as soon as it was sprung up",
    "answer": "it withered away 8:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when this began to happen the twelve told Jesus to send the multitude away",
    "answer": "the day began to wear away 9:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and into what city ye enter and they receive you -- such things that are set before you",
    "answer": "eat 10:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what place is Emmaus",
    "answer": "a village 24:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Pilate purpose to do after He chastised Jesus",
    "answer": "release Him 23:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and He took the cup and gave --",
    "answer": "thanks 22:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For I will give you a mouth and wisdom which all your adversaries shall not be able to -- nor --",
    "answer": "gainsay, resist 21:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the husbandmen do to the second servant",
    "answer": "beat him also, entreated him shamefully, and sent him away empty 20:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for what purpose did a certain noble man go into a far country",
    "answer": "to receive for himself a kingdom and return 19:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The publican smote upon his breast saying --",
    "answer": "God be merciful to me a sinner 18:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jesus meet the ten lepers",
    "answer": "in a certain village 17:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And if you have not been -- in that which is another man's who will give you that which is your own",
    "answer": "faithful 16:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what did the younger son waste his substance",
    "answer": "with riotous living 15:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus told him that bade Him to the feast not to call these groups when he makes a dinner or a supper",
    "answer": "friends, brethren, kinsmen, rich neighbors, 14:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whosoever shall speak a word against the Son of man it shall be -- him",
    "answer": "forgiven 12:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus called the woman to Him, what did He say to heal her",
    "answer": "woman thou art loosed from thine infirmity 13:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who were Simon's fishing partners",
    "answer": "James and John 5:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But He knowing their -- said every kingdom divided against itself is brought to -- and a house divided against a house --",
    "answer": "thoughts, desolation, falleth 11:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the same country where were the shepherds abiding",
    "answer": "in the field 2:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the -- shall be made straight",
    "answer": "crooked 3:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And in their -- they shall bear thee up lest at anytime thou -- thy foot against a --",
    "answer": "hands, dash, stone 4:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where was the angel of the Lord standing that appeared to Zacharias",
    "answer": "on the right side of the altar of incense 1:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when the man stretched forth his hand",
    "answer": "his hand was restored whole as the other 6:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The day after healing the centurion's servant name the city Jesus came to",
    "answer": "Nain 7:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did the seed that fell on the rock wither away as soon as it was sprung up",
    "answer": "because it lacked moisture 8:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the twelve ask Jesus to send the multitude",
    "answer": "into the towns and country round about 9:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the seventy were instructed to tell the city that receives them this is come nigh unto you",
    "answer": "the kingdom of God 10:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus laid His hands on the woman, what happened immediately",
    "answer": "she was made straight 13:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But their eyes were -- that they should know Him",
    "answer": "holden 24:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For of -- he must release one of them at the feast",
    "answer": "necessity 23:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say He will not drink of until the kingdom of God shall come",
    "answer": "the fruit of the vine 22:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by whom did Jesus say ye shall be betrayed",
    "answer": "parents, brethren, kinsfolks, friends 21:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the husbandmen do to the third servant",
    "answer": "wounded him and cast him out 20:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many servants did the nobleman have",
    "answer": "ten 19:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the ten lepers -- a far off",
    "answer": "stood 17:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "No servant can serve two -- for either he will hate the one and -- the other or he will hold to the one and -- the other",
    "answer": "masters, love, despise 16:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the younger son had spent all, what arose in the land so that he began to be in want",
    "answer": "a mighty famine 15:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "lest they also bid thee again and a -- be made thee",
    "answer": "recompense 14:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in Jesus' parable who went down to his house more justified",
    "answer": "the publican 18:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "This act against the Holy Ghost shall not be forgiven",
    "answer": "blasphemy 12:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "At the healing of the man with the withered hand it is said they were filled with this and communed with one another what they might do to Jesus",
    "answer": "madness 6:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus asked if this person is divided against himself how shall his kingdom stand",
    "answer": "satan 11:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the rough -- shall be made smooth",
    "answer": "way 3:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Jesus' response to the devil's third temptation",
    "answer": "it is said, thou shalt not tempt the Lord thy God 4:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the father of James and John",
    "answer": "Zebedee 5:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what time were the shepherds keeping watch over their flock",
    "answer": "at night 2:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who went with Jesus to the city of Nain",
    "answer": "many of His disciples and much people 7:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Zacharias' reaction when he saw the angel of the Lord",
    "answer": "he was troubled and fear fell upon him 1:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Third place seed fell",
    "answer": "among thorns 8:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did the twelve ask Jesus to send the multitude to the towns and country round about",
    "answer": "to lodge and get victuals for they were in a desert place 9:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To the city that does not receive them where in the city were they to go and proclaim \"even the dust of your city, which cleaveth on us, we do wipe off against you, notwithstanding be sure of this, that the kingdom of God is come nigh unto you\"",
    "answer": "in the streets 10:10-11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the woman glorify",
    "answer": "God 13:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Away with this man and release unto us --",
    "answer": "Barabbas 23:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus do with the bread",
    "answer": "took it, gave thanks, brake it and gave it unto them 22:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And ye shall be -- of all men for my name's sake",
    "answer": "hated 21:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "because it was his beloved son what did the man say the husbandmen would do when they see him",
    "answer": "reverence him 20:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the nobleman deliver to his servants",
    "answer": "ten pounds 19:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For everyone that exalt himself shall be --and he that humbleth himself shall be --",
    "answer": "abased, exalted 18:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who cried saying \"Jesus, Master have mercy on us\"",
    "answer": "the ten lepers 17:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ye cannot serve -- and --",
    "answer": "God, mammon 16:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the younger son join himself to",
    "answer": "a citizen of that country 15:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus say to call when you make a feast",
    "answer": "poor, maimed, lame, blind 14:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker 'art thou only a stranger in Jerusalem and has not known the things which are come to pass in these days\"",
    "answer": "Cleopas 24:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said, when you are brought to these take no thought how or what thing ye shall answer, for the Holy Ghost will teach you in that hour what ye ought to say.",
    "answer": "synagogues, magistrates and powers 12:11-12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"fear not from henceforth thou shall catch men\"",
    "answer": "Jesus to Simon 5:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And if I by Beelzebub cast out devils, by whom do your -- cast them out? therefore shall they be your --",
    "answer": "sons, judges 11:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As the angel of the Lord came upon the shepherds, what shone round about them",
    "answer": "the glory of the Lord 2:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And all -- shall see the salvation of God",
    "answer": "flesh 3:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The bible records when the devil had ended all the temptation he departed from Jesus for this space of time",
    "answer": "a season 4:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the angel's first two words to Zacharias",
    "answer": "fear not 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jesus go to pray and continued all night in prayer to God",
    "answer": "a mountain 6:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus came to the gate of the city of Nain what did he behold",
    "answer": "a dead man carried out 7:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to the seed that fell among thorns",
    "answer": "thorns sprang with it and choked it 8:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"give ye them to eat\"",
    "answer": "Jesus to the twelve 9:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But I say unto you it shall be -- in that day for Sodom than for that city.",
    "answer": "tolerable 10:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The men on the road to Emmaus, described Jesus as a prophet who was mighty in two things name them",
    "answer": "deed and word before God and all the people 24:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why was Barabbas cast into prison",
    "answer": "for a certain sedition made in the city and for murder 23:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say the bread was",
    "answer": "His body 22:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But there shall not a hair of your head --",
    "answer": "perish 21:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "This is the -- come let us kill him",
    "answer": "heir 20:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what charge did the nobleman give his servants",
    "answer": "occupy till I come 19:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Infants were brought to Jesus that He might touch them, but what did the disciples do when they saw this",
    "answer": "they rebuked them 18:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus command the ten lepers to go show themselves to",
    "answer": "the priest 17:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which covetous group when they heard all these things derided Jesus",
    "answer": "the Pharisees 16:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the citizen of the country send the young son and for what purpose",
    "answer": "into his fields, to feed swine 15:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for they cannot recompense thee, for thou shalt be recompensed at the resurrection of the --",
    "answer": "just 14:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Master speak to my brother that he divide the -- with me",
    "answer": "inheritance 12:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After the healing of the woman with the spirit of infirmity how did the ruler of the synagogue answer because Jesus healed on the Sabbath day",
    "answer": "with indignation 13:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and when they had brought their ships to land they -- all followed Him",
    "answer": "forsook 5:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But if I with the -- of God cast out devils no doubt the kingdom of God is come to you",
    "answer": "finger 11:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the shepherds feel when the angel of the Lord came upon them",
    "answer": "sore afraid 2:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who to whom \" O generation of vipers who hath warned you to flee from the wrath to come\"",
    "answer": "John to the multitude that came forth to be baptized of him 3:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus returned in the power of the ",
    "answer": ""
  },
  {
    "stem": "Spirit into this place",
    "answer": "Galilee 4:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The angel told Zacharias this was heard",
    "answer": "his prayer 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When it was day who did Jesus call unto Him",
    "answer": "His disciples 6:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The dead man being carried out was the -- son of his mother",
    "answer": "only 7:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Last place seed fell",
    "answer": "on good ground 8:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus said, give ye them to eat, what food were the disciples in possession of",
    "answer": "five loaves and two fishes 9:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "woe unto thee -- woe unto thee --, for if the mighty works had been done in -- and -- which have been done in you, they had a great while ago -- sitting in -- and ashes.",
    "answer": "Chorazin, Bethsaida, Tyre, Sidon, repented, sackcloth 10:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker, \"there are six days in which men ought to work, in them therefore come and be healed and not on the Sabbath day\"",
    "answer": "the ruler of the synagogue 13:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"why, what evil hath He done\"",
    "answer": "Pilate 23:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "This cup is the new -- in my blood which is shed for you",
    "answer": "testament 22:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In your patience -- ye your souls",
    "answer": "possess 21:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The husband men reasoned they will kill the son and this would be theirs",
    "answer": "the inheritance 20:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who hated the nobleman",
    "answer": "his citizens 19:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- little children to come unto me and -- them not for of such is the kingdom of God",
    "answer": "suffer, forbid 18:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened as the lepers went to show themselves to the priest",
    "answer": "they were cleansed 17:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ye are they which justify yourselves before --",
    "answer": "men 16:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he would -- have filled his belly with the -- that the swine did eat, and no man -- unto him",
    "answer": "fain,husks, gave 15:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Jesus' parable what did a certain man make",
    "answer": "a great supper 14:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the men say condemned and delivered Jesus to death",
    "answer": "the chief priest and their rulers 24:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "man who made me a judge or -- over you",
    "answer": "divider 12:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of illness did the person that uttered these words have, Lord if thou wilt thou can make me clean",
    "answer": "leprosy 5:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what results when a strong man armed keepeth his palace",
    "answer": "his goods are in peace 11:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the first two words the angel said unto the shepherds",
    "answer": "fear not 2:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What kind of fruits did John tell the multitude to bring forth",
    "answer": "fruits worthy of repentance 3:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What of Jesus went out through all the region of Galilee",
    "answer": "fame of Him 4:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What kind of child did the angle tell Zacharias his wife was going to bear him",
    "answer": "a son 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many of the disciples did Jesus choose",
    "answer": "twelve 6:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the marital status of the mother of the dead man",
    "answer": "widow 7:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to the seed that fell on good ground",
    "answer": "sprang up and bare fruit an hundredfold 8:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus commanded the disciples to have the people sit down in companies of this amount",
    "answer": "fifties 9:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus told Chorazin and Bethsaida it will be more tolerable for Tyre and Sidon at this than for them",
    "answer": "the judgment 10:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But we trusted that it had been He which should have -- Israel",
    "answer": "redeemed 24:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they were instant with -- voices, requiring that He might be -- and the voices of them and the chief priest --",
    "answer": "loud, crucified, prevailed 23:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But behold the -- of him that betrayeth me is with me on the table.",
    "answer": "hand 22:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is nigh when Jerusalem is seen compassed with armies",
    "answer": "the desolation thereof 21:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the husbandmen do the son",
    "answer": "cast him out of the vineyard and killed him 20:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what message did the citizens send to the nobleman",
    "answer": "we will not have this man to reign over us 19:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said, whosoever shall not receive the kingdom of God as this person, shall in no wise enter therein",
    "answer": "little child 18:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did one of the leper do when he saw he was cleansed",
    "answer": "turned back and with a loud voice glorified God 17:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the sight of God that which is highly esteemed among men is",
    "answer": "an abomination 16:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And when he came to himself, he said how many -- servants of my father's have -- enough and to spare and I perish with --",
    "answer": "hired, bread, hunger 15:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the certain man send at supper time to call those bidden",
    "answer": "his servant 14:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what thing did Jesus say to take heed and beware of",
    "answer": "covetousness 12:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said on the Sabbath day these animals are loosed from the stall",
    "answer": "ox, ass 13:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say to the man with leprosy as He touched him",
    "answer": "I will, be thou clean 5:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what results when a stronger man overcomes a strong man",
    "answer": "he take from him all his armor wherein he trusted and divideth his spoils 11:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold I bring you good tidings of great -- which shall be to all people",
    "answer": "joy 2:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did John tell the multitude not to say within themselves",
    "answer": "we have Abraham to our father 3:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus do in the synagogues",
    "answer": "taught 4:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The angel instructed Zacharias to call the child by this name",
    "answer": "John 1:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus name the twelve disciples",
    "answer": "apostles 6:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how much of the city was with the widow woman as her dead son was carried out",
    "answer": "much 7:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV he that hath ears to hear...",
    "answer": "let him hear 8:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then Jesus took the five loaves and two fishes and looking up to -- He -- them and -- them and -- to His disciples to set before the --",
    "answer": "heaven, blessed, brake, gave, multitude 9:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "spoken by Jesus though this city is exalted to heaven, it shall be thrust down to hell",
    "answer": "Capernaum 10:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "today is the -- day since these things were done",
    "answer": "third 24:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Pilate gave -- that it should be as they required",
    "answer": "sentence 23:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus proclaims woe, to the one that does this to the Son of man",
    "answer": "betrays Him 22:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Those in Judaea are warned to flee where",
    "answer": "to the mountains 21:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will the lord of the vineyard do the husbandmen",
    "answer": "destroy them and give the vineyard to others 20:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when he returned the nobleman called his servants that he might know how much every man had gained by this means",
    "answer": "trading 19:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker :good Master what shall I do to inherit eternal life",
    "answer": "a certain ruler 18:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "of what nation was the leper that turned back to thank Jesus",
    "answer": "samaritan 17:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The law and the prophets were until --",
    "answer": "John 16:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Father I have sinned against -- and before thee",
    "answer": "heaven 15:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "At super time what did the man send his servant to say to them that were bidden",
    "answer": "come for all things are now ready 14:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said a man's life does not consist of this",
    "answer": "the abundance of things which he possess 12:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said on the Sabbath day the animals are led away to this",
    "answer": "watering 13:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how soon did the leprosy depart from the man",
    "answer": "immediately 5:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "he that is not with me is -- me",
    "answer": "against 11:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, for unto is born this day in the city of David a Saviour ..",
    "answer": "which is Christ the Lord 2:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John told the multitude God is able to use these to raise up children unto Abraham",
    "answer": "stones 3:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was Jesus brought up",
    "answer": "in Nazareth 4:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And thou shall have joy and gladness and many shall -- at his birth",
    "answer": "rejoice 1:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which disciple did Jesus name Peter",
    "answer": "Simon 6:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus have on the widow woman and what did He say to her",
    "answer": "compassion, weep not 7:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who asked Jesus the meaning of the parable of the sower",
    "answer": "His disciples 8:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many men were fed with the five loaves and two fishes",
    "answer": "about five thousand 9:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "he that heareth you -- me, and he that despiseth you -- me, and he that despiseth me, despiseth Him that -- me.",
    "answer": "heareth, despiseth, sent 10:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Yea and certain women also of our company made us -- which were early at the sepulchre",
    "answer": "astonished 24:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he -- unto them him that for sedition and murder was cast into prison whom they desired but he delivered Jesus to their --",
    "answer": "released, will 23:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and there was a -- among them which of them should be accounted the --",
    "answer": "strife, greatest 22:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For these be the days of -- that all things which are written may be fulfilled",
    "answer": "vengeance 21:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and when they heard it they said -- forbid",
    "answer": "God 20:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much did the first servant gain with the pound he was given",
    "answer": "ten pounds 19:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said none is good, save one, that is --",
    "answer": "God 18:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to thank Jesus, the leper fell down on his face at His --",
    "answer": "feet 17:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "it is easier for heaven and earth to pass than for one -- of the law to fail",
    "answer": "tittle 16:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "feeling no more worthy as a son what did the young man desire his father to make him as",
    "answer": "one of the hired servants 15:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they all with one consent began to make --",
    "answer": "excuse 14:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the parable, how did the ground of the certain rich man bring forth",
    "answer": "plentifully 12:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "An ought not this woman being a daughter of -- whom satan had -- lo these eighteen years be loosed from this bond on the Sabbath day.",
    "answer": "Abraham, bound 13:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "after He cleansed him what instructions did Jesus give to the man that had the leprosy",
    "answer": "tell no man, go show thyself to the priest, offer for thy cleansing according as Moses commanded for a testimony unto them 5:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "he that gathereth not with me --",
    "answer": "scattereth 11:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The angel told the shepherds the sign unto them is that they will find the babe in this state",
    "answer": "wrapped in swaddling clothes and lying in a manger 2:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where is the axe laid",
    "answer": "unto the root of the trees 3:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As was His custom Jesus did this on the Sabbath day",
    "answer": "went into the synagogue 4:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to the angel in whose sight will the child be great",
    "answer": "in the sight of the Lord 1:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was Simon's brother",
    "answer": "Andrew 6:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "after Jesus came and touched this they that bare the dead man stood still",
    "answer": "bier 7:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Unto you is given to know the -- of the kingdom of God, but to others in -- that seeing they might not -- and hearing they might not --",
    "answer": "mysteries, parables, see, understand 8:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "after the people had eaten twelve baskets of these were taken up",
    "answer": "fragments 9:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what emotion did the seventy return",
    "answer": "with joy 10:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And when He had said these things, all His -- were ashamed, and all the people -- for all the glorious things that were done by Him.",
    "answer": "adversaries, rejoiced 13:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "upon whom did they lay the cross of Jesus and what was his nationality",
    "answer": "Simon a Cyrenian 23:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what do the kings of the gentiles exercise over them",
    "answer": "lordship 22:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but -- unto them that are with child, and them that give suck in those days",
    "answer": "woe 21:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what has become the head of the corner",
    "answer": "the stone which the builders rejected 20:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Over how many cities did the nobleman give his first servant authority",
    "answer": "ten 19:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what commandments did Jesus rehearse to the ruler",
    "answer": "do no commit adultery, do not kill, do not steal, do not bear false witness, honor thy father and thy mother 18:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "were there not -- cleansed, but where are the --",
    "answer": "ten, nine 17:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Whosoever does this to his wife and marries another commits adultery",
    "answer": "puts her away 16:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was the son when the father saw him",
    "answer": "a far off 15:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what excuse did the first make for not coming",
    "answer": "he bought a piece of ground and needs go see it 14:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "O fools and slow of -- to believe all that the prophets have spoken",
    "answer": "heart 24:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to store his fruits and goods what did the rich man decide to do",
    "answer": "pull down his barns and build greater 12:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus withdrew Himself into the wilderness for this purpose",
    "answer": "to pray 5:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when an unclean spirit is gone out of man what does he walk through dry places seeking, and finds none",
    "answer": "rest 11:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Suddenly who was with the angel that appeared to the shepherds",
    "answer": "a multitude of the heavenly host 2:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happens to every tree that which bringeth not forth good fruit",
    "answer": "hewn down and cast into the fire 3:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus went into the synagogue and stood up to do this",
    "answer": "read 4:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was the child not to drink",
    "answer": "wine nor strong drink 1:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Philip was the fifth disciple listed who was the sixth",
    "answer": "Bartholomew 6:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say to the dead man",
    "answer": "young man I say unto thee arise 7:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the parable what is the seed",
    "answer": "the word of God 8:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what response was given when Jesus asked His disciples \"who say the people that I am\"",
    "answer": "John the Baptist, Elias, old prophet is risen again 9:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "through what did the seventy tell Jesus the devils were subject to them",
    "answer": "through His name 10:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ought not Christ to have suffered these things and to enter into His --",
    "answer": "glory 24:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from where was Simon the Cyrenian coming",
    "answer": "out of the country 23:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what are they that exercise authority upon the gentiles called",
    "answer": "benefactors 22:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for there shall be great distress in the -- and wrath upon this people",
    "answer": "land 21:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whosoever shall fall upon that stone shall be -- but on whomsoever it shall fall it will -- him to --",
    "answer": "broken, grind, powder 20:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much did the second servant gain with the pound he was was given",
    "answer": "five pounds 19:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From what time did the ruler state he has kept all the commandments",
    "answer": "from his youth 18:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "There are not found that returned to give glory to God, save this --",
    "answer": "stranger 17:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the rich man clothed in",
    "answer": "purple and fine linen 16:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "having compassion how did the father greet his son",
    "answer": "ran and fell on his neck and kissed him 15:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Which of them bidden ended with the phrase, \"I pray thee have me excused\"",
    "answer": "first and second 14:18-19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "soul thou has much goods, laid up for many years, take thine --, --, -- and be --.",
    "answer": "ease, eat, drink, merry 12:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Unto what is the kingdom of God like, and where unto shall I -- it",
    "answer": "resemble 13:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As Jesus sat by teaching they were Pharisees and doctors of this sitting",
    "answer": "the law 5:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what does the unclean spirit say when it cannot find rest",
    "answer": "I will return unto my house whence I came out 11:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The multitude of heavenly host praised God and said",
    "answer": "Glory to God in the highest and on earth peace, good will toward men 2:13-14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did John tell the people to do if they have two coats",
    "answer": "impart to him that hath none 3:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The book of this prophet was delivered to Jesus",
    "answer": "Esaias 4:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From what time would the child be filled with the Holy Ghost",
    "answer": "from his mother's womb 1:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which disciple was the son of Alphaeus",
    "answer": "James 6:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He that was dead sat up and began to do this",
    "answer": "speak 7:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which location in the parable is represented by these, they that hear then cometh the devil and take away the word out of their hearts lest they should believe and be saved",
    "answer": "those by the wayside 8:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Jesus asked, but whom say ye that I am, Peter answering said",
    "answer": "the Christ of God 9:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I beheld satan as -- fall from heaven",
    "answer": "lightning 10:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "beginning at this person and all the prophets Jesus expounded unto them in all the scriptures the things concerning Himself",
    "answer": "Moses 24:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And there followed Him a great company of people and of women which also -- and -- Him.",
    "answer": "bewailed, lamented 23:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but he that is greatest among you let him be as the -- and he that is chief as he that doth --",
    "answer": "younger, serve 22:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by the edge of what shall they fall",
    "answer": "edge of the sword 21:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the chief -- and the scribes the same -- sought to lay -- on Him, and they feared the -- for they perceived He had spoken this -- against them",
    "answer": "priests, hour, hands, people, parable 20:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many cities was the second servant given charge of",
    "answer": "five 19:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell the ruler he lacked",
    "answer": "one thing 18:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who demanded of Jesus when the kingdom of God should come",
    "answer": "the pharisees 17:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the rich man fared -- everyday",
    "answer": "sumptuously 16:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the father command his servant to put on his son",
    "answer": "the best robe, ring on his finger, shoes on his feet 15:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and another said I bought five yoke of oxen and I go to -- them",
    "answer": "prove 14:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But God said unto him, thou fool, this night shall thy -- be required of thee, then whose shall those things be which thou has --",
    "answer": "soul, provided 12:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To what did Jesus compare a grain of mustard seed",
    "answer": "the Kingdom of God 13:18-19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From what areas did the Pharisees and doctors of the law come",
    "answer": "every town of Galilee, Judaea and Jerusalem 5:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what state does the unclean spirit find the house",
    "answer": "swept and garnished 11:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker(s) \"let us now go even unto Bethlehem and see this thing, which is come to pass, which the Lord hath made known to us \"",
    "answer": "the shepherds 2:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he that hath meat let him do --",
    "answer": "likewise 3:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The -- of the Lord is upon me",
    "answer": "Spirit 4:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And many of the -- of Israel will he turn to the Lord God",
    "answer": "children 1:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "One Simon was called Peter, what was the other Simon called",
    "answer": "Zelotes 6:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus deliver the man that was dead to",
    "answer": "his mother 7:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How do those that represent the seed that fell on the rock, receive the word",
    "answer": "with joy 8:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and He straitly charged them and -- them to tell no man that thing",
    "answer": "commanded 9:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold I give you power to tread on -- and scorpions, and over all the -- of the enemy and nothing shall by any means -- you.",
    "answer": "serpents, power, hurt 10:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when they came nigh the village, Jesus made as if He would done this",
    "answer": "gone further 24:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for whom did Jesus tell the women to weep",
    "answer": "for themselves and their children 23:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For whether is greater he that -- at meat or he that --",
    "answer": "sitteth, serveth 22:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where shall they be led away captives",
    "answer": "into all nations 21:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they watched Him and sent forth -- which would feign themselves -- men, that they might take hold of His --, that so they might deliver Him unto the power and -- of the governor",
    "answer": "spies, just, words, authority 20:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the servant keep the pound laid up",
    "answer": "in a napkin 19:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell the ruler to do with all he had",
    "answer": "sell it and distribute it to the poor 18:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say cometh not with observation",
    "answer": "the kingdom of God 17:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of the beggar that laid at the rich man's gate",
    "answer": "Lazarus 16:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and bring hither the -- and kill it and let us eat and be merry",
    "answer": "fatted calf 15:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what excuse did the last make",
    "answer": "he married a wife and cannot come 14:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "So is he that lay up -- for himself, and is not -- toward God",
    "answer": "treasure, rich 12:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the man cast the grain of mustard seed",
    "answer": "into his garden 13:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the power of the Lord was present to -- them",
    "answer": "heal 5:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who else does the unclean spirit take with him to enter and dwell in the house",
    "answer": "seven other spirits more wicked than himself 11:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what manner did the shepherds come to the babe",
    "answer": "in haste 2:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what question did the publicans that came to be baptized of John ask",
    "answer": "master what shall we do 3:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in the passage of scripture Jesus read from whom was He anointed to preach the gospel to",
    "answer": "the poor 4:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he shall go forth before Him in the -- and power of Elias to turn the hearts of the -- to the children and the disobedient to the wisdom of the -- to make -- a people prepared for the Lord",
    "answer": "spirit, fathers, just, ready 1:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the disciple Judas (not Iscariot ) the brother of",
    "answer": "James 6:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And there came -- on all, and they -- God saying, that a great -- is risen up among us and that God hath -- His people",
    "answer": "fear, glorified, prophet, visited 7:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Those represented by the seed that fell on the rock, have no root, for a time believe but what happens in the time temptation",
    "answer": "they fall away 8:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus declares the Son of man must suffer many things and be rejected of these groups and be slain",
    "answer": "elders, chief priests and scribes 9:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus told the seventy not to rejoice in that the spirits are subject to them but rather rejoice because",
    "answer": "their names are written in heaven 10:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But they -- Him saying abide with us, for it is toward evening and day is far spent",
    "answer": "constrained 24:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus tell the women not to weep for",
    "answer": "Himself 23:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "is not he that sitteth at meat, but I am among you as He that --",
    "answer": "serveth 22:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "of whom shall Jerusalem be trodden down",
    "answer": "the Gentiles 21:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when they asked Jesus is it lawful to give tribute to Caesar or no? what did Jesus perceive",
    "answer": "their craftiness 20:22-23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For I feared thee, because thou art an -- man, thou takest up that thou layest not down and reapest that thou didst not sow",
    "answer": "austere 19:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jesus tell the ruler he will have treasure",
    "answer": "in heaven 18:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Neither shall they say lo -- or lo -- for behold the kingdom of God is -- you",
    "answer": "here, there, within 17:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Lazarus full of",
    "answer": "sores 16:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For this my son was dead and is -- again, he was lost and is --, and they began to be --",
    "answer": "alive, found, merry 15:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the master of the house feel when he heard the excuses of those bidden to the supper",
    "answer": "angry 14:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "take no thought for your life what ye shall -- neither for the -- what ye shall put on",
    "answer": "eat, body 12:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where in the mustard seed did the fowls of the air lodge",
    "answer": "branches 13:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the sickness of the man that was brought in a bed to be healed by Jesus",
    "answer": "palsy 5:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when all the unclean spirits come and dwell in the man how is his last state compared to his first",
    "answer": "worse 11:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the shepherds do with the saying which was told them concerning the child",
    "answer": "they made it known abroad 2:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who to whom \"exact no more than that which is appointed of you\"",
    "answer": "John to the Publicans 3:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He hath sent me to heal the --",
    "answer": "brokenhearted 4:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Zacharias referred to himself as an old man, how did he refer to his wife",
    "answer": "well stricken in years 1:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and Judas Iscariot which was also the --",
    "answer": "traitor 6:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And this -- of Him went forth throughout all Judaea and throughout all the region round about",
    "answer": "rumor 7:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Those represented by the seed that fell among thorns, hears the word and go forth but what are they choked by",
    "answer": "cares, riches, and pleasures of life 8:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what day would the Son of man be raised",
    "answer": "third 9:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the things hidden from the wise and prudent are revealed to whom",
    "answer": "babes 10:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And it came to pass as He sat at meat with them, He took -- and blessed it and -- it and gave it to them",
    "answer": "bread, brake 24:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Blessed are the barren and -- that never bare and paps which never gave --",
    "answer": "wombs,suck 23:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ye are they which have continued with me in my --",
    "answer": "temptations 22:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "until when shall Jerusalem be trodden down of the Gentiles",
    "answer": "until the times of the gentiles be fulfilled 21:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Perceiving their craftiness, what question did Jesus ask",
    "answer": "why tempt ye me 20:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "out of what did the nobleman tell the servant he will judge him",
    "answer": "out of his own mouth 19:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "besides selling all he had and distributing to the poor what invitation did Jesus set forth to the ruler",
    "answer": "come and follow Him 18:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"the days will come, when ye shall desire to see one of the days of the Son of man, and ye shall not see it\"",
    "answer": "Jesus to His disciples 17:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Lazarus desire to be fed with",
    "answer": "the crumbs which fell from the rich man's table 16:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when his brother came home where was the elder son",
    "answer": "in the field 15:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the master tell the servant to bring in to the supper and from where was he instructed to go and get them the first time",
    "answer": "poor, maimed, halt , blind , streets and lanes of the city 14:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the life more than",
    "answer": "meat 12:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In how many measures of meal did the woman hide the leaven,till the whole was leavened",
    "answer": "three 13:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what prevented the men from bringing the man in the bed to Jesus",
    "answer": "the multitude 5:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Blessed is the -- that bare thee and the -- which thou has sucked.",
    "answer": "womb, paps 11:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was the reaction of all those that heard those things that were told by the shepherds",
    "answer": "they wondered 2:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who likewise demanded of John saying, and what shall we do",
    "answer": "the soldiers 3:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to preach -- to the captives",
    "answer": "deliverance 4:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did the angel Gabriel told Zacharias he stands",
    "answer": "in the presence of God 1:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "name the disciples that shared the same name",
    "answer": "Simon Peter and Simon called Zelotes, James the brother of John and James the son of Alphaeus, Judas the brother of James and Judas Iscariot 6:14-16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the disciples of -- showed him all these things",
    "answer": "John 7:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and bring forth no fruit to --",
    "answer": "perfection 8:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If any man would come after Jesus who would he have to deny",
    "answer": "himself 9:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "besides the Son who knows the Father",
    "answer": "he to whom the Son will reveal Him 10:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And their eyes were opened and they knew Him and He -- out of their sight",
    "answer": "vanished 24:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To what will they say fall on us",
    "answer": "the mountains 23:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell the apostles He appoints unto them",
    "answer": "a kingdom 22:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what heavenly bodies shall there be signs",
    "answer": "sun,moon, stars 21:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when asked about giving tribute, what money was shown to Jesus at His request",
    "answer": "a penny 20:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "wherefore then gavest not thou my money into the --, that at my coming I might have required mine own with --",
    "answer": "bank, usury 19:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the ruler's response when He heard Jesus and why",
    "answer": "he was sorrowful for he was very rich 18:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus command not to do when they say, see here or see there",
    "answer": "go not after them nor follow them 17:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the dogs do to Lazarus' sores",
    "answer": "licked them 16:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the elder son hear when he drew nigh to the house",
    "answer": "music and dancing 15:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with room still in the supper, to where did the lord send the servant to go and compel others to come into his house, so it can be filled",
    "answer": "highways and hedges 14:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the body more than",
    "answer": "raiment 12:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to what was Jesus comparing when He said, it is like leaven, which a woman took and hid in three measures of meal till the whole was leavened",
    "answer": "kingdom of God 13:20-21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the men went to the housetop and let the man down through this",
    "answer": "the tiling 5:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, blessed are they which hear the word of God ...",
    "answer": "and keep it 11:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But -- kept all these things and pondered them in her heart",
    "answer": "Mary 2:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What three things did John tell the soldiers to do",
    "answer": "do violence to no man, neither accuse any falsely, be content with your wages 3:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and recovering of -- to the blind",
    "answer": "sight 4:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and am sent to show thee these glad --",
    "answer": "tidings 1:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Jesus came down and stood in the plain, a great multitude of people from these places came to hear him and to be healed of their diseases",
    "answer": "Judaea, Jerusalem, sea coast of Tyre and Sidon 6:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many of his disciples did John send unto Jesus with a question",
    "answer": "two 7:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But that on good ground are they which in -- and -- heart having heard the word -- it and bring forth fruit with --",
    "answer": "honest, good, keep, patience 8:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How often would one have to take up his cross to follow Jesus",
    "answer": "daily 9:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Jesus who desired to see and hear the things the disciples have seen and heard but have not",
    "answer": "many prophets and kings 10:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Did not our hearts -- within us while He talked with us by the way, and while He opened to us the --",
    "answer": "burn, scriptures 24:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to what will they say cover us",
    "answer": "the hills 23:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and sit on thrones judging the -- tribes of Israel",
    "answer": "twelve 22:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the sea and -- roaring",
    "answer": "waves 21:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose image and -- hath it, they answered and said caesar's.",
    "answer": "superscription 20:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the noble man command to take from the wicked servant the pound and give to him that has ten pounds",
    "answer": "them that stood by 19:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How hardly shall they that have -- enter into the kingdom of God",
    "answer": "riches 18:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For as the -- that lihteneth out of one part under heaven, shineth unto the other part under heaven so shall also the Son of man be in His day",
    "answer": "lightening 17:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "once the beggar died to where was he carried by the angels",
    "answer": "into Abraham's bosom 16:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"thy brother is come, and thy father hath killed the fatted calf, because he hath received him safe and sound\"",
    "answer": "servant to the elder brother 15:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For I say unto you that none of those men which are bidden shall taste of my --",
    "answer": "supper 14:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the ravens neither -- nor --",
    "answer": "sow,reap 12:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The scriptures states Jesus went through the cites and villages teaching and journeying towards this place",
    "answer": "Jerusalem 13:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus saw this of the men He said, Man, thy sins are forgiven thee",
    "answer": "their faith 5:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say the evil generation seek",
    "answer": "a sign 11:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The shepherds returned doing two things for all the things they had seen and heard one was glorifying God what was the other",
    "answer": "praising God 2:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The people were in expectation and all men mused in their hearts concerning this of John",
    "answer": "whether he was the Christ or not 3:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to set at -- them that are bruised",
    "answer": "liberty 4:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Gabriel say would happen to Zacharias because he did not believe his words",
    "answer": "he shall be dumb and not able to speak until the day that these things be performed 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Those vexed with these were healed",
    "answer": "unclean spirits 6:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the question John sent two of his disciples to ask Jesus",
    "answer": "Art thou He that should come, or look we for another? 7:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say no man does with a candle when he lights it",
    "answer": "cover it with a vessel, or put it under a bed 8:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For whosoever shall -- his life shall lose it, but whosoever will lose his life for my sake shall -- it",
    "answer": "save, save 9:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who tempted Jesus asking Him, \"Master what shall I do to inherit eternal life\"",
    "answer": "a certain lawyer 10:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "then one said unto Him Lord are there few that be --",
    "answer": "saved 13:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For if they do these things in a -- tree what shall be done in the --",
    "answer": "green, dry 23:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for what purpose did Jesus tell Simon satan desire to have him",
    "answer": "to sift him as wheat 22:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Men's heart failing them for --",
    "answer": "fear 21:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- therefore unto Caesar the -- which be Caesar's and unto God the -- which be God's.",
    "answer": "render, things, things 20:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the nobleman command concerning his enemies that would not have him reign over them",
    "answer": "bring them, and slay them before him 19:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "It is easier for a camel to go through this, than for a rich man to enter into the kingdom of God",
    "answer": "a needle's eye 18:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but first must He suffer many things and be -- of this generation",
    "answer": "rejected 17:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the rich man died and was in torment in this place",
    "answer": "hell 16:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "upon hearing the news of his brother's return what was the reaction of the elder brother",
    "answer": "he was angry and would not go in 15:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus told the multitude if a man does not hate these he cannot be his disciple",
    "answer": "father, mother, wife, children, brethren, sister, his own life 14:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when did the two men arose and returned to Jerusalem to the eleven",
    "answer": "the same hour 24:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the ravens neither have-- or barns",
    "answer": "storehouses 12:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus told the man his sins were forgiven, the scribes and pharisees began to reason, what two question did they ask",
    "answer": "who is this which speak blasphemies? who can forgive sins but God only? 5:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said no sign will be given to the evil generation but the sign of",
    "answer": "Jonas the prophet 11:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many days were accomplished for the circumcising of the child",
    "answer": "eight days 2:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John said he baptized with this",
    "answer": "water 3:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To preach the -- year of the Lord",
    "answer": "acceptable 4:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "..because thou believest not my words which shall be performed in their --",
    "answer": "season 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because this went out of Jesus and they were healed the whole multitude sought to touch Him",
    "answer": "virtue 6:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the disciples of John came to Jesus with the question, name the miracles they witnessed Jesus performing that same hour",
    "answer": "cured many of infirmities and plagues and evil spirits, gave sight to many blind 7:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where does a man set a candle when he lights it",
    "answer": "on a candlestick 8:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For what is a man -- if he gain the whole world, and lose himself or be cast away",
    "answer": "advantaged 9:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when asked about how to inherit eternal life, what two questions did Jesus ask the lawyer",
    "answer": "what is written in the law? how readest thou? 10:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And whosoever doth not bear his -- and come after me, cannot be my disciple",
    "answer": "cross 14:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord is risen indeed and hath appeared to --",
    "answer": "Simon 24:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many malefactors were led with Jesus to be put to death",
    "answer": "two 23:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said He prayed that this of Simon fail not",
    "answer": "his faith 22:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the powers of heaven shall be --",
    "answer": "shaken 21:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- therefore unto Caesar the -- which be Caesar's and unto God the -- which be God's.",
    "answer": "render, things, things 20:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when He came nigh unto Bethphage and Bethany at the mount of olives Jesus sent this many disciples",
    "answer": "two 19:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they that heard said, who then can be --",
    "answer": "saved 18:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As it was in the days of -- so shall it be also in the days of the Son of man",
    "answer": "Noah 17:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the rich man lift up in hell",
    "answer": "his eyes 16:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "because of the elder son's refusal to come in, what did the father do",
    "answer": "came out and intreated him 15:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and God feed them, how much more are ye better than the --",
    "answer": "fowls 12:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which gate did Jesus say strive to enter in",
    "answer": "the strait gate 13:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Blessed be ye -- for yours is the kingdom of God",
    "answer": "poor 6:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what cause the people to marvel that waited for Zacharias",
    "answer": "that he tarried so long in the temple 1:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "compared to himself how did John describe the one that cometh",
    "answer": "mightier 3:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "after Jesus read the passage of scripture from the book what did He do",
    "answer": "closed the book, gave it to the minister and sat down 4:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus perceive of the scribes and pharisees",
    "answer": "their thoughts 5:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After what event was baby Jesus brought to Jerusalem to present Him to the Lord",
    "answer": "after the days of Mary's purification were accomplished according to the law of Moses 2:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Go your way and tell John what things ye have -- and heard, how the -- see, the -- walk, the -- are cleansed, the -- hear, the -- are raised to the -- the gospel is preached.",
    "answer": "seen, blind, lame, lepers, deaf, dead, poor 7:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why does a man set a candle on the candlestick when he lights it",
    "answer": "that they which enter in may see the light 8:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But whosoever shall be -- of me and of my words, of him shall the Son of man be ashamed when He shall come in His own -- and in His Father's and of the holy --",
    "answer": "ashamed, glory, angels 9:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he answering said, thou shalt love the Lord thy God, with all thy -- and with all thy -- and with all -- and with all thy -- and thy -- as thyself",
    "answer": "heart, soul, strength, mind, neighbor 10:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was Jonas a sign unto",
    "answer": "the Ninevites 11:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say one does first if they intend to build a tower",
    "answer": "sit down and count the cost, whether he have sufficient to finish it 14:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As the men spoke Jesus stood in the midst, with what words did He greet them",
    "answer": "peace be unto you 24:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "name the place where they crucified Jesus",
    "answer": "Calvary 23:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell Simon to do when he is converted",
    "answer": "strengthen thy brethren 22:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who shall be seen coming in a cloud with power and great glory",
    "answer": "the Son of man 21:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who deny there's any resurrection",
    "answer": "the Saducees 20:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what animal did Jesus tell the disciples they will find tied in the village",
    "answer": "colt 19:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The things which are -- with men are -- with God",
    "answer": "impossible, possible 18:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "They did eat they -- they married -- they were given in -- until the day that Noah entered the -- and the floods came and -- them all.",
    "answer": "drank, wives, marriage, ark, destroyed 17:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "lifting up his eyes in hell who did the rich man see a far off",
    "answer": "Abraham and Lazarus in his bosom 16:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Lo these many years do I serve thee, neither -- I at any time thy -- and yet thou never gave me a -- that I might make merry with my --",
    "answer": "transgressed, commandment, kid, friends 15:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And which of you with taking thought can add to his stature one --",
    "answer": "cubit 12:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- I say unto you,will seek to enter in and shall not be able",
    "answer": "many 13:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Blessed are they that hunger now for ye shall be --",
    "answer": "filled 6:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the people perceive had happened to Zachrias in the temple",
    "answer": "he had seen a vision 1:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the one that cometh did John say he was not worthy to unloose",
    "answer": "latchet of His shoes 3:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of them in the synagogue was fastened on Jesus",
    "answer": "eyes 4:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whether is easier to say, thy sins be forgiven thee or to say ..",
    "answer": "rise up and walk 5:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As it is written in the law of the Lord every male that openeth the womb shall be called -- to the Lord",
    "answer": "holy 2:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and -- is he whosoever shall not be offended in me",
    "answer": "blessed 7:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For nothing is secret that shall not be made --",
    "answer": "manifest 8:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say some standing there will not taste of till they see the kingdom of God",
    "answer": "death 9:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus to the lawyer, thou has answered right, this do and thou shalt --",
    "answer": "live 10:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus say would be a sign to this generation",
    "answer": "the Son of man 11:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "if one intending to build a tower lays the foundation but is not able to finish it, those beholding it would begin to do what to him",
    "answer": "mock him 14:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But they were terrified and -- and supposed they had seen a --",
    "answer": "affrighted, spirit 24:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with respect to Jesus where were the malefactors crucified",
    "answer": "one on the right hand one on the left 23:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Simon to Jesus, Lord I am ready to go with thee both into -- and to --",
    "answer": "prison, death 22:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and when these things begin to come to pass then look up and lift up your heads for your -- draweth nigh",
    "answer": "redemption 21:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Moses' writing what was the criteria for a man marrying his brother's wife",
    "answer": "if the brother died having no children he should marry her to raise up seed unto his brother 20:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "prior to Jesus who sat on the colt",
    "answer": "no man 19:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"lo we have left all and followed thee\"",
    "answer": "Peter 18:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Likewise also as it was in the days of Lot, they did -- they drank, they bought they --, they planted they --",
    "answer": "eat, sold, builded 17:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the rich man in hell address Abraham",
    "answer": "father Abraham 16:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But as soon as this thy son was come, which hath devoured thy living with -- thou had killed for him the fatted calf",
    "answer": "harlots 15:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If ye then be not able to do that thing which is -- why take ye thought for the --",
    "answer": "least, rest 12:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will the master of the house rise up and shut",
    "answer": "the door 13:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Blessed are ye that -- now for ye shall laugh",
    "answer": "weep 6:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for he -- unto them and remained speechless",
    "answer": "beckoned 1:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John said the one that cometh will baptize with these",
    "answer": "Holy Ghost and fire 3:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And He began to say unto them this day is the -- fulfilled in your ears",
    "answer": "scripture 4:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Be specific, Jesus wanted the scribes and pharisees to know that this person hath power on earth to forgive sins",
    "answer": "Son of man 5:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For every male what sacrifice was to be offered",
    "answer": "a pair of turtledoves or two young pigeons 2:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus asked the people if they went out in the wilderness to see, this shaken with the wind",
    "answer": "reed 7:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "neither anything -- that shall not be made known and come abroad",
    "answer": "hid 8:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "about how many days after the sayings did Jesus take Peter, John and James into a mountain to pray",
    "answer": "eight days 9:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was the lawyer willing to justify",
    "answer": "himself 10:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which woman did Jesus say will rise in the judgment with the men of this generation and condemn them",
    "answer": "the queen of the South 11:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Lest -- after he hath laid the -- and is not able to finish it all that behold it begin to mock him",
    "answer": "haply, foundation 14:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold my hands and -- handle me and see",
    "answer": "feet 24:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, Father forgive them..",
    "answer": "for they know not what they do 23:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell Simon he would thrice deny",
    "answer": "that he Knows Him 22:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is know when the the trees shoot forth",
    "answer": "summer is nigh 21:29-30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the Saducees story how many brethren had the woman to wife",
    "answer": "seven 20:29-31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus command His disciples to do with the colt",
    "answer": "loose him and bring him hither 19:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Having left these for the kingdom of God sake Jesus said that man will receive manifold more in this present time, and in the world to come life everlasting",
    "answer": "house, parents, brethren, wife, children, 18:29-30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what day after Lot went out of Sodom did it rain fire and brimstone from heaven and destroyed them all",
    "answer": "same day 17:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the rich man in hell want Abraham to have on him",
    "answer": "mercy 16:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"son thou art ever with me, and all that I have is thine\"",
    "answer": "father to elder son 15:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From where did the queen of the south come to hear the wisdom of Solomon",
    "answer": "from the utmost parts of the earth 11:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "those without will knock at the door and say",
    "answer": "Lord, Lord open unto us 13:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Blessed are ye when men shall -- you and when they shall separate you from their -- and shall reproach you and shall cast out your name as -- for the Son of man's sake",
    "answer": "hate, company, evil, 6:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Simeon a man in Jerusalem was described as a just and devout man what was it said that he waiting for",
    "answer": "consolation of Israel 2:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose fan is in his -- and He will -- purge the floor",
    "answer": "hand, throughly 3:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what question was asked after this statement, and all bare Him witness and wondered at the gracious words which proceeded out of His mouth and they said,..",
    "answer": "Is not this Joseph's son 4:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say to the sick of the palsy so that he arose immediately",
    "answer": "I say unto thee arise and take up thy couch, and go into thine house 5:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus asked us to consider how these grow",
    "answer": "the lilies 12:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus asked the people if they went to see a man clothed in this kind of raiment",
    "answer": "soft 7:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As Jesus was praying what happened to the fashion of His countenance",
    "answer": "it was altered 9:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "willing to justify himself what question did the lawyer ask Jesus",
    "answer": "and who is my neighbor? 10:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Zacharias do as soon as the days of his ministration were accomplished",
    "answer": "he departed to his own house 1:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Take heed therefore how ye --, for whosoever hath , to him shall be -- and whosoever hath not from him shall be -- even that which he seemeth to have",
    "answer": "hear, given, taken 8:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I -- you not whence ye are",
    "answer": "know 13:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say a spirit hath not",
    "answer": "flesh and bones 24:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they parted His -- and cast lots",
    "answer": "raiment 23:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When I sent you without purse, and scrip and shoes lacked ye anything and they said",
    "answer": "nothing 22:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Heaven and earth shall pass away but my -- shall not pass away",
    "answer": "words 21:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the story of the seven brethren who died last of all",
    "answer": "the woman 20:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was to be the disciples response if any man asked \"why do ye loose him\"",
    "answer": "because the Lord hath need of him 19:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"behold we go up to Jerusalem and all things that are written by the prophets concerning the Son of man, shall be accomplished\"",
    "answer": "Jesus to the twelve 18:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus warns if you're in this location don't come in the house to get your stuff, and likewise he that is in the field should not return back",
    "answer": "housetop 17:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "It was -- that we should make merry and be glad, for thy brother was dead and is alive again and was lost and is found.",
    "answer": "meet 15:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "saying, this man began to build and was not able to --",
    "answer": "finish 14:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for what purpose did the rich man in hell ask Abraham to send Lazarus",
    "answer": "that he may dip the tip of his finger in water and cool his tongue 16:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For how long did Elisabeth hide herself after she conceived",
    "answer": "five months 1:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The bible says the sick of the palsy took up that whereon he lay, and departed to his house in this manner",
    "answer": "glorifying God 5:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and behold a -- than Solomon is here",
    "answer": "greater 11:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Holy Ghost revealed to Simeon that he should not see death before seeing whom",
    "answer": "the Lord's Christ 2:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He will gather the wheat into this",
    "answer": "garner 3:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what proverb did Jesus tell the people they will say unto Him",
    "answer": "Physician heal thyself 4:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "they toil not they -- not",
    "answer": "spin 12:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Rejoice in that day and -- for joy for behold your -- is great in heaven, for in like manner did their -- unto the prophets",
    "answer": "leap, reward, fathers 6:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "they that are aparelled this way are in kings' courts",
    "answer": "gorgeously 7:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why could not Jesus' mother and brethren come at Him",
    "answer": "for the press 8:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe Jesus' raiment in the mountain",
    "answer": "white and glistering 9:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in Jesus answering He said a certain man went down from Jerusalem to this place",
    "answer": "Jericho 10:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus asked, have ye any meat? what did they give Him",
    "answer": "piece of broiled fish and an honeycomb 24:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who derided Jesus saying \"He saved others, let Him save Himself, if He be Christ the chosen of God\"",
    "answer": "the rulers 23:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell the apostle to sell their garment and buy",
    "answer": "a sword 22:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said take heed to yourselves lest at any time your hearts be overcharged with these and that day come upon you unawares",
    "answer": "surfeiting, drunkenness, cares of this life 21:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the Saducees wanted to know whose wife would the woman be at this event",
    "answer": "the resurrection 20:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who said to the disciples \"why loose ye the colt\"",
    "answer": "the owners 19:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For He shall be delivered unto the -- and shall be -- and spitefully -- and -- on.",
    "answer": "gentiles, mocked, entreated, spitted 18:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "scripture reference \"remember Lot's wife\"",
    "answer": "Luke 17:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while in hell, in what did the rich man say he was tormented",
    "answer": "in the flame 16:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "or what king going to war against another king, sitteth not down first and consulteth whether he be able with -- to meet him that cometh against him with --",
    "answer": "ten thousand, twenty thousand 14:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "we have eaten and drunken in thy -- and thou has -- in our streets",
    "answer": "presence , taught 13:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the men of Nineveh do when Jonas preached",
    "answer": "they repented 11:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who in all his glory was not arrayed like one of the lilies",
    "answer": "Solomon 12:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who were the two men that talked with Jesus in the mountain",
    "answer": "Moses and Elias 9:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who told Jesus thy mother and thy brethren stand without desiring to see thee",
    "answer": "certain 8:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "they that live this way are in kings' courts",
    "answer": "delicately 7:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But -- unto you that are rich! for ye have received your consolation",
    "answer": "woe 6:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the reaction of the people at seeing the sick of the palsy healed",
    "answer": "they were all amazed and glorified God and were filled with fear 5:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus told the people they will ask Him to do in His country what they heard He had done in this place",
    "answer": "Capernaum 4:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what kind of fire will He burn the chaff",
    "answer": "unquenchable 3:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Simeon came by the Spirit into this place",
    "answer": "the temple 2:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "identify the speaker \"thus hath the Lord dealt with me in the days wherein He looked on me to take away my reproach among men\"",
    "answer": "Elisabeth 1:24-25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the parable of the good Samaritan who did the certain man fell among",
    "answer": "thieves 10:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they shall scourge Him and put Him to -- and the third day He shall rise again",
    "answer": "death 18:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "or else, while the other is great way off, he sendeth an -- and desireth conditions of peace",
    "answer": "ambassage 14:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In his lifetime what did the rich man receive and what did Lazarus receive",
    "answer": "good things, evil things 16:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in that night where will two men be when one is taken and the other is left",
    "answer": "in one bed 17:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Looking for an emotion, and while they yet believe not for",
    "answer": "joy 24:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "before Jesus sat what did the disciples cast on the colt",
    "answer": "their garments 19:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "according to Jesus whose children marry and are given in marriage",
    "answer": "the children of this world 20:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For as a snare shall it come on all that dwell on the face of the whole --",
    "answer": "earth 21:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they said Lord here are -- swords and He said unto them it is enough",
    "answer": "two 22:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who mocked Jesus coming to Him and offering Him vinegar",
    "answer": "the soldiers 23:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "depart from me, all ye workers of --",
    "answer": "iniquity 13:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If then God so clothe the -- which is today in the field, and tomorrow is cast into the --, how much more will He clothe you, o ye of little --",
    "answer": "grass, oven, faith 12:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who repented at the preaching of Jonas",
    "answer": "the men of Nineveh 11:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Appearing in glory what did Moses and Elias speak to Jesus of",
    "answer": "His decease which He should accomplish at Jerusalem 9:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus say was His mother and brethren",
    "answer": "these which hear the word of God and do it 8:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but what went ye out for to see? a -- yeah I say unto you and much more than a --",
    "answer": "prophet, prophet 7:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Woe unto them that are full! for ye shall --",
    "answer": "hunger 6:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "At what event were these words uttered \"we have seen strange things today\"",
    "answer": "the healing of the sick of the palsy 5:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did Jesus say no prophet is accepted",
    "answer": "in his own country 4:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And many other things in his -- preached he unto them",
    "answer": "exhortation 3:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who brought the child Jesus into the temple to do for Him after the custom of the law",
    "answer": "His parents 2:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what month was Gabriel sent from God to a city of Galilee",
    "answer": "sixth 1:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the thieves strip the man of",
    "answer": "his raiment 10:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and as He went they spread their -- in the way",
    "answer": "clothes 19:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After they both died, Lazarus was comforted but the rich man",
    "answer": "tormented 16:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "two women will be doing this when one is taken and the other left",
    "answer": "grinding 17:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they understood none of these things, and this saying was -- from them, neither knew they the things which were spoken",
    "answer": "hid 18:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "There shall be weeping and gnashing of teeth, when ye shall see -- and -- and -- and all the -- in the kingdom of God and you yourselves thrust out",
    "answer": "Abraham, Isaac, Jacob, prophets 13:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But they which shall be accounted -- to obtain that world and the -- from the dead, neither marry nor are given in marriage",
    "answer": "worthy, resurrection 20:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "so that we may be accounted worthy to escape all these things that shall come to pass, and to stand before the Son of man, what does Jesus admonish us to do",
    "answer": "watch and pray always 21:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Pray that ye enter not into --",
    "answer": "temptation 22:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the superscription written of Jesus",
    "answer": "this is the king of the Jews 23:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the places Jesus says it was written concerning Him",
    "answer": "law of Moses, prophets and Psalms 24:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Not forsaking all makes one unfit for this role",
    "answer": "Jesus' disciple 14:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what city of Galilee was Gabriel sent to",
    "answer": "Nazareth 1:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And seek not what ye shall eat, or what ye shall drink neither be ye of -- mind.",
    "answer": "doubtful 12:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jesus find Levi",
    "answer": "sitting at the receipt of customs 5:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"Lord, now lettest now thy servant depart in peace, according to thy word\"",
    "answer": "Simeon 2:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For what reasons was Herod reproved by John",
    "answer": "for Herodias his brother Philip's wife and for all the evils Herod had done 3:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many widows did Jesus say were in Israel in the days of Elias",
    "answer": "many 4:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "No man when he hath lighted a candle, put it in a -- place neither under a bushel",
    "answer": "secret 11:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Woe unto them that -- now for ye shall mourn and weep",
    "answer": "laugh 6:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "behold I send my -- before thy face, which shall prepare thy way before thee",
    "answer": "messenger 7:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the disciples do when Jesus said, let us go over unto the other side of the lake",
    "answer": "they launched forth 8:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while on the mountain it is said that Peter and they that were with him, were heavy with this",
    "answer": "sleep 9:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the thieves wounded the man and left him in this condition",
    "answer": "half dead 10:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said they will come from these directions and sit down in the kingdom of God.",
    "answer": "east, west, north, south 13:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then opened He their -- that they may understand the scriptures",
    "answer": "understanding 24:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what languages were the superscription written",
    "answer": "Greek, Latin, Hebrew 23:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the mount of olives Jesus withdrew this distance from them and knelt down and prayed",
    "answer": "about a stone's cast 22:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "at night Jesus went out and abode in this mount",
    "answer": "mount of olives 21:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Neither can they die anymore for they are equal to the -- and are the children of God, being the children of the resurrection",
    "answer": "angels 20:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with respect to the mount of olives where was Jesus when the whole multitude of disciples began to rejoice and praise God",
    "answer": "at the descent of the mount of olives 19:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As Jesus came nigh unto Jericho a certain man sat by the way side begging, what was the physical ailment of that man",
    "answer": "he was blind 18:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what outdoor location will two men be when one is taken and the other left",
    "answer": "field 17:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham tell the rich man was fixed between the two of them",
    "answer": "great gulf 16:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is good",
    "answer": "salt 14:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For all these things do the -- of the world seek after, and your -- knoweth that ye have need of these things.",
    "answer": "nations, Father 12:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Not looking for a name, which individual in Nazareth was Gabriel sent to",
    "answer": "a virgin espoused to a man whose name was Joseph 1:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who first encountered the man in the parable of the good Samaritan and what did he do",
    "answer": "a priest, he passed by on the other side 10:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Peter and they with him awoke what did they see on the mountain",
    "answer": "Jesus' glory and the two men that stood with Him 9:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As they sailed what kind of storm came on the lake",
    "answer": "a storm of wind 8:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "among those born of women Jesus said there is not a greater prophet than this man",
    "answer": "John the baptist 7:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Woe unto you, when all men shall speak well of you, for so did their fathers to the --",
    "answer": "false prophets 6:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Levi's occupation",
    "answer": "a publican 5:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was shut up for three years and six months",
    "answer": "the heaven 4:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Luke 3:20 says above all Herod added this deed",
    "answer": "shut up John in prison 3:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what did Simeon take up the child Jesus",
    "answer": "in his arms 2:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the light of the body",
    "answer": "the eye 11:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "--be the king that cometh in the name of the Lord peace in -- and glory in the highest",
    "answer": "blessed, heaven 19:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the rich man asked that Lazarus be sent to this place to testify to his brethren",
    "answer": "father's house 16:27-28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where will the eagles be gathered together",
    "answer": "wheresoever the body is 17:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the blind man cry saying",
    "answer": "Jesus thou son of David have mercy on me 18:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And behold there are -- which shall be first and -- which shall be --",
    "answer": "last, first, first, last 13:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus say are raised",
    "answer": "the dead 20:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what time did the people come in the temple to hear Him",
    "answer": "early in the morning 21:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, Father if thou be willing, remove this cup from me, nevertheless not my will ..",
    "answer": "but thine be done 22:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "identify the speaker \"if thou be the Christ, save thyself and us\"",
    "answer": "one of the malefactors 23:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides repentance what else should be preached in His name among all the nation",
    "answer": "remission of sins 24:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but if the salt have lost his -- wherewith shall it be --",
    "answer": "savor, seasoned 14:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happens when the eye is single",
    "answer": "the whole body is full of light 11:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But rather seek ye the -- and all these things shall be added unto you",
    "answer": "kingdom of God 12:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say to Levi when He met him",
    "answer": "follow me 5:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "of whose house was Joseph",
    "answer": "David's 1:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Jesus was baptized in what bodily shape did the Holy Ghost descend upon Him",
    "answer": "a dove 3:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How does the bible describe the famine that was throughout all the land in the days of Elias",
    "answer": "great 4:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Joseph and Mary's reaction at the things spoken by Simeon",
    "answer": "they marvelled 2:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- your enemies",
    "answer": "love 6:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is greater than John the baptist",
    "answer": "he that is least in the kingdom of God 7:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they were filled with water and were in --",
    "answer": "jeopardy 8:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Not knowing what to say, what did Peter suggest should be made for Jesus, Moses and Elias",
    "answer": "three tabernacles 9:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who came next and looked on the man, and passed by the other side",
    "answer": "a Levite 10:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Fear not little -- for it is your Father's good -- to give you the --",
    "answer": "flock, pleasure, kingdom 12:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "at what place should the preaching begin",
    "answer": "Jerusalem 24:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Dost thou not fear God, seeing thou art in the same --",
    "answer": "condemnation 23:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who appeared strengthening Jesus",
    "answer": "an angel from heaven 22:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "showing the dead are raised, what did Moses call the Lord at the bush",
    "answer": "God of Abraham, and the God of Isaac and the God of Jacob 20:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "identify the speaker(s) \"Master, rebuke thy disciples \"",
    "answer": "some of the Pharisees 19:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who rebuked the blind man, that he should hold his peace",
    "answer": "they which went before 18:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many brethren did the rich man have",
    "answer": "five 16:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "salt with no savor is not fit for these places",
    "answer": "land, dunghill 14:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who warned Jesus to depart for Herod intended to kill Him",
    "answer": "certain of the Pharisees 13:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happens when the eye is evil",
    "answer": "the whole body is full of darkness 11:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Luke 1:28 how did Gabriel address Mary",
    "answer": "hail, thou that art highly favored, the Lord is with thee, blessed art thou among women"
  },
  {
    "stem": "While Peter was speaking on the mount what came and overshadowed them",
    "answer": "a cloud 9:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the disciples say to Jesus when they awoke Him",
    "answer": "Master, master we perish 8:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who justified God, being baptized with the baptism of John",
    "answer": "all the people that heard him and the publicans 7:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "do good to them which -- you",
    "answer": "hate 6:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Levi do when Jesus said follow me",
    "answer": "he left all, arose and followed Him 5:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said of all the widows Elias was sent to one living in this place",
    "answer": "Sarepta 4:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was opened when Jesus was baptized",
    "answer": "the heaven 3:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "A light to lighten the --",
    "answer": "Gentiles 2:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Samaritan have on the man when he saw him",
    "answer": "compassion 10:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "sell that ye have and give --, provide yourselves -- which wax not old, a treasure in the -- that faileth not, where no -- approacheth neither -- corrupteth",
    "answer": "alms, bags, heavens, thief, moth 12:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what do men do with salt that has no savor",
    "answer": "cast it out 14:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham said unto them they have -- and the -- let them hear them",
    "answer": "Moses, prophets 16:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the blind do when he was rebuked",
    "answer": "cried so much the more 18:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus told the disciples to tarry in the city of Jerusalem until they be endued with this",
    "answer": "power from on high 24:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I tell you that if these should hold their peace, the -- would immediately cry out",
    "answer": "stones 19:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For He is not a God of the -- but of the -- for all -- unto Him",
    "answer": "dead, living,live 20:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "being in this state the scriptures says Jesus prayed more earnestly",
    "answer": "in agony 22:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for we receive the due reward for our -- but this man had done nothing amiss",
    "answer": "deeds 23:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Which man did Jesus refer to as a fox",
    "answer": "Herod 13:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- them that curse you",
    "answer": "bless 6:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Take heed therefore that the light which is in thee be not --",
    "answer": "darkness 11:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What is Sarepta",
    "answer": "a city of Sidon 4:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how did Mary react to Gabriel's greetings",
    "answer": "she was troubled 1:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold this child is set for the -- and -- again of many in Israel and for a -- which shall be spoken against",
    "answer": "fall, rising, sign 2:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Jesus was baptized what did the voice from heaven say",
    "answer": "Thou art my beloved Son in thee I am well pleased 3:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Samaritan do the man's wounds",
    "answer": "bound it up, pouring in oil and wine 10:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Levi make at his own house",
    "answer": "a great feast 5:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then He arose and rebuked the wind and the -- of water and they ceased and there was a --",
    "answer": "raging, calm 8:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how did the disciples feel as they entered into the cloud",
    "answer": "they feared 9:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by not being baptized by John what did the Pharisees and lawyers reject against themselves",
    "answer": "the counsel of God 7:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Repeat Luke 12:34",
    "answer": "For where your treasure is, there will your heart be also"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He led them out as far as to --",
    "answer": "Bethany 24:50"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Lord remember me when thou comest in thy --",
    "answer": "kingdom 23:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was described as great drops of blood falling down to the ground",
    "answer": "Jesus' sweat 22:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker(s) Master thou has well said",
    "answer": "certain of the scribes 20:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And when He was come near He beheld the city and -- over it",
    "answer": "wept 19:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to who did Jesus address these words \"what wilt thou that I shall do unto thee\"",
    "answer": "the blind man at Jericho 18:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the rich man say his brothers would do if one from the dead went unto them",
    "answer": "they would repent 16:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold I cast out devils and I do cures today and tomorrow and the third day I shall be --",
    "answer": "perfected 13:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "ftv he that hath ears to hear ...",
    "answer": "let him hear 14:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and cast in her mind what manner of -- this should be",
    "answer": "salutation 1:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said from all this group of people only Naaman was cleansed by Eliseus",
    "answer": "lepers 4:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Samaritan set the man on",
    "answer": "his own beast 10:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Yea a sword shall pierce through thy own -- that the thoughts of many hearts may be revealed",
    "answer": "soul 2:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Luke 3:23 states that Jesus was about this age",
    "answer": "thirty 3:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If thy whole -- be therefore full of light, having no part -- the whole shall be full of light as when the bright -- of a candle doth give thee light",
    "answer": "body, dark, shinning 11:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "There was a great company of this group at Levi's feast",
    "answer": "publicans 5:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and -- for them which despitefully use you",
    "answer": "pray 6:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said the men of this generation are liken to children sitting in this place and calling one to another",
    "answer": "marketplace 7:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what question did Jesus ask the disciples after He rebuked the wind",
    "answer": "where is your faith 8:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what came out of the cloud",
    "answer": "a voice 9:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while Jesus blessed them He was parted from them and carried up to this place",
    "answer": "Heaven 24:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Verily I say unto thee today, shalt thou be with me in --",
    "answer": "paradise 23:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And when He rose up from prayer and was come to His disciples He found them sleeping for --",
    "answer": "sorrow 22:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In which book does David say these words, \"the Lord said unto my Lord sit thou on my right hand, till I make thine enemies thy footstool\"",
    "answer": "Psalms 20:42-43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If thou had known, even thou at least in this day, the things which belong to thy -- but now are they hid from thine eyes",
    "answer": "peace 19:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Receive thy sight, thy -- hath saved thee",
    "answer": "faith 18:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he said unto him, if they -- not Moses and the prophets, neither will they be -- though one rose from the --",
    "answer": "hear, persuaded, dead 16:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Nevertheless I must walk today and tomorrow and the day --",
    "answer": "following 13:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Let your -- be girded about, and your lights burning.",
    "answer": "loins 12:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the voice out of the cloud say",
    "answer": "this is my beloved Son hear Him 9:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "a certain Pharisee besought Him to -- with him and He went in and sat down to meat",
    "answer": "dine 11:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what nationality was Naaman",
    "answer": "Syrian 4:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the prophetess mentioned in Luke 2:36",
    "answer": "Anna 2:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus the son of Joseph the son --",
    "answer": "Heli 3:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the angel tell Mary she has found with God",
    "answer": "favor 1:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The scribes and pharisees murmured against the disciples asking why does Jesus do this with publicans and sinners",
    "answer": "eat and drink 5:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say to do unto him that smite thee on the one cheek",
    "answer": "offer also the other 6:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "we have piped unto you and ye have not --",
    "answer": "danced 7:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what manner of man is this, for He -- even the winds and water and they obey Him",
    "answer": "commandeth 8:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to what place did the Samaritan bring the man",
    "answer": "to the inn 10:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Pharisee marvelled that Jesus had not first done this before dinner",
    "answer": "washed 11:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Upon Jesus departure to heaven it is said they returned to Jerusalem with this emotion",
    "answer": "great joy 24:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from what hour to what hour was there darkness over the land",
    "answer": "sixth to ninth hour 23:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Judas came to betray Jesus how many accompanied him",
    "answer": "a multitude 22:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus questioned how they can say, Christ is this man's son",
    "answer": "David's 20:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will it's enemies cast about Jerusalem",
    "answer": "a trench 19:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how soon did the blind man receive his sight",
    "answer": "immediately 18:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said it cannot be that a prophet perish out of this place",
    "answer": "Jerusalem 13:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And ye yourselves like unto men that wait for their --, when he will return from the -- and when he cometh and --, they may open unto him --",
    "answer": "lord, wedding, knocketh, immediately 12:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "having witnessed the transfiguration on the mountain Luke 9:36 said the disciples did this",
    "answer": "kept it close and told no man in those days the things which they had seen"
  },
  {
    "stem": "on the morrow when the Samaritan departed how much money did he give to the host",
    "answer": "two pence 10:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, which was the son of Enos, which was the son of Seth, which was the son of Adam ..",
    "answer": "which was the son of God 3:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the disciples say the wind and water do to Jesus",
    "answer": "obey Him 8:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the parent of Anna",
    "answer": "Phanuel 2:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what name did the angel instruct Mary to call the child",
    "answer": "Jesus 1:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when they in the synagogue heard they were filled with --",
    "answer": "wrath 4:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who need not a physician",
    "answer": "they that are whole 5:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and to him that take away thy cloke forbid not to take thy -- also",
    "answer": "coat 6:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "we have -- to you and ye have not wept",
    "answer": "mourned 7:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And were continually in the temple -- and -- God, amen.",
    "answer": "praising, blessing 24:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which part of the cup and platter do the Pharisees make clean",
    "answer": "the outside 11:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Judas betrayest thou the Son of man with a --",
    "answer": "kiss 22:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "David therefore calleth Him -- how can He be His --",
    "answer": "Lord, Son 20:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who will compass Jerusalem and keep it on every side",
    "answer": "it's enemies 19:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the blind man do after he received his sight",
    "answer": "he followed Jesus, glorifying God 18:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "O Jerusalem, Jerusalem thou that kills the -- and -- them that are sent unto thee",
    "answer": "prophets, stone 13:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- are those servants whom the lord when he cometh shall find watching.",
    "answer": "blessed 12:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the -- was darkened and the veil of the temple was rent in the --",
    "answer": "sun, midst 23:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"take care of him, and whatsoever thou spendest more, when I come again, I will repay thee\"",
    "answer": "Samaritan to the host 10:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "They rose up and thrust Jesus out of the city where did they lead Him to and for what purpose",
    "answer": "brow of the hill whereon their city was built, to cast Him down headlong 4:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "on the -- day when they were come down from the hill much people met Him",
    "answer": "next 9:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To what tribe did Anna belong",
    "answer": "Aser 2:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He shall be great and shall be called the Son of the -- and the Lord God shall give unto Him the throne of His father --",
    "answer": "Highest, David 1:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who do the sick need",
    "answer": "a physician 5:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- to every man that ask of thee",
    "answer": "give 6:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Even though John did not come doing these things they say he hath a devil",
    "answer": "eating bread, drinking wine 7:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In which country did they encounter a man that had devils a long time",
    "answer": "Gadarenes 8:26-27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus say the inward part of the Pharisee is full of",
    "answer": "ravening and wickedness 11:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Father into thy hands I commend my spirit, having said this, what did Jesus do",
    "answer": "gave up the ghost 23:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose right ear was cut off",
    "answer": "the servant of the high priest 22:50"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what robes do scribes desire to walk in",
    "answer": "long robes 20:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And shall lay thee even with the ground, and thy -- within thee",
    "answer": "children 19:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the people do when they saw the blind man received his sight",
    "answer": "gave praise unto God 18:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how often would I have gathered thy -- together as a hen gather her -- under her wings and ye would not",
    "answer": "children, brood 13:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "verily I say unto you that he shall gird himself, and make them to sit down to meat and will come forth and -- them",
    "answer": "serve 12:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the longest chapter in Luke, how many verses does it have",
    "answer": "chapter two, eighty verses"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when asked who was a neighbor to the man, what was the lawyer's response",
    "answer": "he that showed mercy on him 10:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but He passing through the -- of them went His way",
    "answer": "midst 4:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Master, I -- thee look upon my son, for he is mine only child",
    "answer": "beseech 9:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what word does the scripture use to describe the age of Anna",
    "answer": "great 2:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And He shall -- over the house of Jacob forever and of His kingdom there shall be no --",
    "answer": "reign, end 1:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I came not to call the -- but -- to ---",
    "answer": "righteous, sinners, repentance 5:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and of him that take away thy -- ask them not again",
    "answer": "goods 6:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Son of man is come eating and drinking and ye say, behold a -- man, and a -- a friend of -- and sinners",
    "answer": "gluttonous, winebibber, publicans 7:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the man with the devils did not abide in any house but in this",
    "answer": "the tombs 8:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many chapters does the book of Luke have",
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who glorified God saying, 'certainly this was a righteous man\"",
    "answer": "the centurion 23:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Be ye come out as against a -- with swords and --",
    "answer": "thief, staves 22:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what do scribes love in the markets",
    "answer": "greetings 20:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they shall not leave in thee one stone upon another because thou knew not the time of thy --",
    "answer": "visitation 19:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Behold your house is left unto you --",
    "answer": "desolate 13:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And if he shall come in the -- watch or come in the -- watch, and find them so, blessed are those servants",
    "answer": "second, third 12:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ye --, did not he that made that which is without make that which is within also",
    "answer": "fools 11:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"go and do thou likewise\"",
    "answer": "Jesus to the lawyer 10:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what does the man say occurs when the spirit takes his son",
    "answer": "he suddenly crieth out, it teareth him, he foameth and it bruises him 9:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the man do when He saw Jesus",
    "answer": "he cried out and fell down before Him 8:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is justified of all her children",
    "answer": "wisdom 7:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, as ye would that men should do to you...",
    "answer": "do ye also to them likewise 6:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's disciples fast oft and make prayers",
    "answer": "the disciples of John and the pharisees 5:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "after escaping the people who tried to cast Him off a hill to what place did Jesus go",
    "answer": "Capernaum a city of Galilee 4:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long had Anna lived with her husband",
    "answer": "seven years from her virginity 2:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV,Then Mary said unto the angel , how shall this be .....",
    "answer": "seeing I know not a man 1:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But rather give -- of such things as ye have, and behold, all things are clean unto you.",
    "answer": "alms 11:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the last word in the book of Luke",
    "answer": "amen"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did they smote, beholding those things which were done",
    "answer": "their breast 23:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus told the chief priests, captains of the temple and the elders when He was daily in this place they stretched forth no hands against him",
    "answer": "temple 22:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where do the scribes love the highest rooms",
    "answer": "in synagogues 20:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jesus cast out of the temple",
    "answer": "them that sold therein and them that bought 19:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV verily I say unto you, ye shall not see me, until the time come when ye shall say ..",
    "answer": "Blessed is He that cometh in the name of the Lord 13:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If the good man of the house had known what hour the thief would come what would he have done",
    "answer": "he would have watched and not have suffered his house to be broken through 12:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Luke 7:36 what did one of the Pharisees desire Jesus to do",
    "answer": "eat with him"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which woman received Jesus into her house",
    "answer": "Martha 10:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what have I to do with thee Jesus, thou Son of God Most High, I beseech thee -- me not",
    "answer": "torment 8:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The -- shall come upon thee, and the power of the Highest shall -- thee, therefore that holy -- which shall be born of thee shall be called the -- of God.",
    "answer": "Holy Ghost, overshadow, thing, Son 1:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For if ye -- them which -- you what thank have ye? for sinners also -- those that -- them.",
    "answer": "love, love, love, love 6:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while the disciples of John and the pharisees fast oft and make prayers what did they say Jesus' disciples did",
    "answer": "eat and drink 5:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "At Capernaum they were astonished at His doctrine for His word was with this",
    "answer": "power 4:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Anna",
    "answer": "about 84 2:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, and I besought thy disciples to cast him out...",
    "answer": "and they could not 9:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was Martha's sister",
    "answer": "Mary 10:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but this is your hour and the power of --",
    "answer": "darkness 22:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who love the chief rooms at feasts",
    "answer": "the scribes 20:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTv It is written, My house is the house of prayer, but ye have made it ..",
    "answer": "a den of thieves 19:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV be ye also ready for the Son of man cometh at an hour ..",
    "answer": "when ye think not 12:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "of what do the Pharisees tithe",
    "answer": "mint,rue, all manner of herbs 11:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph of Arimathaea was described as a good man and --",
    "answer": "just 23:50"
  },
  {
    "stem": "O -- and -- generation how long shall I be with you and suffer you",
    "answer": "faithless, perverse 9:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the man in the tombs kept bound with",
    "answer": "chains and in fetters 8:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the woman that brought the alabaster box of ointment was described as this kind of person",
    "answer": "sinner 7:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And if ye do good to them, which do good to you what thank have ye? for -- also do even the same",
    "answer": "sinners 6:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus asked if you can make the children of the bridechamber fast while this person is with them",
    "answer": "bridegroom 5:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of spirit did the man in synagogue at Capernaum have",
    "answer": "spirit of an unclean devil 4:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Having lost her husband to death seven years after marriage, Anna was this kind of woman",
    "answer": "widow 2:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The angel told Mary this was the -- month of Elisabeth's pregnancy",
    "answer": "sixth 1:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "even though Joseph of Arimathaea was a counsellor what had he not consented to",
    "answer": "the counsel and deed of them 23:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus was led to the high priest's house who followed a far off",
    "answer": "Peter 22:54"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the widows do the scribes devour",
    "answer": "their houses 20:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus taught daily in this place",
    "answer": "the temple 19:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"Lord, speakest thou this parable unto us, or even to all",
    "answer": "Peter 12:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "even though the Pharisees tithe what did Jesus say they pass over",
    "answer": "judgment and the love of God 11:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Mary sat at Jesus' feet and heard His --",
    "answer": "word 10:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while the child was coming to Jesus what did the devil do to him",
    "answer": "threw him down and tare him 9:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what would the man do to the bands",
    "answer": "brake them 8:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in whose house did Jesus sat to meat when a woman in the city came with an alabaster box of ointment",
    "answer": "one of the Pharisees 7:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And if ye lend to them of whom ye hope to receive, what-- have ye?",
    "answer": "thank 6:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will the children of the bridechamber do when the bridegroom is taken from them",
    "answer": "fast 5:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what kind of voice did the man with the spirit at Capernaum cry",
    "answer": "loud voice 4:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From what place did Anna not depart",
    "answer": "temple 2:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Mary and Elisabeth's relationship",
    "answer": "they were cousins 1:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Martha cumbered about",
    "answer": "much serving 10:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Arimathaea",
    "answer": "a city of the Jews 23:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did they kindle the fire when Peter sat down among them",
    "answer": "in the midst of the hall 22:55"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For a show the scribes make these",
    "answer": "long prayers 20:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the chief priest, scribes and chief of the people sought to do to Jesus",
    "answer": "destroy Him 19:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who then is that faithful and wise -- whom his lord shall make ruler over his household, to give them their -- of meat in due season.",
    "answer": "steward, portion 12:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, these ought ye have done..",
    "answer": "and not to leave the other undone 11:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where does no man put a piece of new garment",
    "answer": "upon an old 5:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After Jesus rebuked the unclean spirit and healed the child who did He deliver Him to",
    "answer": "his father 9:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with respect to Jesus where was the woman with the alabaster box of ointment positioned",
    "answer": "at His feet behind Him 7:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for -- also lend to -- to receive as much again",
    "answer": "sinners, sinners 6:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and this is the sixth month with her, who was called --",
    "answer": "barren 1:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the first three words did the man with the spirit of an unclean devil say to Jesus",
    "answer": "let us alone 4:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Anna serve God night and day",
    "answer": "with fastings and prayers 2:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where would the devil drive the man",
    "answer": "into the wilderness 8:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Martha want Jesus to bid her sister to do",
    "answer": "help her 10:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Peter first denied Jesus, what did he say to the maid",
    "answer": "woman I know him not 22:57"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they could not take hold of His words before the people and they -- at His answer and held their peace",
    "answer": "marvelled 20:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they could not find what they might do, for all the people were very -- to hear Him",
    "answer": "attentive 19:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the things the servant that says in his heart \"my lord delayeth his coming\" begins to do",
    "answer": "beat the menservants and maidens, eat and drink and be drunken 12:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where do the Pharisees love the uppermost seats",
    "answer": "in the synagogues 11:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph of Arimathaea wait for",
    "answer": "the kingdom of God 23:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Let these saying sink down in your --for the Son of man shall be delivered into the hands of men",
    "answer": "ears 9:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did the man say his name was legion",
    "answer": "because many devils were entered into him 8:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the woman wash with tears",
    "answer": "Jesus' feet 7:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But love your -- do good and lend hoping for -- again, and your reward shall be -- and ye shall be the children of the -- for He is kind unto the unthankful and to the --",
    "answer": "enemies, nothing, great, Highest, evil 6:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happens if new garment is put upon old",
    "answer": "the new maketh a rent, the piece that was taken out of the new agree not with the old 5:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what two questions did the man with the spirit of an unclean devil ask Jesus",
    "answer": "what have we to do with thee thou Jesus of Nazareth? art thou come to destroy us? 4:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is this referring to, and she coming in that instant gave thanks likewise unto the Lord, and spake of Him to all them that looked for redemption in Jerusalem",
    "answer": "Anna 2:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Repeat Luke 1:37",
    "answer": "For with God nothing shall be impossible"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph beg Pilate for",
    "answer": "the body of Jesus 23:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Peter's second denial of Jesus, what was his response when he was recognized",
    "answer": "man,I am not 22:58"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- therefore unto Caesar the -- which be Caesar's and unto God the -- which be God's.",
    "answer": ""
  },
  {
    "stem": "The lord of that servant will come in a -- when he looketh not for him, and at an -- when he is not -- and will cut him -- and will appoint him his portion with the --",
    "answer": "day, hour, aware, asunder, unbelievers 12:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where do the Pharisees love to receive greetings",
    "answer": "in the markets 11:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Martha, Martha thou art -- and -- about many things",
    "answer": "careful, troubled 10:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the devils besought Jesus that He would not command them to go out into this",
    "answer": "the deep 8:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But they understood not this saying and it was -- from them and they -- to ask Him of that saying",
    "answer": "hid, feared 9:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what did the woman wipe Jesus' feet",
    "answer": "with the hairs of her head 7:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, be ye therefore merciful...",
    "answer": "as your Father also is merciful 6:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where is new wine not to be placed",
    "answer": "in old bottles 5:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, I know thee who thou art ..",
    "answer": "the Holy One of God 4:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Jesus' parents had performed all things according to the law of the Lord, they returned to this place",
    "answer": "Nazareth of Galilee 2:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"behold the handmaid of the Lord, be it unto me, according to thy word\"",
    "answer": "Mary 1:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph wrap Jesus' body in",
    "answer": "linen 23:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much time had elapsed from Peter's second to his third denial of Jesus",
    "answer": "one hour 22:59"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the husbandmen do to the first servant",
    "answer": "beat him and sent him away empty 20:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what will happen to the servant which knew his lord's will and prepared not himself, neither did according to his will",
    "answer": "shall be beaten with many stripes 12:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "this arose among the disciples concerning which of them should be greatest",
    "answer": "a reasoning 9:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But one thing is needful, and Mary hath chosen that -- part which shall not be -- from her.",
    "answer": "good, taken 10:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Woe unto you scribes and pharisees, hypocrites, for ye are as -- which appear not, and the men that walk over them are not aware of them",
    "answer": "graves 11:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where/what did Jesus suffer the devils to enter",
    "answer": "the herd of swine 8:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the child grew and waxed strong in the --, filled with wisdom and the -- of God was upon Him",
    "answer": "spirit, grace 2:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "With what did Mary go into the hill country",
    "answer": "with haste 1:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by whom is wisdom justified",
    "answer": "her children 7:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what words did Jesus cast the spirit of an unclean devil out of the man in the synagogue",
    "answer": "hold thy peace and come out of him 4:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Judge not and ye shall not be --, condemn not and ye shall not be --, forgive and ye shall be --",
    "answer": "judged, condemned, forgiven 6:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "else the new wine will -- the bottle, and be -- and the bottles shall --",
    "answer": "burst, spilled, perish 5:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was the herd of many swine and what were they doing",
    "answer": "on the mountain, feeding 8:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what did Joseph lay Jesus' body",
    "answer": "in a sepulchre 23:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "another confidently affirmed saying of a truth this fellow also was with him, for he is a --",
    "answer": "Galilaean 22:59"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who will be beaten with few stripes",
    "answer": "he that knew not, and did commit things worthy of stripes 12:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker 'Master, thus saying thou reproachest us also\"",
    "answer": "one of the lawyers 11:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "perceiving this of the disciple's heart Jesus took a child and set him by Him",
    "answer": "the thought 9:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Give and it shall be given unto you, good measure -- down, and -- together and -- over shall men give into your --",
    "answer": "pressed, shaken, running, bosom 6:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happens when new wine is put in new bottles",
    "answer": "both are preserved 5:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and when the devil had thrown him in the -- he came out of him and -- him not",
    "answer": "midst, hurt 4:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How often did Jesus' parents go to the passover feast",
    "answer": "every year 2:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Mary went to the hill country to a city of this place",
    "answer": "Juda 1:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "besides washing and wiping what else did the woman do to Jesus' feet",
    "answer": "kissed it and anointed it with the ointment 7:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Whosoever shall receive this child in my name receive --",
    "answer": "me 9:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And that day was the -- and the Sabbath drew on",
    "answer": "preparation 23:54"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Man, I know not what thou sayest, what happened immediately while Peter yet spake these words",
    "answer": "the cock crew 22:60"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Of whom will much be required",
    "answer": "whomsoever much is given 12:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what do the lawyers lade men with",
    "answer": "burdens grievous to be borne 11:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For with the same -- that ye mete withal it shall be -- to you again",
    "answer": "measure, measured 6:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus do when the devils besought Him to enter the herd of swine",
    "answer": "He suffered them 8:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who spake within himself saying \"this man if he were a prophet would have known who and what manner of woman this is that toucheth him, for she is a sinner\"",
    "answer": "the Pharisee Simon 7:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "No man after having drunk old wine straightway desireth new, what does he say of the old",
    "answer": "the old is better 5:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The people were amazed and said with these two things Jesus command the unclean spirits and they come out",
    "answer": "authority and power 4:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And when He was -- they went up to Jerusalem after the custom of the feast",
    "answer": "twelve years old 2:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Mary entered into the house of Zacharias and did this to Elisabeth",
    "answer": "saluted her 1:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the women beheld the sepulchre and how Jesus' body was --",
    "answer": "laid 23:55"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After he thrice denied Jesus who turned and looked upon Peter",
    "answer": "the Lord 22:61"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV and to whom men have committed much, of him they will ..",
    "answer": "ask the more 12:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what do the lawyers not touch the burdens",
    "answer": "one of their fingers 11:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whosoever shall receive me, receive ..",
    "answer": "Him that sent me 9:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the herd of swine run down the steep place into the lake",
    "answer": "violently 8:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the response to this \"Simon I have somewhat to say unto thee\"",
    "answer": "Master, say on 7:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And He spake a -- unto them, can the blind lead the the blind? shall they not both fall into the --?",
    "answer": "parable,ditch 6:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "after Jesus left the synagogue who's house did He enter",
    "answer": "Simon's 4:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who knew not that Jesus had tarried behind in Jerusalem",
    "answer": "Joseph and His mother 2:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what occurred when Elisabeth heard the salutation of Mary",
    "answer": "the babe leaped in her womb, and Elisabeth was filled with the Holy Ghost 1:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the women return and prepare",
    "answer": "spices and ointments 23:56"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After his denial of Jesus the scripture records Peter went out and did this",
    "answer": "wept bitterly 22:62"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for he that is least among you all the same shall be --",
    "answer": "great 9:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I am come to send fire on the earth, and what will I, if it be already --",
    "answer": "kindled 12:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Woe unto you for ye build the -- of the prophets and your fathers killed them",
    "answer": "sepulchers 11:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was taken with a great fever in Simon's house",
    "answer": "his wife's mother 4:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to the herd of swine in the lake",
    "answer": "they were choked 8:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the disciple not above",
    "answer": "his master 6:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Supposing the child Jesus to have been in the company how long did Joseph and Mary journey",
    "answer": "a day 2:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"blessed are thou among women, and blessed it the fruit of thy womb\"",
    "answer": "Elisabeth 1:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many debtors did the certain creditor have",
    "answer": "two 7:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John told Jesus they saw one doing this act and they forbad him, because he did not follow them",
    "answer": "casting out devils in Jesus' name 9:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "according to what did the women rest on the Sabbath day",
    "answer": "according to the commandment 23:56"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the men which held -- mocked Him and smote Him",
    "answer": "Jesus 22:63"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But I have a -- to be baptized with, and how am I straitened till it be accomplished",
    "answer": "baptism 12:50"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Truly ye bear witness that ye allow the deeds of your -- for they indeed killed them, and ye build their sepulchers",
    "answer": "fathers 11:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when they that fed the swine saw what was done, they fled and went and told it where",
    "answer": "in the city and in the country 8:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much did each debtor owe",
    "answer": "one five hundred, the other fifty 7:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but everyone that is -- shall be as his master",
    "answer": "perfect 6:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus stood over her and did this to the fever",
    "answer": "rebuked the fever 4:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Among whom did Joseph and Mary search for Jesus",
    "answer": "kinsfolk and acquaintance 2:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And whence is this the mother of my -- should come to me",
    "answer": "Lord 1:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, forbid him not for he that is not against us ..",
    "answer": "is for us 9:50"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To what will they say fall on us",
    "answer": "the mountains 23:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did they do when they had blindfolded Jesus",
    "answer": "struck Him on the face, and asked Him saying, prophesy who is it that smote thee 22:64"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said He did not come to bring peace on the earth but rather --",
    "answer": "division 12:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what said this \"I will send them prophets and apostles and some of them they shall slay and persecute, that the blood of the prophets which was shed from the foundation of the world may be required of this generation\"",
    "answer": "wisdom of God 11:49-50"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did the creditor do when each debtor had nothing to pay",
    "answer": "he frankly forgave them both 7:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did they that went out to see what was done found the man that had the devils",
    "answer": "sitting at the feet of Jesus, clothed and in his right mind 8:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And why -- thou the mote that is in thy brother's eyes, but -- not the beam that is in thine own eye.",
    "answer": "beholdest, perceivest 6:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Simon's wife's mother do after the fever left her",
    "answer": "immediately she arose and ministered unto them 4:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Joseph and Mary do when they did not find Jesus in their company",
    "answer": "they returned to Jerusalem, seeking Him 2:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For lo as soon as the -- of thy salutation sounded in my ears the babe leaped in my womb for --",
    "answer": "voice, joy 1:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "to what place did Jesus stedfastly set His face to go",
    "answer": "Jerusalem 9:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And many other things -- spake they against Him",
    "answer": "blasphemously 22:65"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From hence forth they shall be -- in one house divided, three against -- and two against --",
    "answer": "five, two, three 12:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From the blood of Abel to the blood of --",
    "answer": "Zacharias 11:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Which debtor did Simon say would love the creditor most",
    "answer": "he to whom he forgave most 7:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did they react to seeing the man in his right mind",
    "answer": "they were afraid 8:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said if you behold not the beam in thine own eye how can you say this to your brother",
    "answer": "brother let me pull out the mote that is in thine eye 6:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "about what time of the day did all they that had any sick with divers diseases bring them unto Jesus",
    "answer": "when the sun was setting 4:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After how many days did Jesus parents find Him in the temple",
    "answer": "three 2:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And blessed is she that believed, for there shall be a -- of those things which were told her from the Lord",
    "answer": "performance 1:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "They also which saw it told them by what means he that was possessed of the devils was --",
    "answer": "healed 8:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "as soon as it was day to where did they lead Jesus",
    "answer": "to the council 22:66"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who shall be divided against the son",
    "answer": "the father 12:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Jesus send messengers to the Samaritan village",
    "answer": "to make ready for Him 9:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Zacharias perish",
    "answer": "between the altar and the temple 11:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom: \"thou has rightly judged\"",
    "answer": "Jesus to Simon 7:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Mary praising God, what did she say doth magnify the Lord",
    "answer": "my soul 1:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus lay on the sick to heal them",
    "answer": "His hands 4:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when they found the child Jesus in the temple in whose midst was He sitting",
    "answer": "the doctors 2:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Thou -- cast out first the beam out of thine own eye, and then thou shall see -- to pull out the mote that is in thy -- eyes.",
    "answer": "hypocrite, clearly, brother's 6:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did not the Samaritan village receive Jesus",
    "answer": "because His face was as though He would go to Jerusalem 9:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jesus hereafter the Son of man shall sit",
    "answer": "on the right hand of the power of God 22:69"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who shall daughter be divided against",
    "answer": "the mother 12:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what key did Jesus state the lawyers have taken away",
    "answer": "the key of knowledge 11:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell Simon he did not give Him for His feet",
    "answer": "water 7:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the whole multitude of the country of the Gadarenes besought Jesus to do",
    "answer": "depart from them 8:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of fruit does a good tree not bring forth",
    "answer": "corrupt fruit 6:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the devils that came out of many were crying out and saying this",
    "answer": "thou art Christ the Son of God 4:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Jesus doing in the midst of the doctors",
    "answer": "both hearing them and asking them questions 2:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And my spirit hath -- in the God my Saviour",
    "answer": "rejoiced 1:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did the country of the Gadarenes besought Jesus to depart from them",
    "answer": "for they were taken with great fear 8:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they said what need we any further --",
    "answer": "witnesses 22:71"
  },
  {
    "stem": "though the lawyers do not enter in themselves what did they do to those that were entering in",
    "answer": "they hindered them 11:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who asked to command fire to come down and consume the Samaritan village for not receiving Jesus",
    "answer": "James and John 9:54"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who will be against the mother in law",
    "answer": "the daughter in law 12:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Thou gavest me no -- but this woman since the time I came in hath not ceased to -- my feet",
    "answer": "kiss, kiss 7:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus rebuked the devils and suffered them not to speak for they knew this",
    "answer": "that He was Christ 4:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And all that heard Him were astonished at His understanding and --",
    "answer": "answers 2:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Mary's praise to God, what did she say God hath regarded",
    "answer": "the low estate of His handmaiden 1:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of tree does not bring forth good fruit",
    "answer": "corrupt tree 6:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and He went up into the -- and returned back again",
    "answer": "ship 8:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who began to urge Jesus vehemently and to provoke Him to speak of many things",
    "answer": "scribes and pharisees 11:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's example did James and John reference when they asked of commanding fire to come down and consuming the Samaritans",
    "answer": "Elias 9:54"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what does a cloud arise out of the west indicate",
    "answer": "a shower cometh 12:54"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Simon not anoint with oil",
    "answer": "Jesus' head 7:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when it was day to what kind of place did Jesus depart",
    "answer": "desert place 4:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What question did Jesus' mother ask Him when they found Him in the temple",
    "answer": "Son why has thou thus dealt with us 2:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Mary say from henceforth all generations will call her",
    "answer": "blessed 1:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is every tree known by",
    "answer": "his own fruit 6:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The man that had the devils besought Jesus to be with Him, but to where did Jesus tell the man to return and show how great things God hath done unto him",
    "answer": "to his own house 8:38-39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what sign is an indication of heat",
    "answer": "when the south wind blows 12:55"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for what purpose were the scribes and pharisees laying wait for Jesus and seeking to catch something out of His mouth",
    "answer": "that they might accuse Him 11:54"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but He turned and -- them and said ye not what manner of -- ye are of",
    "answer": "rebuked, spirit 9:55"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Men do not gather figs of these",
    "answer": "thorns 6:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Her sins which are -- are forgiven, for she -- much.",
    "answer": "many, loved 7:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ftv and the people sought Him and came unto Him and stayed Him that He should not ..",
    "answer": "depart from them 4:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "behold thy father and I have sought thee --",
    "answer": "sorrowing 2:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For He that is mighty hath done to me -- and -- is His name",
    "answer": "great things, holy 1:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ye hypocrites, ye can discern the face of the --, and of the -- , but how is it that ye do not discern the --",
    "answer": "sky, earth, time 12:56"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, but to whom little is forgiven ..",
    "answer": "the same loveth little 7:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the man publish how great things Jesus had done unto him",
    "answer": "throughout the whole city 8:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, for the Son of man is not come to destroy men's lives ..",
    "answer": "but to save them 9:56"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Men do not gather this from a bramble bush",
    "answer": "grapes 6:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And His mercy is on them that fear Him from -- to --",
    "answer": "generation, generation 1:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell the people He must preach to other cities",
    "answer": "the kingdom of God 4:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus responded to His mother's inquiry with two questions one was, how is it that ye sought me, what was the other",
    "answer": "wist ye not that I must be about my Father's business 2:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Jairus occupation",
    "answer": "ruler of the synagogue 8:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He hath showed -- with His arm",
    "answer": "strength 1:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when you go with this person to the magistrate, when in the way give diligence that you may be delivered from him",
    "answer": "adversary 12:58"
  },
  {
    "stem": "having been rejected of the Samaritan village to where did Jesus and His disciples go",
    "answer": "to another village 9:56"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus tell the woman of her sins",
    "answer": "they are forgiven 7:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "A good man out of the -- treasure of his heart bringeth forth that which is --",
    "answer": "good, good 6:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what buildings in Galilee did Jesus preach",
    "answer": "synagogue 4:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "give the scripture reference, and Jesus increased in wisdom and stature and in favor with God and man",
    "answer": "Luke 2:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And He went down with them, and came to Nazareth and was -- unto them",
    "answer": "subject 2:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "An -- man out of the evil -- of his heart bringeth forth that which is evil",
    "answer": "evil, treasure 6:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus told the woman her sins are forgiven, who began to say within themselves, who is this that forgiveth sins also?",
    "answer": "they that sat at meat with Him 7:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jairus fell down at Jesus' feet and besought Him to do this",
    "answer": "that He would come into his house 8:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who said this to Jesus \"Lord I will follow thee, whithersoever thou goest\"",
    "answer": "a certain man 9:57"
  },
  {
    "stem": "lest he hale thee to the --, and the judge deliver thee to the -- and the officer cast thee into --",
    "answer": "judge, officer, prison 12:58"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He hath scattered the -- in the imagination of their hearts",
    "answer": "proud 1:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Jairus' daughter",
    "answer": "about twelve years of age 8:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I tell thee thou shalt not depart thence, till thou has paid the last --",
    "answer": "mite 12:59"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who/what have holes",
    "answer": "foxes 9:58"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus to the woman with ointment, thy -- hath saved thee go in --",
    "answer": "faith, peace 7:50"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for of the -- of his heart his mouth speaketh",
    "answer": "abundance 6:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in Mary's praise from where did she say God hath put down the mighty",
    "answer": "from their seats 1:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and -- them of low degree",
    "answer": "exalted 1:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And why call ye me --, -- and do not the things which I say.",
    "answer": "Lord, Lord 6:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what state did Jairus' daughter lay in",
    "answer": "dying 8:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who/what have nests",
    "answer": "the birds of the air 9:58"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He hath filled the hungry with --",
    "answer": "good things 1:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jesus said whosoever come to Him, hear His sayings and do them he is like a man which built a -- and digged -- and laid the -- on a rock.",
    "answer": "house, deep, foundation 6:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the people do to Jesus as He went to Jairus' house",
    "answer": "thronged Him 8:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but the Son of man hath not where to lay His --",
    "answer": "head 9:58"
  },
  {
    "stem": "before following Jesus what did the individual want permission to go and do",
    "answer": "bury his father 9:59"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and when the flood arose the -- beat vehemently upon that house and could not -- it for it was -- upon a rock",
    "answer": "stream, shake, founded 6:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did the woman have the issue of blood",
    "answer": "twelve years 8:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the -- He hath sent empty away",
    "answer": "rich 1:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He hath holpen His servant Israel in remembrance of His --",
    "answer": "mercy 1:54"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But he that heareth and doeth not is like a man that without a -- built a house upon the -- against which the stream did -- vehemently and immediately it fell and the -- for that house was great.",
    "answer": "foundation, earth, beat, ruin 6:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the woman with the issue of blood spend upon the physicians",
    "answer": "all her living 8:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Let the -- bury their -- but go thou and preach the Kingdom of God.",
    "answer": "dead, dead 9:60"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As He spake to our --, to Abraham and his seed forever",
    "answer": "fathers 1:55"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Jesus' illustration how did the stream beat upon both houses",
    "answer": "vehemently 6:48-49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what could the physicians not do to the woman",
    "answer": "heal her 8:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "before following Jesus to whom did the individual want to go and bid farewell",
    "answer": "those at home in his house 9:61"
  },
  {
    "stem": "No man having put his hand to the -- and looking back is -- for the kingdom of God.",
    "answer": "plough, fit 9:62"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How soon did the house without a foundation built upon the earth fall after the stream beat vehemently",
    "answer": "immediately"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the woman came behind and touched this of Jesus",
    "answer": "border of His garment 8:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For how long did Mary abide with Elisabeth before returning to her own house",
    "answer": "about three months 1:56"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who heard how the Lord had showed great mercy upon Elisabeth and rejoiced with her",
    "answer": "her neighbors and her cousins 1:58"
  },
  {
    "stem": "immediately what happened to the woman's issue of blood after she touched the border of Jesus' garment",
    "answer": "it stanched 8:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "on which day did they come to circumcise the child",
    "answer": "the eight 1:59"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"who touched me?\"",
    "answer": "Jesus 8:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "They called the child Zacharias after the name of his --",
    "answer": "father 1:59"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus asked, who touched me? who denied",
    "answer": "all 8:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who's speaking, \"not so but he shall be called John\"",
    "answer": "his (John's) mother/Elisabeth 1:60"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Master the multitude throng thee and -- thee and sayest thou who -- me",
    "answer": "press, touched 8:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Somebody hath touched me for I perceive that -- is gone out of me",
    "answer": "virtue 8:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they said unto her there is none of thy -- that is called by this name",
    "answer": "kindred 1:61"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they made -- to his father how he would have him called",
    "answer": "signs 1:62"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and when the woman saw that she was not -- she came trembling and falling down before Him.",
    "answer": "hid 8:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when they inquired of Zacharias what name his son would be called, what did he ask for",
    "answer": "a writing table 1:63"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the woman with the issue of blood declare to Jesus before all the people",
    "answer": "for what cause she had touched Him, and how she was healed immediately 8:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Zacharias write on the writing table",
    "answer": "his name is John 1:63"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- be of good comfort thy faith hath made thee whole go in peace",
    "answer": "Daughter 8:48"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the reaction of the people when Zacharias wrote, his name is John",
    "answer": "they marvelled 1:63"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while Jesus yet spake to the woman, one came from the ruler of the synagogue's house with this message to him",
    "answer": "thy daughter is dead, trouble not the Master 8:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to Zacharias after he wrote the words and what did he do",
    "answer": "his mouth was opened immediately, his tongue loosed and he spake and praised God 1:64"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom, \"fear not believe only and she shall be made whole\"",
    "answer": "Jesus to Jairus 8:50"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jesus came to Jairus' house, He suffered no man to go in save these individuals",
    "answer": "Peter, James, John, father and mother of the maiden 8:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What came upon all them that dwelt round about Zacharias and his wife",
    "answer": "fear 1:65"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and all these sayings were -- abroad throughout the hill country of Judaea",
    "answer": "noised 1:65"
  },
  {
    "stem": "weep not she is not dead but --",
    "answer": "sleepeth 8:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After hearing of the circumstances surrounding John's birth the bible states all that heard laid them up in their hearts what two things did they say",
    "answer": "what manner of child shall this be, and the hand of the Lord is with him 1:66"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Knowing the damsel was dead what did the people do to Jesus when He said she was not dead but sleepeth",
    "answer": "laughed Him to scorn 8:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Zacharias prophecy he stated the Lord hath visited and -- His people",
    "answer": "redeemed 1:68"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by what did Jesus take the maid",
    "answer": "by the hand 8:54"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Zacharias say the Lord hath raised up in the house of His servant David",
    "answer": "an horn of salvation 1:69"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when Jesus said, \"maid arise\"",
    "answer": "her spirit came again, and she arose straightway 8:55"
  },
  {
    "stem": "By who's mouth did Zacharias say the Lord has spoken since the world began",
    "answer": "mouth of His holy prophets 1:70"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jesus command be given the damsel",
    "answer": "meat 8:55"
  },
  {
    "stem": "That we should be saved from our -- and from the hand of all that -- us",
    "answer": "enemies, hate 1:71"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the parents reaction to the raising of the damsel",
    "answer": "they were astonished 8:56"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To perform the mercy promised to our fathers and to remember His holy --",
    "answer": "covenant 1:72"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what charge did Jesus give to the parents of the damsel",
    "answer": "that they should tell no man what was done 8:56"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The oath which He sware to our father --",
    "answer": "Abraham 1:73"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Zacharias' prophecy being delivered out of the hand of our enemies how might we serve God",
    "answer": "without fear, in holiness and righteousness 1:74-75"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And thou child shall be called the prophet of the -- for thou shall go before the face of the Lord to prepare His --",
    "answer": "Highest, ways 1:76"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To give knowledge of -- unto His people by the remission of their sins",
    "answer": "salvation 1:77"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Through the tender mercy of our God whereby the -- from on high hath visited us",
    "answer": "dayspring 1:78"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To give light to them that sit in -- and in the shadow of --to guide our -- in the way of peace",
    "answer": "darkness, death, feet 1:79"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the child grew and waxed strong in the --",
    "answer": "spirit 1:80"
  },
  {
    "stem": "John was in this place until the day of his showing unto Israel",
    "answer": "deserts 1:80"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides being without form, how was the earth in the beginning - ",
    "answer": "void 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Isaac go unto Abimelech king of the Philistines in Gerar - ",
    "answer": "because of a famine in the land 26:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In a vision the word of the Lord came to Abram saying I am thy shield and thy exceeding great -- - ",
    "answer": "reward 15:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the butler and baker offend - ",
    "answer": "their lord the king of Egypt 40:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Thus the -- and the -- were finished and all the host of them - ",
    "answer": "heaven, earth 2:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what day did Isaac tell Esau he did not know - ",
    "answer": "the day of his death 27:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many did Keturah bare Abraham - ",
    "answer": "six 25:1-2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Joseph fell upon his father's face, and wept upon him and -- him - ",
    "answer": "kissed 50:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Under what did Abraham make his servant to put his hand and swear - ",
    "answer": "his thigh 24:2,3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob told his sons to gather together and he will tell them what will befall them in these days - ",
    "answer": "last days 49:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when it was told Joseph his father was sick, who did he take when he went to see him - ",
    "answer": "his two sons Manasseh and Ephraim 48:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Sarah when she died - ",
    "answer": "127 years old 23:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what place did the Lord command Abraham to go and offer up his son - ",
    "answer": "in the land of Moriah (upon one of the mountains) 22:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many of his brethren did Joseph present unto Pharaoh - ",
    "answer": "five 47:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham called the name of the son which Sarah bare unto him - ",
    "answer": "Isaac 21:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In journeying to Egypt, Israel came to this place and offered sacrifices unto the God of his father Isaac - ",
    "answer": "Beer-sheba 46:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After the destruction of Sodom and Gomorrah, Abraham journeyed toward the --- country - ",
    "answer": "South 20:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"cause every man to go out from me\" - ",
    "answer": "Joseph 45:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where was Abraham sitting when the Lord appeared to him in the plains of Mamre in the heat of the day - ",
    "answer": "tent door 18:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"the man did solemnly protest us saying, ye shall not see my face except your brother be with you\" - ",
    "answer": "Judah 43:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Abram when the Lord appeared to him and said \"I am God almighty walk before me and be thou perfect\" - ",
    "answer": "99, 17:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob heard this was in Egypt - ",
    "answer": "corn 42:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "At the end of what time frame did Pharaoh dream - ",
    "answer": "two full years 41:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Hagar's relationship to Sarai - ",
    "answer": "she was her handmaid 16:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What time did the two angels come to Sodom - ",
    "answer": "even 19:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with how much food did Joseph command his steward to fill every man's sack - ",
    "answer": "as much as they can carry 44:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the king of Shinar - ",
    "answer": "Amraphel 14:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was Potiphar - ",
    "answer": "an officer of Pharaoh, captain of the guard 39:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the Lord said unto Noah, come thou and all thy --into the ark, for thee have I seen -- before me in this generation - ",
    "answer": "house, righteous 7:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Jacob call the place where he said, this is God's host - ",
    "answer": "Mahanaim 32:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "compared to any beast of the field the serpent was more this than any other - ",
    "answer": "subtil 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Isaac charged his son to go to this place to the house of Bethuel - ",
    "answer": "Padanaram 28:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Abram left Egypt to which direction did he go - ",
    "answer": "south 13:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Judah went down from his brethren and turned and turned in to a certain Adullamite whose name was - ",
    "answer": "Hirah 38:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "This is the book of the -- of Adam - ",
    "answer": "generations 5:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did Rachel envy when she saw she bare Jacob no children - ",
    "answer": "her sister 30:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And it came to pass when men began to -- on the face of the earth and -- were born unto them - ",
    "answer": "multiply, daughters 6:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"Jacob hath taken away all that was our father's and of that which was our father's hath he gotten all this glory\" - ",
    "answer": "Laban's sons 31:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Eve say when she had conceived and bare Cain - ",
    "answer": "I have gotten a man from the Lord 4:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob encountered a well when he came to land of the people of the east, what was on the mouth of the well - ",
    "answer": "a great stone 29:1,2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to the waters when God made a wind to pass over the earth - ",
    "answer": "the waters asswaged 8:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jacob place the handmaids and their children - ",
    "answer": "foremost 33:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God blessed Noah and his sons and said unto them be -- and -- and -- the earth - ",
    "answer": "fruitful, multiply, replenish 9:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Dinah go out to see - ",
    "answer": "the daughters of the land 34:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons did Japheth have - ",
    "answer": "seven 10:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God told Jacob to arise and go to this place and dwell there and make an altar - ",
    "answer": "Bethel 35:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the whole earth was of one language and one -- - ",
    "answer": "speech 11:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many wives did Esau have - ",
    "answer": "three"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Now the Lord said unto Abraham get thee out of thy -- and from thy -- and from thy father's -- unto a land that I will show thee - ",
    "answer": "country, kindred, house 12:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Joseph when he was feeding the flock with his brethren - ",
    "answer": "seventeen 37:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the king of Ellasar - ",
    "answer": "Arioch 14:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The -- was with Joseph and he was a prosperous man - ",
    "answer": "Lord 39:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the sons Keturah bare to Abraham - ",
    "answer": "Zimran, Jokshan, Medan, Midian, Ishbak, Shuah 25:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did Joseph command to embalm his father - ",
    "answer": "his servants the physicians 50:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From among whom did Abraham not want his servant to take a wife for his son - ",
    "answer": "Canaanites 24:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To which son of Jacob were these words directed, unstable as water thou shall not excel - ",
    "answer": "Reuben 49:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When it was told that Joseph was coming to see him, Israel straightened himself and did this - ",
    "answer": "sat upon the bed 48:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Sarah die - ",
    "answer": "Kirjatharba 23:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For what kind of offering was Abraham commanded to offer his son - ",
    "answer": "burnt offering 22:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph's brethren tell Pharaoh was their occupation - ",
    "answer": "shepherds 47:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the Lord -- Sarah as He had said, and the Lord did unto Sarah as He had -- - ",
    "answer": "visited, spoken 21:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did God tell Jacob He would make of him in Egypt - ",
    "answer": "a great nation 46:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham dwelt between Kadesh and Shur and sojourned in -- - ",
    "answer": "Gerar 20:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who stood with Joseph while he made himself known to his brethren - ",
    "answer": "no man 45:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham do when he saw the three men - ",
    "answer": "he ran to meet them and bowed himself toward the ground 18:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The man asked us straitly of our state and of our kindred saying is your father yet alive? have ye another brother and we told him according to the -- of these words. - ",
    "answer": "tenor 43:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because he would make him a father of many nations, what did God change Abram's name to - ",
    "answer": "Abraham 17:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The first time how many of Joseph's brethren went down to Egypt to buy corn - ",
    "answer": "ten 42:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Pharaoh's dream he stood by this location - ",
    "answer": "the river 41:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Hagar's nationality - ",
    "answer": "Egyptian 16:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the steward of Abram's house and where was he from - ",
    "answer": "Eliezer, Damascus 15:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "against which two of his officers was Pharaoh wroth - ",
    "answer": "the chief of the butlers, chief of the bakers 40:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where was Lot when the two angels came to Sodom - ",
    "answer": "gate of Sodom 19:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Joseph command the steward to put every man's money - ",
    "answer": "in his sack's mouth 44:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What three things was Abram rich in - ",
    "answer": "cattle, silver and gold 13:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons did Shuah's daughter bear Judah - ",
    "answer": "three"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what group of beasts were to be taken by sevens - ",
    "answer": "the clean 7:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To where did Jacob send messengers to Esau - ",
    "answer": "unto the land of Seir the country of Edom 32:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who's speaking \"yeah hath God said, ye shall not eat of every tree of the Garden\" - ",
    "answer": "the serpent 3:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From whose daughters did Isaac not want Jacob to take a wife - ",
    "answer": "daughters of Canaan 28:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abel was a keeper of the sheep, but Cain was this - ",
    "answer": "a tiller of the ground 4:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many flocks of sheep was lying by the well - ",
    "answer": "three 29:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Male and female created He them and blessed them and called their name -- in the day they were created. - ",
    "answer": "Adam 5:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"give me children, or else I die\" - ",
    "answer": "Rachel to Jacob 30:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who saw the daughters of men that they were fair - ",
    "answer": "sons of God 6:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of Laban was not towards Jacob as before - ",
    "answer": "his countenance 31:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "On what day did God end His work - ",
    "answer": "seventh 2:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The bible say Isaac's eyes were in this state that he could not see - ",
    "answer": "dim 27:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where upon the deep was the darkness - ",
    "answer": "on the face 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In a dream the Lord told Isaac not to go to this place - ",
    "answer": "Egypt 26:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As they journeyed from the east, where did they find a plain and what did they do there - ",
    "answer": "in the land of Shinar, dwelt there 11:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the wives of Esau - ",
    "answer": "Adah, Aholibamah, Bashemath 36:2,3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The fountains also of the deep and the windows of heaven were -- and the rain from heaven was -- - ",
    "answer": "stopped, restrained 8:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jacob place after the handmaids and their children - ",
    "answer": "Leah and her children 33:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of Abram did the Lord say He will make great - ",
    "answer": "his name 12:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the sons of Bilhah and Zilpah did Joseph bring unto his father - ",
    "answer": "their evil report 37:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the sons of Japheth - ",
    "answer": "Gomer, Magog, Madai, Javan, Tubal, Meshech and Tiras 10:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Before going to Bethel what did Jacob command his household to do - ",
    "answer": "put away the strange gods, be clean and change your garments 35:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God told Noah and his sons the fear and -- of them will be upon every beast of the field, every fowl of the air and upon all the fishes of the sea - ",
    "answer": "dread 9:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what nationality was Shechem - ",
    "answer": "Hivite 34:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the king of Elam - ",
    "answer": "Chedorlaomer 14:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph's master saw that the Lord was with him, and He made all that he did to -- in his hand - ",
    "answer": "prosper 39:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many days are fulfilled for those who are embalmed - ",
    "answer": "forty 50:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To whom did Abraham give all that he had - ",
    "answer": "Isaac 25:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham told the servant if the woman is not willing to follow him, them he shall be clear from this - ",
    "answer": "the oath 24:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Reuben thou art my -- my might and the beginning of my -- the -- of dignity and the -- of power - ",
    "answer": "firstborn, strength, excellency, excellency 49:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is Kirjatharba also known as - ",
    "answer": "Hebron 23:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where in the land of Canaan did Jacob tell Joseph God Almighty appeared to him - ",
    "answer": "Luz 48:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Isaac when Abraham circumcised him - ",
    "answer": "eight days old 21:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Upon what body part of Jacob did God tell him Joseph will put his hands - ",
    "answer": "his eyes 46:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the king of Gerar - ",
    "answer": "Abimelech 20:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who heard as Joseph wept aloud - ",
    "answer": "the Egyptians and Pharaoh 45:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Lot greet the two angels - ",
    "answer": "bowed himself with his face toward the ground 19:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph command his steward to put in the sack's mouth of the youngest - ",
    "answer": "his silver cup and corn money 44:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which son promised Israel to be surety for the lad - ",
    "answer": "Judah 43:8,9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Under what did Abraham tell the three men to rest - ",
    "answer": "a tree 18:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of rulers did the Lord say would come from Abraham - ",
    "answer": "kings 17:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did not Jacob send Benjamin the first time with his brethren - ",
    "answer": "lest peradventure mischief befall him 42:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Sarai say the Lord had restrained her from doing - ",
    "answer": "bearing 16:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From where did the kines come - ",
    "answer": "out of the river 41:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord told Abram, Eliezer will not be his heir but one that come forth from his own -- shall be his heir - ",
    "answer": "bowels 15:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "being wroth with them, where did Pharaoh put his two officers - ",
    "answer": "in prison 40:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When going to offer his son how many young men did Abraham take with him - ",
    "answer": "two 22:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph's brethren tell Pharaoh they don't have for their flock - ",
    "answer": "pasture 47:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of nation did the Lord tell Abram He would make of him - ",
    "answer": "a great nation 12:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Israel love Joseph more than all his brethren - ",
    "answer": "because he was the son of his old age 37:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Lot had flocks, herds and -- - ",
    "answer": "tents 13:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name Judah's firstborn - ",
    "answer": "Er 38:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Adam when he begat Seth - ",
    "answer": "one hundred and thirty years 5:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Jacob's anger was -- against Rachel, and he said am I in God's -- who hath withheld from thee the -- of the womb - ",
    "answer": "kindled, stead, fruit 30:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did they use for stone? - ",
    "answer": "brick 11:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the father of Adah, Esau's wife - ",
    "answer": "Elon the Hittite 36:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From what did God rest on the seventh day - ",
    "answer": "from all His work which He had made 2:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides weapons what else did Isaac tell Esau to take with him to the field to obtain venison - ",
    "answer": "quiver and bow 27:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides not eating of the tree in the midst of the garden what else did the woman tell the serpent God commanded them not to do with the tree - ",
    "answer": "touch it 3:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From among whom did Isaac instruct Jacob to take a wife - ",
    "answer": "from the daughters of Laban 28:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Cain bring as an offering to the Lord - ",
    "answer": "fruit of the ground 4:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob do after rolling the stone away from the well's mouth - ",
    "answer": "watered the flock of Laban his mother's brother 29:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who moved upon the face of the waters - ",
    "answer": "the Spirit of God 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because that Abraham obeyed my voice kept my charge ,-- statutes and my -- - ",
    "answer": "commandments, laws 26:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they took them -- of all which they chose - ",
    "answer": "wives 6:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many times had Laban changed Jacob's wages - ",
    "answer": "ten times 31:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and of the beast that are not clean by two the -- and his -- - ",
    "answer": "male, female 7:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In his message to Esau who did Jacob say he has sojourned with - ",
    "answer": "Laban 32:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the waters were abated after the end of how many days - ",
    "answer": "one hundred and fifty 8:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was Rachel and Joseph placed by Jacob - ",
    "answer": "hindermost 33:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Every moving thing that liveth shall be -- for you even as the -- herb have I given you all things - ",
    "answer": "meat, green 9:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what nobility was Shechem - ",
    "answer": "a prince 34:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob do with the strange gods and earrings given to him by his household - ",
    "answer": "hid them under the oak which was by "
  },
  {
    "stem": "Shechem 35:4",
    "answer": ""
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons did Gomer have - ",
    "answer": "three 10:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the king of nations - ",
    "answer": "Tidal 14:1"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what position did Potiphar place Joseph in his house - ",
    "answer": "overseer 39:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham give to the sons of the concubines - ",
    "answer": "gifts 25:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did the Egyptians mourn for Jacob - ",
    "answer": "threescore and ten day (70 days) 50:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many camels did Abraham's servant take on the journey to Mesopotamia - ",
    "answer": "ten 24:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why was it said of Reuben unstable as water thou shall not excel - ",
    "answer": "because he went up to his father's bed and defiled it 49:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "whose sons did Abraham ask for burying place - ",
    "answer": "son of Heth 23:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob took Ephraim and Manasseh as his own sons which sons of his were replaced in doing this - ",
    "answer": "Reuben and Simeon 48:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham rose early in the morning and -- his ass - ",
    "answer": "saddled 22:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did Pharaoh give permission for Joseph's brethren and father to dwell - ",
    "answer": "in Goshen 47:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "His sons and his --, sons with him his daughters and his son's -- - ",
    "answer": "son's, daughters 46:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Abraham when Isaac was born - ",
    "answer": "100 years 21:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Abraham said of Sarah his wife she is my -- - ",
    "answer": "sister 20:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Joseph declared, I am Joseph, doth my father yet live, what was his brethren's response and why - ",
    "answer": "they could not answer him, for they were troubled at his presence 45:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For what purpose did Abraham tell the men a little water should be fetched - ",
    "answer": "to wash their feet 18:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Israel tell his sons to take as a present for the man - ",
    "answer": "best of the fruits of the land, a little balm, a little honey, spices, myrrh, nuts and almonds 43:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord told Abraham He will give the land to him and his seed for an everlasting -- - ",
    "answer": "possession 17:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was governor over the land of Egypt - ",
    "answer": "Joseph 42:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For what purpose did Sarai tell Abram to go in unto her maid Hagar - ",
    "answer": "to obtain children by her 16:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Give the description of the first set of kine that came out of the river - ",
    "answer": "seven well favored and fat fleshed 41:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Like what number did the Lord tell Abram his seed shall be - ",
    "answer": "the stars 15:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did the two officers of Pharaoh continue in ward - ",
    "answer": "a season 40:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The men initially refused Lot's invitation stating they would abide in this place all night - ",
    "answer": "the street 19:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when were the men sent away - ",
    "answer": "as soon as the morning was light 44:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why could not Lot and Abram dwell together - ",
    "answer": "their substance was great 13:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Second son born to Judah - ",
    "answer": "Onan 38:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord say will not always strive with man - ",
    "answer": "His Spirit 6:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when Laban told Jacob the speckled shall be thy wages - ",
    "answer": "then all the cattle bare speckled 31:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I will bless thee and make thy name great and thou shall be a -- - ",
    "answer": "blessing 12:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Israel make for Joseph - ",
    "answer": "a coat of many colors 37:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"ye shall not surely die\" - ",
    "answer": "serpent to the woman 3:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "seeing that his wives did not please his father, who's daughter did Esau go and marry what is her name - ",
    "answer": "Mahalath daughter of Ishmael 28:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Abel's offering to the Lord - ",
    "answer": "firstling of the flock and of the fat 4:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Rachel run and tell when Jacob told her he was Rebekah's son - ",
    "answer": "her father 29:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Adam begat a son in his own -- after his -- - ",
    "answer": "likeness, image 5:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did Rachel give to Jacob - ",
    "answer": "Bilhah 30:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In addition to blessing the seventh day, what else did God to it - ",
    "answer": "sanctified it 2:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what Isaac tell Esau to make for him - ",
    "answer": "savoury meat 27:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For how long did the Lord say He would cause it to rain upon the earth - ",
    "answer": "forty days and forty nights 7:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The messengers returned to tell Jacob, Esau is coming to meet him with this many men - ",
    "answer": "four hundred 32:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The waters were returned from off the earth -- - ",
    "answer": "continually 8:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob did this seven times until he came near to his brother - ",
    "answer": "bowed himself to the ground 33:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "This was considered the life of the flesh and not to be eaten - ",
    "answer": "blood 9:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In laying with Dinah what did Shechem do to her - ",
    "answer": "defiled her 34:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did not the cities round abut them pursue after the sons of Jacob as they journeyed - ",
    "answer": "the terror of God was upon them 35:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the three sons of Gomer - ",
    "answer": "Ashkenaz, Riphath, Togarmah 10:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was used for morter - ",
    "answer": "slime 11:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the father of Aholibamah - ",
    "answer": "Anah 36:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Repeat Gen 1:1 - ",
    "answer": "In the beginning God created the heaven and the earth"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Isaac tell the men of Gerar was his relationship with Rebekah - ",
    "answer": "she was his sister 26:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Lot do to cause the men to come to his house - ",
    "answer": "he pressed upon them greatly 19:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what distance had the men gone when Joseph sent his steward after them - ",
    "answer": "when they were gone out of the city not yet far off 44:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he believed in the Lord, and he counted it to him for -- - ",
    "answer": "righteousness 15:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the two officers feel the morning after their dreams - ",
    "answer": "sad 40:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long had Abram dwelt in the land of Canaan when Sarai gave Hagar to him to be his wife - ",
    "answer": "ten years 16:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the well favored kine feed - ",
    "answer": "in the meadow 41:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was it that sold to all the people of the land - ",
    "answer": "Joseph 42:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was the token of the covenant between God, Abraham and his seed - ",
    "answer": "circumcising the flesh of their foreskin 17:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham ask Sarah to make for the three men - ",
    "answer": "three measures of fine meal knead it and make cakes 18:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much money did Israel tell his sons to take the second time - ",
    "answer": "double the money and the money that was brought again in the mouth of their sacks 43:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham clave for the burnt offering - ",
    "answer": "the wood 22:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"if thou knowest any men of activity among them, then make them rulers over my cattle\" - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh 47:5-6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did God speak to Abimelech - ",
    "answer": "in a dream 20:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph's brethren do when he said, come near I pray you - ",
    "answer": "they came near 45:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Abraham do the same day Isaac was weaned - ",
    "answer": "made a great feast 21:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the mother of Reuben, Simeon, Levi, Judah, Issachar, Zebulun and Dinah - ",
    "answer": "Leah 46:9-15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The sons of Heth referred to Abraham as a mighty -- among them. - ",
    "answer": "prince 23:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Jacob came from Padan, Rachel died a little way from this place - ",
    "answer": "Ephrath 48:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham's servant made his camels to kneel down by the well of water at the time of evening when women did this - ",
    "answer": "go out to draw water 24:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob say was in the habitation of Simeon and Levi - ",
    "answer": "instruments of cruelty 49:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "T or F, Abraham allowed the other sons to dwell with Isaac after he gave them gifts - ",
    "answer": "false 25:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who went up with Joseph to bury his father - ",
    "answer": "all the servants of Pharaoh, the elders of his house, and all the elders of the land of Egypt , all the house of Joseph and his brethren and his father's house 50:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the king of Sodom - ",
    "answer": "Bera 14:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did the Lord bless the Egyptian's house - ",
    "answer": "for Joseph's sake 39:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was there between the herdmen of Abram's cattle and the herdmen of Lot's cattle - ",
    "answer": "strife 13:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was Judah when Shuah's daughter bear him Shelah - ",
    "answer": "Chezib 38:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I will -- them that -- thee, and -- him that -- thee and in thee shall all -- of the earth be blessed - ",
    "answer": "bless, bless, curse, curseth, families 12:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what resulted when Joseph's brethren saw that their father loved him more than all his brethren - ",
    "answer": "they hated him and could not speak peaceably unto him 36:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many years after he had begotten Seth did Adam live - ",
    "answer": "eight hundred 5:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the first son Bilhah bare to Jacob - ",
    "answer": "Dan 30:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they said go to, let us build a city and --- - ",
    "answer": "tower 11:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the father of Bashemath - ",
    "answer": "Ishamael 36:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the beginning what condition was the earth in - ",
    "answer": "without form and void 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Isaac was afraid the men would kill him for Rebekah his wife for she had this appearance - ",
    "answer": "fair to look upon 26:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did God bless the seventh day and sanctified it - ",
    "answer": "because He had rested from all His work which He created and made 2:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Isaac intend to do to Esau after eating his savoury meat - ",
    "answer": "bless him 27:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV God had said , ye shall not eat of it neither shall ye touch it .. - ",
    "answer": "lest ye die 3:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob use for a pillow - ",
    "answer": "stones 28:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the Lord had -- unto Abel and to his offering - ",
    "answer": "respect 4:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Laban do when he heard the tidings of Jacob his sister's son - ",
    "answer": "ran to meet him, embraced him, kissed him and brought him to his house 29:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when Laban told Jacob the ringstraked shall be thy hire - ",
    "answer": "then bare all the cattle ringstraked 31:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for that he (man) also is flesh the Lord said his days shall be this - ",
    "answer": "one hundred and twenty years 6:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many days after entering the ark were the waters of the flood upon the earth - ",
    "answer": "seven 7:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Jacob's reaction when he heard Esau was coming with four hundred men - ",
    "answer": "greatly afraid and distressed 32:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Upon what mountains did the ark rest - ",
    "answer": "Ararat 8:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Esau greet Jacob? - ",
    "answer": "ran to meet him, embraced him, fell on his neck, and kissed him and wept 33:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "at who's hand did God say he will require the life of man - ",
    "answer": "every man's brother 9:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of Shechem clave unto Dinah - ",
    "answer": "his soul 34:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons did Javan have - ",
    "answer": "five 10:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is another name for Bethel - ",
    "answer": "Luz 35:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Lot make for the men in his home - ",
    "answer": "a feast 19:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph commanded his steward to tell the men, wherefore have ye rewarded -- for -- - ",
    "answer": "evil, good 44:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom, \"wherefore look ye so sadly today\" - ",
    "answer": "Joseph to the two officers 40:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I am the Lord thy God which brought thee out of -- of the Chaldees - ",
    "answer": "Ur 15:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Hagar do when she saw she had conceived - ",
    "answer": "her mistress was despised in her eyes 16:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the second set of kine that came out of the river - ",
    "answer": "seven ill favored and lean fleshed 41:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "He that is -- days old shall be circumcised among you - ",
    "answer": "eight 17:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When the sons of Israel came to buy corn, how did they greet Joseph - ",
    "answer": "bowed themselves down before him with their faces to the earth 42:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Abraham take from his herd for the three men - ",
    "answer": "a calf tender and good 18:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Israel say peradventure the money brought again in the mouth of their sacks was - ",
    "answer": "an oversight 43:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Abraham when he died - ",
    "answer": "175, 25:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who/what was left in the land of Goshen when Jacob was buried - ",
    "answer": "their little ones, flocks and herds 50:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"behold thou art but a dead man, for the woman which thou has taken, for she is a man's wife\" - ",
    "answer": "God to Abimelech 20:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I am Joseph your brother whom ye sold into -- - ",
    "answer": "Egypt 45:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Sarah see the son of Hagar doing - ",
    "answer": "mocking 21:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the place where Leah bare six sons and a daughter to Jacob - ",
    "answer": "Padan-aram 46:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Being commanded to go and sacrifice his son, what day did Abraham lift up his eyes and saw the place a far off - ",
    "answer": "third day 22:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob do to Pharaoh - ",
    "answer": "blessed him 47:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham asked the sons of Heth to intreat this person so he can purchase from him the cave of Machpelah - ",
    "answer": "Ephron son of Zohar 23:8-9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jacob bury Rachel - ",
    "answer": "in the way of Ephrath 48:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what sign did the servant pray for in the woman the Lord choose for Isaac - ",
    "answer": "she would say drink and I will give thy camels drink also 24:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "o my soul come not thou in their -- unto their assembly mine -- be not thou united - ",
    "answer": "secret, honor 49:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the king of Gomorrah - ",
    "answer": "Birsha 14:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the blessing of the Lord was upon all that Potiphar had in the house as well as this place - ",
    "answer": "in the field 39:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the Canaanite and the -- dwelt then in the land - ",
    "answer": "Perizzite 13:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the wife Judah took for Er his firstborn - ",
    "answer": "Tamar 38:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Abram when he departed out of Haran - ",
    "answer": "75 years old 12:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what resulted when Joseph told his brethren the dream - ",
    "answer": "they hated him yet the more 36:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Adam when he died - ",
    "answer": "nine hundred and thirty years 5:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To which son is this reference, God hath judged me and hath also heard my voice, and hath given me therefore a son - ",
    "answer": "Dan 30:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The people decided to build a city and tower who's top may reach this place - ",
    "answer": "heaven 11:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Bashemath was sister to whom - ",
    "answer": "Nebajoth 36:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the Spirit of God moved upon the -- of the -- - ",
    "answer": "face, waters 1:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Abimelech the king looked out a window what did he see Isaac doing - ",
    "answer": "sporting with Rebekah his wife 26:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "These are the -- of the heavens and of the earth when they were created - ",
    "answer": "generations 2:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who heard when Isaac spoke to Esau - ",
    "answer": "Rebekah 27:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To where did the top of that ladder in Jacob's dream reach - ",
    "answer": "heaven 28:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The serpent told the woman God knows that in the day they eat of the tree, this will be opened, ye will be like these and ye will know this - ",
    "answer": "eyes, gods, good and evil 3:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but to Cain and his offering He had -- - ",
    "answer": "not respect 4:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Jacob abide with Laban when he proposed to pay him wages for serving him - ",
    "answer": "space of a month 29:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "They were -- in the earth in those days - ",
    "answer": "giants 6:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was the description of the rams that leaped upon the cattle in Jacob's dream - ",
    "answer": "ringstraked, speckled and grisled 31:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Noah when the flood of waters came upon the earth - ",
    "answer": "six hundred years old 7:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Into how many bands did Jacob divide the people, flock, herd and camels - ",
    "answer": "two 32:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what day and month did the ark rest upon the mountains of Ararat - ",
    "answer": "17th day of the 7th month 8:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Jacob's wives and children greet Esau - ",
    "answer": "bowed themselves 33:6-7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, whoso sheddeth man's blood, by man shall his blood be shed... - ",
    "answer": "for in the image of God made He man 9:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Shechem feel towards Dinah - ",
    "answer": "he loved her 34:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Jacob call the place El-behtel - ",
    "answer": "because there God appeared to him when he fled from the face of his brother 35:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the five sons of Javan - ",
    "answer": "Elishah, Tarshish, Kittim, and Dodanim 10:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of bread did the men eat in Lot's house - ",
    "answer": "unleavened 19:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what two things was the steward told to tell the men his lord does with the cup - ",
    "answer": "drinketh, divineth 44:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"Lord God, whereby shall I know that I shall inherit it\" - ",
    "answer": "Abram 15:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the officers tell Joseph was the cause of their sadness - ",
    "answer": "they dreamed a dream and there is no interpreter 40:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Hagar do when Sarai dealt hardly with her - ",
    "answer": "she fled from her face 16:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The ill favored kine stood by the other kine at this location - ",
    "answer": "upon the brink of the rive 41:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What would happen to the man child that is not circumcised - ",
    "answer": "shall be cut off from his people 17:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Even though Joseph knew his brethren, how did he make himself unto them and how did the speak unto them - ",
    "answer": "made himself strange to them, spake roughly unto them 42:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Abraham give the calf to - ",
    "answer": "a young man 18:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If I'm -- of my children I am -- - ",
    "answer": "bereaved, bereaved 43:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who buried Abraham - ",
    "answer": "Isaac and Ishmael 25:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by whose threshingfloor did they mourn with a great and very sore lamentation - ",
    "answer": "Atad 50:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"Lord wilt thou slay also a righteous nation?\" - ",
    "answer": "Abimelech 20:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Now therefore be not -- nor angry with yourselves that ye -- me hither, for God did send me before you to -- life. - ",
    "answer": "grieved, sold, preserve 45:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"cast out this bondwoman and her son, for the son of this bondwoman shall not be heir with my son, even with Isaac\" - ",
    "answer": "Sarah to Abraham 21:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "all the souls of Jacob's which came through Leah were how many - ",
    "answer": "thirty three 46:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham told the young men to abide with the ass and he and the lad will go yonder and do this, and come again - ",
    "answer": "worship 22:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The days of the years of my -- are -- years few and -- have the days of the years of my life been and have not attained unto the days of the years of the life of my -- in the days of their pilgrimage - ",
    "answer": "pilgrimage, hundred and thirty years, evil, fathers 47:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where in Ephron's field was the cave of Machpelah located - ",
    "answer": "at the end 23:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ephrath is also known by this name - ",
    "answer": "Bethlehem 48:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Before Abraham's servant had finished speaking, Rebekah came out with this upon her shoulder - ",
    "answer": "a pitcher 24:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Simeon and Levi do in their anger - ",
    "answer": "slew a man 49:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was king of Admah - ",
    "answer": "Shinab 14:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Potiphar left all that he had in Joseph's hand, he knew not ought he had save .. - ",
    "answer": "the bread which he did eat 39:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who to whom \"let there be no strife I pray thee between me and thee, and between my herdmen and thy herdmen for we are brethren\" - ",
    "answer": "Abram to Lot 13:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who slew Er and why - ",
    "answer": "the Lord, he was wicked 38:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was Abram's wife - ",
    "answer": "Sarai 12:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Joseph's dream what were they doing in the field - ",
    "answer": "binding sheaves 37:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Seth when he begat Enos - ",
    "answer": "one hundred and five years old 5:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To which son is this referring \"with great wrestling have I wrestled with my sister and have prevailed\" - ",
    "answer": "Naphtali 30:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The people said let us make a name lest this happens - ",
    "answer": "they be scattered abroad upon the face of the earth 11:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Adah bare to Esau - ",
    "answer": "Eliphaz 36:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abimilech tell Isaac should have been brought upon them if one of thee people had lain with his wife - ",
    "answer": "guiltiness 26:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, and God said let there be light - ",
    "answer": "and there was light 1:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God did not cause it to rain upon the earth, instead this watered the ground - ",
    "answer": "a mist from the earth 2:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Esau go to hunt for venison - ",
    "answer": "the field 27:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And when the woman saw that the tree was good for -- and it was -- to the eyes and a tree to be -- to make one wise she took of the fruit thereof and did -- - ",
    "answer": "food,pleasant, desired, eat 3:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was ascending and descending on the ladder in Jacob's dream - ",
    "answer": "angels of God 28:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The bible states Cain was very wroth and his -- fell - ",
    "answer": "countenance 4:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of Laban's elder daughter - ",
    "answer": "Leah 29:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When the sons of God came in unto the daughters of men they bare them children, what did the children become - ",
    "answer": "mighty men which were of old, men of renown 6:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"is there yet any portion or inheritance for us in our father's house?\" - ",
    "answer": "Leah and Rachel 31:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Give the day and month when the fountains of the deep were broken up and the windows of heaven were opened - ",
    "answer": "17th day , 2nd month 7:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In dividing into two band Jacob hoped if Esau come to the one company and smite it the other company which is left shall do this - ",
    "answer": "escape 32:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the response, what meanest thou by all this drove which I met? - ",
    "answer": "these are to find grace in the sight of my lord 33:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As the waters decreased continually what was seen on the first day of the tenth month - ",
    "answer": "tops of the mountains 8:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God established a covenant with Noah and his sons that all flesh shall not be cut off anymore by waters of the flood neither this event - ",
    "answer": "neither shall there be any flood to destroy the earth 9:8-11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Shechem speak unto the damsel - ",
    "answer": "kindly 34:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "By these were the -- of the gentiles divided in their lands, everyone after his --, after their families in their -- - ",
    "answer": "isles, tongue, nations 10:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who died and was buried under and oak in Bethel - ",
    "answer": "Deborah, Rebekah's nurse 35:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the integrity of my heart and -- of my hands have I done this - ",
    "answer": "innocency 20:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For these -- years hath the famine been in the land, and there are -- years in the which there shall neither be -- nor -- - ",
    "answer": "two, five, earing, harvest 45:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The angel of the Lord found Hagar by a fountain of water in the wilderness, in the way to this place - ",
    "answer": "Shur 16:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the ill favored and lean fleshed kine do to the well favored and fat kine in Pharaoh's dream - ",
    "answer": "eat them 41:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Sarai's name changed to - ",
    "answer": "Sarah 17:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Joseph's brethren response when he asked, from whence come ye? - ",
    "answer": "from the land of Canaan to buy food 42:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker, \"after I am waxed old shall I have pleasure, my lord being old also\" - ",
    "answer": "Sarah 18:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph command the ruler of his house to do concerning his brothers when he saw Benjamin with them - ",
    "answer": "take them home, slay and make ready 43:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And before they lay down, the -- of the city even the men of Sodom -- the house round, both -- and -- and all the people from every -- - ",
    "answer": "men, compassed, old, young, quarter 19:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how then should we steal out of thy lord's house -- or -- - ",
    "answer": "silver, gold 44:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was king of Zeboim - ",
    "answer": "Shemeber 14:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and Joseph was a goodly person and well -- - ",
    "answer": "favoured 39:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the thing was very -- in Abraham's sight because of his son - ",
    "answer": "grievous 21:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons did Reuben have - ",
    "answer": "four 46:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham took the wood of the burnt offering and laid it on Isaac what did Abraham take in his hand - ",
    "answer": "the fire and knife 22:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Genesis 47:11 name the land where Joseph gave his brethren possession - ",
    "answer": "in the land of Rameses"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Ephron's nationality - ",
    "answer": "Hittite 23:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What of Israel was dim for age - ",
    "answer": "his eyes 48:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How was Rebekah described - ",
    "answer": "fair to look upon a virgin 24:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what did Simeon and Levi digged down a wall - ",
    "answer": "in their self will 49:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was Abraham buried - ",
    "answer": "in the cave of Macpelah 25:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for how long did Joseph make a mourning for his father at Atad's threshingfloor - ",
    "answer": "seven days 50:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what animals did the Lord instruct Abram to take - ",
    "answer": "heifer, she goat, ram, turtledove and a young pigeon 15:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who's speaking \"do not interpretations belong to God\" - ",
    "answer": "Joseph 40:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Be specific, who did the woman give the fruit to after she ate of it according Gen3:6 - ",
    "answer": "her husband with her"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Leah saw she had left bearing, who did she give to Jacob - ",
    "answer": "Zilpah her maid 30:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Abram tell Lot he would do if Lot takes the left hand - ",
    "answer": "he will go to the right 13:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"go in unto thy brother's wife, and marry her and raise up seed to thy brother\" - ",
    "answer": "Judah to Onan 38:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As whom did Rachel and Leah say they are accounted by their father - ",
    "answer": "strangers 31:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God saw the wickedness of man was great in this place - ",
    "answer": "the earth 6:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Abram left Haran to what land did he go - ",
    "answer": "Canaan 12:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph's sheaf arose and stood upright, what did his brethren's sheaf do - ",
    "answer": "stood round about and made obeisance to Joseph's sheaf 37:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God saw the light, that it was -- - ",
    "answer": "good 1:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who stood above the ladder in Jacob's dream - ",
    "answer": "the Lord 28:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom, why art thou wroth and why is thy countenance fallen - ",
    "answer": "The Lord to Cain 4:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Leah was -- eyed, but Rachel was beautiful and well -- - ",
    "answer": "tender, favored 29:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Seth lived -- after he begat Enos - ",
    "answer": "eight hundred and seven years 5:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Abimelech charge his people concerning Isaac and his wife - ",
    "answer": "whosoever touch them shall be put to death 26:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from what was man formed - ",
    "answer": "the dust of the ground 2:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Rebekah tell Jacob to fetch from the flock - ",
    "answer": "two good kid of the goats 27:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What word describes how the Lord promised Jacob He would deal with him when he returns to his country and kindred - ",
    "answer": "well 32:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they went in unto Noah into the ark, two and two of all flesh, wherein is the -- of -- - ",
    "answer": "breath, life 7:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when did Noah open the windows of the ark - ",
    "answer": "at the end of forty days 8:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob told Esau he has seen his face as though he had seen the face of this person - ",
    "answer": "God 33:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "This is the -- of the covenant which I make between me and you and every living creature that is with you for -- generations - ",
    "answer": "token, perpetual 9:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"give me this damsel to wife\" - ",
    "answer": "Schechem to Hamor 34:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons did Ham have - ",
    "answer": "four 10:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of Deborah's burial place - ",
    "answer": "Allonbachuth 35:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who came down to see the city and tower which the children of men built - ",
    "answer": "the Lord 11:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Bashemath bare to Esau - ",
    "answer": "Reuel 36:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the king of Bela - ",
    "answer": "Zoar 14:2"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Potiphar's wife cast upon Joseph and what did she say to him - ",
    "answer": "her eyes, lie with me 39:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the weight of the golden earring the servant gave to Rebekah - ",
    "answer": "half a shekel 24:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "cursed be their anger for it was -- and their wrath for it was -- I will -- them in Jacob and -- them in Israel - ",
    "answer": "fierce, cruel, divide, scatter 49:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much did Abraham pay Ephron for the field - ",
    "answer": "four hundred shekels of silver 23:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Israel greet Joseph's sons - ",
    "answer": "kissed and embraced them 48:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, behold the fire and the wood ... - ",
    "answer": "but where is the lamb for a burnt offering 22:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph nourish his father and brethren with - ",
    "answer": "bread 47:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "With respect to Sarah asking Abraham to cast out the bondwoman and her son, what did the Lord tell Abraham to hearken to - ",
    "answer": "Sarah's voice 21:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the father of Er, Onan, Shelah, Pharez and Zerah - ",
    "answer": "Judah 46:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did God tell Abimelech to restore to Abraham - ",
    "answer": "his wife 20:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God sent me before you to preserve you a -- in the earth and to save your lives by a great deliverance - ",
    "answer": "posterity 45:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"where are the men which came in to thee this night? bring them out unto us that we may know them - ",
    "answer": "the men of Sodom to Lot 19:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the men propose should happen if the silver cup was found among them - ",
    "answer": "the person with whom it was found should die, and the rest would be the lord's bondmen 44:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham set before the men - ",
    "answer": "butter, milk and a calf which he had dressed 18:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what time did Joseph tell the ruler of the house the men will dine with him - ",
    "answer": "at noon 43:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then Abraham fell upon his face and -- and said in his heart shall a child be born unto him that is -- years old and shall Sarah that is -- years old bear - ",
    "answer": "laughed, hundred, ninety 17:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, and Joseph knew his brethren but they.. - ",
    "answer": "knew him not 42:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the angel address Hagar - ",
    "answer": "Hagar Sarai's maid 16:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to Pharaoh after the ill favored kine ate the fat kine - ",
    "answer": "he awoke 41:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was to be the heifer, she goat and ram Abram was commanded to take - ",
    "answer": "three years old 15:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which of the officers dreamed about a vine - ",
    "answer": "the chief butler 40:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was the firstborn of Ishmael - ",
    "answer": "Nebajoth 25:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the threshingfloor of Atad is beyond this place - ",
    "answer": "Jordan 50:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because Onan knew the seed would not be his what did he with it when he went in unto his brother's wife - ",
    "answer": "he spilled it on the ground 38:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, if thou depart to the right hand ... - ",
    "answer": "then I will go to the left 13:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "At what age did Seth die - ",
    "answer": "nine hundred and twelve 5:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Rachel and Leah say had sold them and devoured their money - ",
    "answer": "their father 31:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did Abram take with him to the land of Canaan - ",
    "answer": "Sarai, Lot, all the souls they had gotten in Haran 12:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for what purpose did Rebekah tell Jacob to fetch two good kid of the goats from the flock - ",
    "answer": "to make savoury meat for his father 27:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, And the Lord God formed man from the dust of the ground, and breathed into his nostrils the breath of life ... - ",
    "answer": "and man became a living soul 2:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob do with the stone which he had used for a pillow - ",
    "answer": "set it up for a pillar and poured oil upon the top of it 28:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the man and woman's eyes were opened what did they know - ",
    "answer": "they were naked 3:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many years did Jacob propose to serve for Rachel - ",
    "answer": "seven 29:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If thou doest well shall thou not be -- - ",
    "answer": "accepted 4:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Zilpah bare Jacob a son, and Leah said \"a troop cometh and she called his name --\" - ",
    "answer": "Gad 30:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much did Isaac receive in the land when he sowed - ",
    "answer": "a hundred fold 26:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God -- the light from the darkness - ",
    "answer": "divided 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "every imagination of the thought of man's heart was only this continually - ",
    "answer": "evil 6:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob told God he was not worthy of the least to these - ",
    "answer": "mercies and truth he has shown him 32:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the first creature Noah sent forth out of the ark - ",
    "answer": "a raven 8:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Aholibamah bare to Esau - ",
    "answer": "Jeush,Jaalam, Korah 36:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the token of the covenant between God and the earth - ",
    "answer": "bow in the cloud 9:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Jacob describe to Esau as tender - ",
    "answer": "the children 33:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the sons of Ham - ",
    "answer": "Cush, Mizraim, Phut and Canaan 10:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "shalt thou indeed -- over us, shalt thou indeed have -- over us - ",
    "answer": "reign, dominion 37:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord said the people are one, how many languages did they have - ",
    "answer": "one 11:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob call the name of the place where God spake with him - ",
    "answer": "Bethel 35:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who shut Noah in the ark - ",
    "answer": "the Lord 7:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Hamor the father of Shechem went out unto Jacob to -- with him - ",
    "answer": "commune 34:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and it ceased to be with Sarah after the -- of women - ",
    "answer": "manner 18:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph told Potiphar's wife the only the master has kept back from him was - ",
    "answer": "her, because she is his wife 39:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the pigeon Abram was commanded to take - ",
    "answer": "young 15:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the inhabitants of the land the Canaanites saw the mourning in the floor of Atad what did they say - ",
    "answer": "this is a grievous mourning to the Egyptians 50:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what two questions did the angel ask Hagar - ",
    "answer": "whence camest thou? and wither wilt thou go? 16:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To whom is this referring, thou art he whom thy brethren shall praise - ",
    "answer": "Judah 49:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many princes did the Lord say Ishmael will beget - ",
    "answer": "twelve 17:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Joseph took them both Ephraim in his -- hand towards Israel's -- hand, and Manasseh in his -- hand towards Israel's -- hand and brought them near unto him - ",
    "answer": "right, left, left, right 48:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Abraham's response when Isaac asked about the lamb for the burnt offering - ",
    "answer": "My son, God will provide Himself a lamb for a burnt offering 22:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Er and Onan die - ",
    "answer": "in the land of Canaan 46:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I pray you brethren do not so --- - ",
    "answer": "wickedly 19:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Ultimately who did Joseph say had sent him to Egypt - ",
    "answer": "God 45:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What kind of man did God tell Abimelech, Abraham was - ",
    "answer": "a prophet 20:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "he with whom it is found shall be my servant and ye shall be -- - ",
    "answer": "blameless 44:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In who did the Lord tell Abraham his seed shall be called - ",
    "answer": "Isaac 21:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph's brothers were afraid when they were brought to his house, for what reason did they suppose they were brought there - ",
    "answer": "for the money that was returned in their sacks the first time 43:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the servant give to Rebekah that was ten shekels weight of gold - ",
    "answer": "two bracelets 24:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph remember concerning his brethren - ",
    "answer": "the dreams which he dreamed of them 42:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who begat twelve princes - ",
    "answer": "Ishmael 25:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Pharaoh's second dream upon what did the first seven ears of corn come up - ",
    "answer": "upon one stalk 41:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the butler's dream how many branches were in the vine - ",
    "answer": "three 40:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, all these were joined together in the vale of Siddim which is the ... - ",
    "answer": "Salt sea 14:3"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abram passed through the place of Sichem unto this plain - ",
    "answer": "Moreh 12:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Joseph bring the money he gathered from the land of Egypt and Canaan - ",
    "answer": "into Pharaoh's house 47:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the place where Lot beheld was well watered every where - ",
    "answer": "the plain of Jordan 13:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they hated him the yet more for his dreams and for his -- - ",
    "answer": "words 37:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Enos was ninety when he begat a son, name the son - ",
    "answer": "Cainan 5:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Onan spill his seed on the ground - ",
    "answer": "lest that he should give seed to his brother 38:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": ".. and now nothing will be -- from them what they have -- to do - ",
    "answer": "restrained, imagined 11:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Zilpah bare Jacob a second son and Leah said, Happy am I for the daughters will call me blessed and she called his name -- - ",
    "answer": "Asher 30:12,13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did God plant the garden - ",
    "answer": "eastward in Eden 2:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what prevented Jacob and Esau from dwelling together - ",
    "answer": "their riches 36:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Esau my brother is -- man and I am a -- man - ",
    "answer": "hairy, smooth 27:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Adam and his wife use to make aprons - ",
    "answer": "they sewed fig leaves together 3:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord told Cain if he doest not well this lieth at the door - ",
    "answer": "sin 4:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob call the name of the place where he set up the pillar - ",
    "answer": "Bethel 28:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did God call the light - ",
    "answer": "day 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the seven years Jacob serve for Rachel seem to him and why - ",
    "answer": "a few days, for the love he had to her 29:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And it -- the Lord that He had made man on the earth and it -- Him at His heart - ",
    "answer": "repented, grieved 6:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Isaac had possession of flocks and herds and great store of --- - ",
    "answer": "servants 26:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the waters increased what did it do to the ark - ",
    "answer": "bare up the ark and it was lift up above the earth 7:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what animals did Jacob set his wives and sons upon - ",
    "answer": "camels 31:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Noah send forth to see if the waters were abated from off the face of the ground - ",
    "answer": "a dove 8:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob acknowledge to God that although he passed over Jordan with only this he has now become two bands - ",
    "answer": "his staff 32:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what did the Lord say the bow shall be seen - ",
    "answer": "the cloud 9:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Jacob say would happen to the flock if they were overdriven in one day - ",
    "answer": "they would die 33:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the father of Seba, Havilah, Sabtah, Raamah and Sabtecha - ",
    "answer": "Cush 10:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Jacob heard that Shechem had defiled Dinah he held his peace until this - ",
    "answer": "until his sons were come in from the field 34:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the sons of Ishmael - ",
    "answer": "Nebajoth, Kedar, Abdeel, Mibsam, Mishma, Dumah, Massa, Hadar, Tema, Jetur, Naphish, Kedemah 25:13-15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God to Jacob, a company of nations shall be of thee and kings shall come out of thy -- - ",
    "answer": "loins 35:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The plain of Jordan was well watered even as the garden of the Lord, before the Lord did this - ",
    "answer": "destroyed Sodom and Gomorrah 13:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "because the Canaanites saw the mourning in the floor of Atad, what is the place called - ",
    "answer": "Abel-mizraim 50:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham do to his son before laying him on the altar - ",
    "answer": "bound him 22:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"how can I do this great wickedness and sin against God\" - ",
    "answer": "Joseph 39:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham give to Hagar before sending her away and where did he place it - ",
    "answer": "bread, bottle of water, on her shoulder 21:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Upon which son of Joseph did Israel place his right hand - ",
    "answer": "Ephraim 48:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Once he restores his wife, what did God tell Abimelech, Abraham would do for him. - ",
    "answer": "pray for him 20:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the money failed what did Joseph tell the people to bring for bread - ",
    "answer": "their cattle 47:15-16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many of his daughters did Lot offer to the men of Sodom - ",
    "answer": "two 19:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons did Simeon have - ",
    "answer": "six 46:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For I know him that he will command his -- and his -- after him - ",
    "answer": "children, household 18:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God hath made me a -- to Pharaoh , and -- of all his house and a -- throughout all the land of Egypt - ",
    "answer": "father, lord, ruler 45:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what groups of male was circumcised in Abraham's house - ",
    "answer": "all that were born in house all that were bought with his money 17:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then they -- took down every man's sack to the ground and opened every man his sack - ",
    "answer": "speedily 44:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was Hagar's response to the questions of the angel - ",
    "answer": "I flee from the face of my mistress Sarai 16:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "that he may seek occasion against us and fall upon us and take us for -- and our asses - ",
    "answer": "bondmen 43:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "ye are -- to see the nakedness of the land ye are come - ",
    "answer": "spies 42:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abram did not divide the birds, but the other animals he divided in the -- - ",
    "answer": "midst 15:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many years did they serve Chedorlaomer - ",
    "answer": "twelve 14:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the first seven ears of corn - ",
    "answer": "rank and good 41:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "we have both -- and provender enough and -- to lodge in - ",
    "answer": "straw, room 24:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in the butler's dream what did the cluster bring forth - ",
    "answer": "ripe grapes 40:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Abram passed through Sichem who was in the land - ",
    "answer": "Canaanite 12:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where on his enemies shall Judah's hand be - ",
    "answer": "the neck 49:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Enos lived after he begat Cainan - ",
    "answer": "eight hundred and fifteen 5:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the Lord feel about Onan spilling his seed on the ground, and what did the Lord do to him - ",
    "answer": "He was displeased, He slew him 38:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "come let us go down and -- their language that they may not understand one another's speech - ",
    "answer": "confound 11:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Reuben find in the field during the wheat harvest - ",
    "answer": "mandrakes 30:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who envied Isaac - ",
    "answer": "the Philistines 26:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where in the garden was the tree of life located - ",
    "answer": "in the midst 2:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when did they hear the voice of the Lord God walking in the garden - ",
    "answer": "in the cool of the day 3:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "My father peradventure will feel me, I shall seem to his as a -- and shall bring a -- upon me and not a -- - ",
    "answer": "deceiver, curse, blessing 27:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Cain -- with Abel his brother - ",
    "answer": "talked 4:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Bethel called first - ",
    "answer": "Luz 28:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did God call the darkness - ",
    "answer": "night 1:5"
  },
  {
    "stem": "it must not be done so in our country to give the -- before the -- - ",
    "answer": "younger, firstborn 29:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Gen 6:7 God purposed to destroy these groups from the earth - ",
    "answer": "man, beast, creeping things, fowls of the air 6:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the second dream Joseph shared with his brethren - ",
    "answer": "the sun the moon and eleven stars made obeisance to him 37:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to all the high hills that were under the whole heaven - ",
    "answer": "they were covered 7:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of her father's had Rachel stolen - ",
    "answer": "the images 31:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the dove find no rest for - ",
    "answer": "the sole of her foot 8:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jacob build a house - ",
    "answer": "Succoth 33:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God said He will remember His covenant and the waters shall no more become this to destroy all flesh - ",
    "answer": "a flood 9:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Jacob sons feel about what Shechem had done to Dinah - ",
    "answer": "grieved and very wroth 34:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who is the following referring to \"the same began to be a mighty one in the earth\" - ",
    "answer": "Nimrod 10:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who travailed and had a hard labor - ",
    "answer": "Rachel 35:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Ishamel when he died - ",
    "answer": "137, 25:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why could not the in which Jacob and Esau were strangers bear them - ",
    "answer": "because of their cattle 36:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of Rebekah's brother - ",
    "answer": "Laban 24:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob sent two hundred of each of these animals as a present to Esau - ",
    "answer": "she goats, ewes 32:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who called to Abraham when he stretched forth his hand and took the knife to slay his son - ",
    "answer": "an angel of the Lord 22:10-11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides the children of Jacob who/what else did Joseph say would dwell in the land of Goshen - ",
    "answer": "children's children, flocks, herd all he has 45:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Abraham sent Hagar and her son away in which wilderness did they wander - ",
    "answer": "Beersheba 21:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "we are all one man's --, we are -- men, thy -- are no spies - ",
    "answer": "sons, true, servants 42:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abimelech rose early in the morning and told his servants all the things, what was the reaction of the servants - ",
    "answer": "the men were sore afraid 20:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did the brothers commune with the steward of Joseph's house - ",
    "answer": "at the door of the house 43:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Lot told the men at the door, that the two strangers came under the shadow of this - ",
    "answer": "his roof 19:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he searched and began at the -- and left at the -- - ",
    "answer": "eldest, youngest 44:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did Sarah deny laughing - ",
    "answer": "she was afraid 18:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Upon which son of Joseph did Israel place his left hand - ",
    "answer": "Manasseh 48:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what day did Abraham take all the males in his house and circumcised them - ",
    "answer": "the selfsame day as God had said unto him 17:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which son of Simeon had a mother who was a Canaanitish woman - ",
    "answer": "Shaul 46:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "name the cattle the people gave in exchange for bread - ",
    "answer": "horses, flocks, asses 47:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The angel instructed Hagar to return to her mistress and do this - ",
    "answer": "submit thyself under her hands 16:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abram do when the fowls came down upon the carcases - ",
    "answer": "he drove them away 15:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "as she spake to Joseph day by day that he hearkened not unto her to lie by her or to .. - ",
    "answer": "be with her 39:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what year did they rebel against Chedorlaomer - ",
    "answer": "13th 14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who will bow down before Judah - ",
    "answer": "his father's children 49:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Abram build in the place where the Lord appeared to him - ",
    "answer": "an altar 12:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham purchase along with the cave - ",
    "answer": "the field 50:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The plain of Jordan was as the garden of the Lord like the land of -- as thou comest unto Zoar - ",
    "answer": "Egypt 13:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the butler's dream what was in his hand - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh's cup 40:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Enos died at this age - ",
    "answer": "nine hundred and five 5:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Describe the second ears of corn that came up - ",
    "answer": "seven thin ears blasted with the east wind 41:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "remain a -- at thy -- house till -- my son be grown - ",
    "answer": "widow , father's, Shelah 38:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To where were the people scattered - ",
    "answer": "upon the face of all the earth 11:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Into how many heads was the river that went out of Eden parted - ",
    "answer": "four 2:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob stole away -- to Laban the Syrian in that he told him not that he had fled - ",
    "answer": "unawares 31:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "among what did Adam and his wife hide themselves from the presence of the Lord - ",
    "answer": "among the trees of the garden 3:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"upon me be thy curse, my son\" - ",
    "answer": "Rebekah 27:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Give the location where Cain slew his brother Abel - ",
    "answer": "in the field 4:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Of all God give him, how much of it did Jacob vow to give back to Him - ",
    "answer": "a tenth 28:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when light and darkness were named, what day was the evening and the morning - ",
    "answer": "first day 1:4"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of the handmaid Laban gave to Rachel - ",
    "answer": "Bilhah 29:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Repeat Gen 6:8 - ",
    "answer": "But Noah found grace in the eyes of the Lord"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what did Leah tell Jacob she has hired him - ",
    "answer": "with her sons mandrakes 30:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How high upwards did the waters prevail - ",
    "answer": "15 cubits 7:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Philistines do to the wells which Abraham's servants had dug - ",
    "answer": "stopped them and filled them with earth 26:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many days did Noah wait before sending forth the dove a second time - ",
    "answer": "seven days 8:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob sent twenty of each of these animals as a present to Esau - ",
    "answer": "he goats, rams, she asses 32:14,15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did God promise to do when He looks upon the bow - ",
    "answer": "remember the covenant 9:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In which mount did Esau dwell - ",
    "answer": "mount Seir 36:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the father of Nimrod - ",
    "answer": "Cush 10:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob make for his cattle at Succoth - ",
    "answer": "booths 33:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In whose presence did Ishmael die - ",
    "answer": "all his brethren 25:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob do when Joseph told him his dream - ",
    "answer": "he rebuked him 37:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who's speaking \" come in thou blessed of the Lord, wherefore standest thou without? for I have prepared the house and room for the camels - ",
    "answer": "Laban 24:29-30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when thy left Bethel and was but a little way from this place, Rachel travailed in hard labor - ",
    "answer": "Ephrath 35:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for now I know that thou -- God, seeing thou has not withheld thy son, thine only son from me - ",
    "answer": "fearest 22:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what had Shechem wrought in Israel by lying with Jacob's daughter - ",
    "answer": "folly 34:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After the water was spent where did Hagar cast the child - ",
    "answer": "under one of the shrubs 21:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in his dream what did the butler do after he pressed the grapes into Pharaoh's cup - ",
    "answer": "he gave the cup into Pharaoh's hand 40:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"what has thou done to us, and what have I offended thee, that thou has brought on me and my kingdom a great sin? thou has done deeds unto me that ought not to be done - ",
    "answer": "Abimelech to Abraham 20:9,10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And when Joseph's brethren saw that their -- was dead, they said that Joseph will peradventure -- us and will certainly -- us all the evil which we did unto him - ",
    "answer": "father, hate, requite 50:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "This one fellow came in to --, and he will needs be a --, now we will deal -- with thee than with them. - ",
    "answer": "sojourn, judge, worse 19:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Israel's blessings who was referred to as lion's whelp - ",
    "answer": "Judah 49:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who's speaking, \"shall I hide from Abraham the thing which I do\" - ",
    "answer": "the Lord 18:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For how long did the people exchange cattle for bread - ",
    "answer": "year 47:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the sons of Levi - ",
    "answer": "Gershon, Kohath and Merari 46:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Abraham when he was circumcised - ",
    "answer": "99 (17:24)"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did the angel tell Hagar he would multiply exceedingly, that it shall not be numbered for multitude - ",
    "answer": "her seed 16:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And there will I -- thee for there are yet five years of famine, lest thou and they household, and all that thou hast come to -- - ",
    "answer": "nourish, poverty 45:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the sun was going down, what two things fell upon Abram - ",
    "answer": "deep sleep, horror of darkness 15:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was the cup found - ",
    "answer": "in Benjamin's sack 44:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the 14th year Chedorlaomer and the kings with him smote the -- in Ashteroth Karnaim, the -- in Ham, the -- in Shaveh Kirathaim and the -- in their mount Seir unto Elparan which is by the wilderness - ",
    "answer": "Rephaims, Zuzims, Emims, Horites 14:5-6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "our money in full -- and we have brought it again in our hand - ",
    "answer": "weight 43:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From Sichem Abram departed unto a mountain east of this place - ",
    "answer": "Bethel 12:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Joseph put all his brethren in ward - ",
    "answer": "three days 42:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Lot chose the plain of Jordan and journeyed in this direction - ",
    "answer": "east 13:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the seven thin ears do to the seven rank and full ears - ",
    "answer": "devoured them 41:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was Joseph's firstborn - ",
    "answer": "Manasseh 48:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's the father of Mahalaleel - ",
    "answer": "Cainan 5:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "once scattered the people left off building this - ",
    "answer": "the city 11:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"what is this dream that thou has dreamed, shall I and thy mother and thy brethren indeed come to bow down ourselves to thee to the earth\" - ",
    "answer": "Jacob 37:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the name of the first head of the river - ",
    "answer": "Pison 2:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph go in the house to do when he found himself alone with his master's wife - ",
    "answer": "his business 39:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, and the Lord God called unto Adam and said unto him, ... - ",
    "answer": "where art thou 3:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob passed over the river and set his face toward this mount - ",
    "answer": "Gilead 31:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Cain's response when the Lord asked him where is Abel thy brother - ",
    "answer": "I know not, am I my brother's keeper 4:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Judah go to his sheep shearers - ",
    "answer": "Timnath 38:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where in the waters was the firmament to reside - ",
    "answer": "in the midst 1:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of Esau's did Rebekah place upon her younger son - ",
    "answer": "his goodly raiment 27:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Noah was described as a just man and -- in his generation - ",
    "answer": "perfect 6:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord do when He saw Leah was hated - ",
    "answer": "he opened her womb 29:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "all flesh of these groups died - ",
    "answer": "fowl, cattle, beast, creeping thing, man 7:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which son is Leah referencing \"God hath given me my hire, because I have given my handmaid to my husband\" - ",
    "answer": "Issachar"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what time did the dove return to Noah - ",
    "answer": "evening 8:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"go from us, for thou art much mightier than than we\" - ",
    "answer": "Abimilech to Isaac 26:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the sons of Noah that went forth out of the ark - ",
    "answer": "Shem, Ham, Japheth 9:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many milch camels with their colts was sent to Esau - ",
    "answer": "thirty 32:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was a mighty hunter before the Lord - ",
    "answer": "Nimrod 10:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is Shalem - ",
    "answer": "a city in Shechem 33:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Isaac when he married Rebekah? - ",
    "answer": "40, 25:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Hamor ask Jacob to make with them - ",
    "answer": "marriages 34:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was set before Abraham's servant to eat - ",
    "answer": "meat 24:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Rachel name her son before her death - ",
    "answer": "Ben-oni 35:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by what was the ram caught in the thicket - ",
    "answer": "by his horns 22:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is Edom - ",
    "answer": "Esau 36:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Hagar went and sat a good way off from the child as it were a -- - ",
    "answer": "bowshot 21:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Fearing retribution who did Joseph brethren send unto him when their father died - ",
    "answer": "a messenger 50:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"because I thought surely the fear of God is not in this place, and they will slay me for my wife's sake\" - ",
    "answer": "Abraham 20:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "referring to whom, from the prey my son thou art gone up, he stooped down he couched as a lion, who shall rouse him up? - ",
    "answer": "Judah 49:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After the men at the door of Lot's house both small and great were smitten with blindness what occurred - ",
    "answer": "they wearied themselves to find the door 19:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was Joseph's younger son - ",
    "answer": "Ephraim 48:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the second year the people came to Joseph having no money or cattle what did they say was left - ",
    "answer": "their bodies and land 47:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How does the Lord describe the cry and sin of Sodom and Gomorrah - ",
    "answer": "great, very grievous 18:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Ishmael when he was circumcised? - ",
    "answer": "thirteen 17:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the daughter of Asher - ",
    "answer": "Serah 46:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what name did the angel instruct Hagar to call her son and why - ",
    "answer": "Ishmael, because the Lord had heard her affliction 16:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and ye shall tell my father all my -- in Egypt - ",
    "answer": "glory 45:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord tell Abram his seed shall be in land that is not theirs - ",
    "answer": "a stranger 15:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did they do when the cup was found in Benjamin's sack - ",
    "answer": "rent their clothes, laded every man his ass and returned to the city 44:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Enmishpat is also known as this - ",
    "answer": "Kadesh 14:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \" peace be to you, fear not, your God and the God of your father, hath given you treasure in your sacks\" - ",
    "answer": "the steward of Joseph's house 43:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abram pitched his tent having Bethel on the west and this place on the east - ",
    "answer": "Hai 12:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did Joseph tell his brethren he feared - ",
    "answer": "God 42:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to Pharaoh after the seven thin ears devoured the rank and full ears - ",
    "answer": "he awoke 41:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Lot dwelt in the cities of the plain and pitched his tent towards this place - ",
    "answer": "Sodom 13:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Cainan when he begat Mahalaleel - ",
    "answer": "seventy years 5:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph tell the butler the three branches represented - ",
    "answer": "three days 40:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why was the name of it called Babel - ",
    "answer": "because there the Lord confound the language of all the earth and from thence the Lord did scatter them abroad upon the face of all the earth 11:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who went with Judah to Timnath - ",
    "answer": "Hirah the Adullamite 38:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What land does Pison compass - ",
    "answer": "the whole land of Havilah 2:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Potiphar's wife caught Joseph by this - ",
    "answer": "his garment 39:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"I heard thy voice in the garden, and I was afraid, because I was naked and I hid myself\" - ",
    "answer": "Adam 3:9,10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "On what day was it told Laban that Jacob had fled - ",
    "answer": "third day 31:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the -- of thy brother's blood crieth unto me from the ground - ",
    "answer": "voice 4:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and his brethren -- him but his father observed the saying - ",
    "answer": "envied 37:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was to divide the waters from the waters - ",
    "answer": "the firmament 1:6"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where on Jacob did Rebekah place the skins of the kids of the goats - ",
    "answer": "upon his hand, upon the smooth of his neck 27:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The earth was also corrupt before God and the earth was filled with -- - ",
    "answer": "violence 6:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name of Leah's first son - ",
    "answer": "Reuben 29:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "All who had this in their nostrils on dry land died - ",
    "answer": "breath of life 7:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the name of the fifth son Leah bare Jacob - ",
    "answer": "Issachar 30:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the dove have in her mouth - ",
    "answer": "an olive leaf plucked off 8:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Isaac pitch his tent when he departed from Abimelech - ",
    "answer": "valley of Gerar 26:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who is the father of Canaan - ",
    "answer": "Ham 9:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "forty of these animals was sent to Esau - ",
    "answer": "kine 32:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is Babel,Erech, Accad, and Calneh the beginning of - ",
    "answer": "Nimrod's kingdom 10:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where in Shalem did Jacob pitch his tent - ",
    "answer": "before the city 33:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because she was barren what did Isaac do for his wife - ",
    "answer": "intreated the Lord 25:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Hamor tell Jacob to do in the land - ",
    "answer": "dwell, trade and get possessions 34:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham's servant refused to eat until he had done this - ",
    "answer": "told his errand 24:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who renamed Benjamin - ",
    "answer": "his father 35:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But the men of Sodom were -- and -- before the Lord exceedingly - ",
    "answer": "wicked, sinners 13:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the father of the Edomites - ",
    "answer": "Esau 36:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Hagar went and sat a good way off from the child, what did she not want to see - ",
    "answer": "the death of the child 21:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph left the garment in her hand and did this - ",
    "answer": "fled and got him out 39:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And yet indeed she is my --, she is the daughter of my -- but not the daughter of my -- and she became my -- - ",
    "answer": "sister, father, mother, wife 20:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The -- shall not depart from Judah nor a -- from between his feet until -- come, and unto Him shall the gathering of the -- be - ",
    "answer": "sceptre, lawgiver, Shiloh, people 49:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In placing his hands on Joseph's sons to bless them, what word does the scripture use to describe how Israel guided his hands - ",
    "answer": "wittingly 48:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What reason did the men give Lot for destroying the city - ",
    "answer": "because the cry of them is waxen great before the face of the Lord 19:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham asked the Lord if He will destroy this group with the wicked - ",
    "answer": "righteous 18:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph bought all the land of Egypt for this person - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh 47:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What kind of man did the angel tell Hagar her son will be - ",
    "answer": "a wild man 16:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was the mother of Gad and Asher - ",
    "answer": "Zilpah 46:16-18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For how long did the Lord tell Abram his seed shall be afflicted - ",
    "answer": "four hundred years 15:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and he fell upon Benjamin's -- and wept and Benjamin wept upon his -- - ",
    "answer": "neck, neck 45:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Cherdorlaomer and the other kings came to Enmishpat which is Kadesh and smote all the country of the --- and also the -- that dwelt in Hazeron-tamar - ",
    "answer": "Amalekites, Amorites 14:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"what deed is this that ye have done,wot ye not that such a man as I can certainly divine - ",
    "answer": "Joseph 44:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham offer up for a burnt offering instead of his son - ",
    "answer": "a ram 22:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the steward bring out to Joseph's brethren - ",
    "answer": "Simeon 43:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "we are very -- concerning our brother, in that we saw the -- of his soul, when he besought us, and we would not hear, therefore is this -- come upon us - ",
    "answer": "guilty, anguish, distress 42:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abram built an altar who's name did he call upon - ",
    "answer": "the Lord 12:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For how long did Cainan live after he begat Mahalaleel - ",
    "answer": "eight hundred and forty 5:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the morning after the dream, how was Pharaoh - ",
    "answer": "his spirit was troubled 41:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Shem when he begat Arphaxad - ",
    "answer": "one hundred 11:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph tell the butler Pharaoh would do within three days - ",
    "answer": "lift up his head and restore him to his place 40:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What precious element is found in the land of Havilah - ",
    "answer": "gold 2:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph's brethren sent a messenger unto him, who did they say gave a command before he died - ",
    "answer": "thy father 50:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who told thee thou was --, hast thou -- of the tree whereof I -- thee that thou should not eat? - ",
    "answer": "naked, eaten, commanded 3:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "It was told Tamar that this person was going up to Timnath to shear his sheep - ",
    "answer": "her father in law 38:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the Lord told Cain he was cursed from this place - ",
    "answer": "the earth 4:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Laban took his brethren and pursued Jacob, how many days journey was it - ",
    "answer": "seven 31:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with respect to the firmament where were the waters - ",
    "answer": "under the firmament, above the firmament 1:7"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did Joseph's brethren go to feed the flock - ",
    "answer": "in Shechem 37:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for all -- had corrupted his way upon the earth - ",
    "answer": "flesh 6:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the response to this question \"how is it that thou has found it so quickly , my son ?\" - ",
    "answer": "because the Lord thy God brought it to me 27:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did the waters prevail upon the earth - ",
    "answer": "a hundred and fifty days 7:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Concerning what son did Leah utter these words - ",
    "answer": "surely the Lord hath looked upon my affliction, now therefore will my husband love me 29:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Noah know (lol) when he saw the olive leaf in the mouth of the dove - ",
    "answer": "the waters were abated from off the earth 8:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which son is Leah referring to \"God hath endowed me with a good dowry, now will my husband dwell with me, because I have borne him six sons\" - ",
    "answer": "Zebulun 30:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Noah began to be a -- and planted a vineyard - ",
    "answer": "husbandman 9:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "after what did Isaac call the names of the well - ",
    "answer": "after the names by which his father had called them 26:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In which land is Babel, Erech, Accad and Calneh located - ",
    "answer": "Shinar 10:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "ten of each of these animals was sent to Esau - ",
    "answer": "bulls, foals 32:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is another name for Bela - ",
    "answer": "Zoar 14:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from whom did Jacob buy a parcel of ground - ",
    "answer": "children of Hamor 33:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Rebekah go to inquire of the Lord - ",
    "answer": "because the children struggled together within her 25:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who's speaking \"ask me never so much dowry and gift and I will give according as ye shall say unto me\" - ",
    "answer": "Shechem 34:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to the servant what had the Lord blessed Abraham with - ",
    "answer": "flocks, herd, silver, gold, menservants, maidservants, camels, asses 24:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Rachel was buried in the way to Ephrath which is -- - ",
    "answer": "Bethlehem 35:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Abraham call the place where he offered the ram instead of his son - ",
    "answer": "Jehovah-jireh 22:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Eliphaz the son of Esau had how many sons - ",
    "answer": "five 36:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Hagar do as she sat over against the child - ",
    "answer": "lift up her voice and wept 21:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"but think on me when it shall be well with thee, and make mention of me unto Pharaoh and bring me out of this house\" - ",
    "answer": "Joseph to butler 40:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "so shall we say unto Joseph, -- I pray thee now the -- of thy brethren and their sin, for they did unto thee -- - ",
    "answer": "forgive, trespass, evil 50:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what/who did Abimelech give unto Abraham - ",
    "answer": "sheep, oxen, menservants, womenservants 20:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the men tell Lot had sent them to destroy the city - ",
    "answer": "the Lord 19:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Binding his foal unto the -- - ",
    "answer": "vine 49:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In pleading for Sodom Abraham began at what number of righteous - ",
    "answer": "fifty 18:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Joseph feel when he saw his father laid his right hand upon the head of Ephraim - ",
    "answer": "it displeased him 48:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who is this referring to \"his hand will be against every man and every man's hand against him, and he shall dwell in the presence of all his brethren\" - ",
    "answer": "Ishmael 16:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did the Egyptians sell their field - ",
    "answer": "because the famine prevailed over them 47:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And also that nation, whom they shall serve I will -- and afterward they shall come out with great -- - ",
    "answer": "judge, substance 15:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many souls were borne to Jacob through Zilpah - ",
    "answer": "sixteen 46:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Abram journeyed, going on still toward the -- - ",
    "answer": "South 12:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Moreover he -- all his brethren and wept upon them and after that his brethren -- with him - ",
    "answer": "kissed, talked 45:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "identify the speaker \"what shall we say unto my lord, what shall we speak or how shall we clear ourselves, God hath found out the iniquity of thy servants, behold we are my lord's servants both we and he also with whom the cup is found\" - ",
    "answer": "Judah 44:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According Gen 13:16 like what did the Lord tell Abram he would make his seed - ",
    "answer": "the dust of the earth"
  },
  {
    "stem": "At what age did Cainan die - ",
    "answer": "nine hundred and ten 5:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the man brought the men into Joseph's house, and gave them -- and they washed their -- and he gave their asses -- - ",
    "answer": "water, feet,provender 43:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did God call the firmament - ",
    "answer": "heaven 1:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"spake I not unto you saying, do not sin against the child and ye would not hear?, therefore also his blood is required - ",
    "answer": "Reuben 42:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the man said the -- whom thou gavest to be with me, she gave me of the tree and I did eat - ",
    "answer": "woman 3:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the morning after the dream who did Pharaoh send and call for - ",
    "answer": "all the magicians and wise men of Egypt 41:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the Lord told Cain the earth opened this to receive his brother's blood from his hand - ",
    "answer": "her mouth 4:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Tamar took this garment off of her and covered herself with a vail - ",
    "answer": "widow's garment 14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How is the gold in the land of Havilah described - ",
    "answer": "good 2:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when she saw that he left his garment in her hand and was fled forth who did she call unto - ",
    "answer": "the men of her house 39:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"the end of all flesh is come before me\" - ",
    "answer": "God to Noah 6:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob tell his servant to put between drove and drove - ",
    "answer": "a space 32:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After an additional seven days Noah sent forth the dove again what did she not do - ",
    "answer": "she returned not again unto him anymore 8:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who strove with Isaac's herd men over the well - ",
    "answer": "the herd men of Gerar 26:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when Noah drunk the wine - ",
    "answer": "he was drunken 9:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To which son is Leah referring, because the Lord hath heard that I was hated, He hath therefore given me this son also - ",
    "answer": "Simeon 29:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who built Nineveh, city of Rehoboth and Calah and Resen - ",
    "answer": "Asshur 10:11,12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the name of the sixth son Leah bare Jacob - ",
    "answer": "Zebulun 30:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many years after the flood did Shem begat Arphaxad - ",
    "answer": "two 11:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did Laban overtake Jacob - ",
    "answer": "in mount Gilead 31:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did the kings join for battle - ",
    "answer": "vale of Siddim 14:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The -- is Jacob's -- but the -- are the -- of Esau - ",
    "answer": "voice, voice, hands, hands 27:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the Lord said unto her two -- are in thy womb, and two manner of --- shall be separated from thy bowels and one people shall be -- than the other and the -- shall serve the -- - ",
    "answer": "nations, people, stronger, elder, younger 25:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much did Jacob pay for the parcel of ground - ",
    "answer": "a hundred pieces of money 33:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then Laban and Bethuel answered and said the thing proceedeth from the Lord, we cannot speak unto thee -- or -- - ",
    "answer": "bad, good 24:50"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the sons of Jacob answer Shechem and his father - ",
    "answer": "deceitfully 34:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Like what two thing did the angel of the Lord tell Abraham He would multiply his seed - ",
    "answer": "stars of heaven, the sand which is upon seashore 22:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob set on Rachel's grave - ",
    "answer": "a pillar 35:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God heard the voice of the -- and the angel of God called to -- out of heaven - ",
    "answer": "lad, Hagar 21:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was the concubine of Eliphaz, Esau's son - ",
    "answer": "Timna 36:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did Abimelech restore to Abraham - ",
    "answer": "Sarah his wife 20:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Israel sent Joseph out of this place to Shechem - ",
    "answer": "vale of Hebron 37:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "out of which land did Joseph tell the butler he was stolen away - ",
    "answer": "land of the Hebrews 40:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"up, get you out of this place, for the Lord will destroy this city\" - ",
    "answer": "Lot to his sons in law 19:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Shall not the -- of all the earth do right - ",
    "answer": "judge 18:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Joseph's emotional response when his brethren sent a messenger asking for forgiveness - ",
    "answer": "he wept 50:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Hagar call the name of the Lord that spake unto her - ",
    "answer": "Thou God seest me 16:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and His ass' colt unto the -- - ",
    "answer": "choice vine 49:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what state did the Lord tell Abram he would go to his fathers - ",
    "answer": "in peace 15:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph do when he saw his father had laid his right hand upon the head of Ephraim - ",
    "answer": "he held up his father's hand to remove it from Ephraim's head to Manasseh's head 48:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did Abram go down to Egypt to sojourn there - ",
    "answer": "for the famine was grievous in the land 12:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "so the land became -- - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh's 47:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Arise walk through the land in the -- of it and in the -- of it for I will give it unto thee - ",
    "answer": "length, breadth 13:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "All the souls born to Jacob through Rachel were how many - ",
    "answer": "fourteen 46:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In whose house was the fame thereof heard saying Joseph's brethren are come - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh's house 45:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was Mahalaleel's son - ",
    "answer": "Jared 5:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what day did God divide the waters and named heaven - ",
    "answer": "second 1:6-8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "seeing that his life is bound up in the -- life - ",
    "answer": "lad's 44:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Be specfic, who to whom, what is this that thou has done - ",
    "answer": "Lord God to the woman 3:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To whom did Joseph direct these words, \"God be gracious unto thee my son\" - ",
    "answer": "Benjamin 43:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the Lord told Cain the voice of his brother's blood crieth unto Him from this place - ",
    "answer": "the ground 4:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did not Joseph's brothers know that he understood them - ",
    "answer": "for he spake unto them by an interpreter 42:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what stones are found in the land of Havilah - ",
    "answer": "bdellium, onyx 2:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Pharaoh told his dream, but there was none that could do this - ",
    "answer": "interpret the dream 41:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What kind of wood was Noah instructed to use to make the ark - ",
    "answer": "gopher wood 6:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"go I pray thee and see whether it be well with thy brethren and well with the flocks\" - ",
    "answer": "Israel to Joseph 37:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the --- year, in the -- month the -- day of the month the waters were dried up from off the face of the earth - ",
    "answer": "601, 1st, 1st 8:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"see he hath brought in an Hebrew unto us to mock us, he came in to lie with me and I cried with a loud voice\" - ",
    "answer": "Potiphar's wife 39:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was Noah uncovered - ",
    "answer": "within his tent 9:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob hope the present would do to Esau - ",
    "answer": "appease him 32:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Between what places was Resen located - ",
    "answer": "between Nineveh and Calah 10:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To which son is Leah referring, now this time will my husband be joined unto me, because I have borne him three sons - ",
    "answer": "Levi 29:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Shem live after he begat Arphaxad - ",
    "answer": "five hundred 11:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the name of the daughter Leah bare Jacob - ",
    "answer": "Dinah 30:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Two groups of kings battled in the vale of Siddim, how many kings did each group consist of - ",
    "answer": "four and five 14:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What instructions did God give to Laban in a dream, concerning Jacob - ",
    "answer": "take heed that thou speak not unto Jacob either good or bad 31:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the physical description of Esau when he came out of the womb - ",
    "answer": "red all over like a hairy garment 25:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did Isaac not discern it was Jacob - ",
    "answer": "because his hands were hairy as his brother Esau's hand 27:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The servant gave to Rebekah jewels of silver and jewels of gold and -- - ",
    "answer": "raiment 24:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob name the altar he erected in the parcel of ground he bought - ",
    "answer": "El-elohe Israel 33:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of his enemies shall Abraham's seed possess - ",
    "answer": "the gate 22:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Isaac's herd men digged in this place and found a well of springing water - ",
    "answer": "valley 26:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what question did the angel of God ask Hagar - ",
    "answer": "what aileth thee Hagar 21:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the sons of Jacob told Shechem and his father it would be a reproach to them to give their sister to one that is this - ",
    "answer": "uncircumcised 34:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many pieces of silver did Abimelech give to Abraham - ",
    "answer": "thousand 20:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Tamar covered herself with a vail, wrapped herself and went and sat in this place - ",
    "answer": "in an open place which is by the way to Timnath 38:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Lot seem to his sons in law - ",
    "answer": "as one that mocked 19:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Timna bare one son to Eliphaz the son of Esau, what was his name - ",
    "answer": "Amalek 36:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob spread his tent beyond this tower - ",
    "answer": "Edar 35:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "besides being dust how else does Abraham describe himself to the Lord - ",
    "answer": "ashes 18:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The well where the angel spoke with Hagar was called Beerlahairoi, between what places is it located - ",
    "answer": "Kadesh, Bered 16:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In his dream what did the chief baker have on his head - ",
    "answer": "three white baskets 40:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord told Abram this would happen to him in a good old age - ",
    "answer": "he would be buried 15:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"fear not, for am I in the place of God\" - ",
    "answer": "Joseph to his brethren 50:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Abram tell Sarai to say to the Egyptians regarding her relationship to him - ",
    "answer": "she was his sister 12:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "he washed his garments in -- and his clothes in the blood of -- - ",
    "answer": "wine, grapes 49:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After separating from Lot Abram came to dwell in this plain - ",
    "answer": "Mamre 13:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After the land was bought where were the Egyptians removed to - ",
    "answer": "cities 47:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Mahalaleel when he begat Jared - ",
    "answer": "sixty-five 5:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was the mother of Joseph and Benjamin - ",
    "answer": "Rachel 46:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Pharaoh and his servants feel when they heard Joseph's brethren had come - ",
    "answer": "it pleased them well 45:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God commanded that the waters under the heaven be gathered together unto one place and this should appear - ",
    "answer": "dry land 1:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the woman tell the Lord God the serpent had done to her - ",
    "answer": "beguiled her 3:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when they cup was found and they brought back to Joseph's house, who was it that made a earnest plea to Joseph, offering up himself to be a bondman instead of Benjamin - ",
    "answer": "Judah 44:18-34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord tell Cain would happen when he tillest the ground - ",
    "answer": "it shall not henceforth yield unto him her strength 4:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The scriptures says Joseph made haste for this yearn upon his brothers and he sought where to weep - ",
    "answer": "his bowels 43:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What is the name of the second river - ",
    "answer": "Gihon 2:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph turned himself from his brethren and did this then returned and communed with them - ",
    "answer": "wept 42:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "within and without the ark was to be pitched with this - ",
    "answer": "pitch 6:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"I do remember my faults this day\" - ",
    "answer": "the chief butler 41:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what state was the face of the ground when Noah removed the covering from the ark - ",
    "answer": "dried 8:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when asked to put his right hand on Manasseh what was Israel's response - ",
    "answer": "he refused 48:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who saw the nakedness of his father and told his two brethren without - ",
    "answer": "Ham 9:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when a certain man found Joseph what was he doing in the field - ",
    "answer": "wandering 37:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the father of, Ludim, anamim, Lehabim, Naphtuhim, Pathrusim, Casluhim and Caphtorhim - ",
    "answer": "Mizraim 10:13,14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Potiphar's wife do with Joseph's garment - ",
    "answer": "laid it up by her until his lord came home 39:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the son Arphaxad begat when he was thirty five years old - ",
    "answer": "Salah 11:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did Laban and his brethren pitch - ",
    "answer": "in the mount of Gilead 31:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In which land is the plain of Mamre - ",
    "answer": "Hebron 13:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Isaac call the first well, and why - ",
    "answer": "Esek, because they strove with him 26:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "coming out of the womb what did Jacob take hold of - ",
    "answer": "Esau's heel 25:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Even though Shelah was grown what did Tamar see - ",
    "answer": "she was not given unto him to wife 38:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham's servant give to Rebekah's mother and brother - ",
    "answer": "precious things 24:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Leah said of this son, now I will praise the Lord - ",
    "answer": "Judah 29:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From mount Moriah where did Abraham return with the young men and dwelt - ",
    "answer": "Beersheba 22:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Saying God hath taken away my reproach what did Rachel name her son - ",
    "answer": "Joseph 30:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Hagar see when God opened her eyes - ",
    "answer": "a well of water 21:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Isaac what did Jacob's raiment smell like - ",
    "answer": "the field 27:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did God do when Abraham prayed for Abimelech - ",
    "answer": "healed him his wife and his maidservants and they bare children 20:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which ford did Jacob pass over with his sons and wives - ",
    "answer": "Jabbok 32:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when this arose then the angels hastened Lot - ",
    "answer": "the morning 19:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was Shechem's father - ",
    "answer": "Hamor 33:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham asked the Lord to spare the cities if it lacked this many from the fifty - ",
    "answer": "five 18:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The sons of Jacob told Shechem and his father if the males consented to this then they will give them their daughters, or else they will take their daughter and be gone - ",
    "answer": "being circumcised 34:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which of his father's concubine did Reuben lay with - ",
    "answer": "Bilhah 35:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what generation did the Lord tell Abram his descendants would return to Canaan - ",
    "answer": "fourth 15:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was the vale of Siddim full of - ",
    "answer": "slime pits 14:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Reuel son of Esau had how many sons - ",
    "answer": "four 36:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Abram when Hagar bear him Ishmael - ",
    "answer": "86, 16:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "in the chief baker's dream, which basket contained all manner of bakements for Pharaoh - ",
    "answer": "the uppermost basket 40:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did the Egyptians behold Sarai to be - ",
    "answer": "very fair 12:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Now therefore fear ye not, I will nourish you and your little one and he comforted them and spake -- unto them - ",
    "answer": "kindly 50:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Mahalaleel live after he begat Jared - ",
    "answer": "eight hundred and thirty years 5:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "His -- shall be red with wine, and his -- white with milk - ",
    "answer": "eyes, teeth 49:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Arphaxad live after he begat Salah - ",
    "answer": "403 years 11:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Which son of Joseph did Israel say will be greater - ",
    "answer": "Ephraim 48:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Whose was the only land in Egypt that was not bought - ",
    "answer": "the priests 47:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord told the serpent it was cursed above these two groups - ",
    "answer": "above all cattle and above every beast of the field 3:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides a fugitive what else did the Lord tell Cain he would be in the earth - ",
    "answer": "a vagabond 4:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons did Benjamin have - ",
    "answer": "ten 46:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what land does Gihon compass - ",
    "answer": "the whole land of Ethiopia 2:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what transportation did Pharaoh offer to Joseph's brethren - ",
    "answer": "wagons 45:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Noah instructed to make in the ark - ",
    "answer": "rooms 6:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph do to Simeon - ",
    "answer": "took him and bound him before their eyes 42:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What day and month was the earth dried - ",
    "answer": "27th day of the 2nd month 8:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After Pharaoh sent for Joseph he was brought hastily out of this place - ",
    "answer": "the dungeon 41:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Shem and Japheth use to cover the nakedness of their father - ",
    "answer": "a garment 9:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Joseph enter and weep - ",
    "answer": "his chambers 43:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what does the bible say was the result when God commanded that the waters under the heaven be gathered together unto one place and dry land appear - ",
    "answer": "it was so 1:9"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"the Hebrew servant which thou has brought unto us, came in unto me to mock me\" - ",
    "answer": "Potiphar's wife to Potiphar 39:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who came out of Casluhim - ",
    "answer": "Philistim 10:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Until when did the man wrestle with Jacob - ",
    "answer": "breaking of the day 32:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abram build unto the Lord in the plain of Mamre - ",
    "answer": "an altar 13:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Judah saw Tamar in the way he thought her to be this person because she had covered her face - ",
    "answer": "a harlot 38:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Isaac when Rebekah bare him the twins - ",
    "answer": "sixty 25:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"for I have learned by experience that the Lord hath blessed me for thy sake\" - ",
    "answer": "Laban 30:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many more days did Rebekah's mother and brother want her to stay with them - ",
    "answer": "ten 24:55"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As whom did Laban tell Jacob he has carried away his daughters - ",
    "answer": "as captives taken with the sword 31:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "It was told Abraham that this person had borne children unto Nahor - ",
    "answer": "Milcah 22:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In Isaac's blessing to Jacob, God give thee the -- of heaven and the -- of the earth and plenty of corn and -- - ",
    "answer": "dew, fatness, wine 27:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from what container did Hagar give her son water to drink - ",
    "answer": "a bottle 21:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Hamor and Shechem feel about the words of Jacob' s sons - ",
    "answer": "it pleased them 34:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did God close up all the wombs of the house of Abimelech - ",
    "answer": "because of Sarah Abraham's wife 20:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who heard that Reuben had laid with Bilhah - ",
    "answer": "Israel 35:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Arise take thy wife and thy two daughters, which are here lest thou be consumed in the -- of the city - ",
    "answer": "iniquity 19:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of the second well they strove for - ",
    "answer": "Sitnah 26:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In pleading for Sodom and Gomorrah what was the third number Abraham presented to the Lord - ",
    "answer": "forty 18:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was Esau's firstborn - ",
    "answer": "Eliphaz 36:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for the -- of the Amorites is not yet full - ",
    "answer": "iniquity 15:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The told Joseph he heard his brethren say they will go to this place - ",
    "answer": "Dothan 37:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what ate the bakements in the chief baker's dream - ",
    "answer": "the birds 40:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Those that did not fall in the slime pits fled to this place - ",
    "answer": "the mountain 14:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "At age thirty Salah begat this son - ",
    "answer": "Eber 11:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To what generation did Joseph see Ephraim's children - ",
    "answer": "third 50:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who commended Sarai before Pharaoh - ",
    "answer": "the princes of Pharaoh 12:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where shall Zebulun dwell - ",
    "answer": "at the haven of the sea 49:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Mahalaleel when he died - ",
    "answer": "eight hundred and ninety five 5:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many portion above his brethren did Israel give Joseph - ",
    "answer": "one 48:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did God call the dry land - ",
    "answer": "earth 1:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for the priests had a portion assigned them of -- - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh 47:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "upon thy -- shalt thou go and -- shalt thou eat all the days of thy life - ",
    "answer": "belly, dust 3:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was the mother of Dan and Naphtali - ",
    "answer": "Bilhah 46:23-25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph gave to each man changes of raiment but what did he give to Benjamin - ",
    "answer": "three hundred pieces of silver and five changes of raiment 45:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"my punishment is greater than I can bear\" - ",
    "answer": "Cain to the Lord 4:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name of the third river - ",
    "answer": "Hiddekel 2:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And he washed his face went out and -- himself and said set on bread - ",
    "answer": "refrained 43:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the length of the ark - ",
    "answer": "three hundred cubits 6:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides filling their sacks with corn what else did Joseph command concerning his brothers - ",
    "answer": "restore every man's money into his sack, give them provision for the way 42:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Every living thing was to go forth out of the ark and breed in this manner - ",
    "answer": "abundantly 8:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph do before he came in unto Pharaoh - ",
    "answer": "he shaved himself and changed his raiment 41:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Shem and Japheth carry the garment they used to cover their father - ",
    "answer": "upon their shoulders 9:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Judah promise to give Tamar whom he thought was a harlot for going in unto her - ",
    "answer": "a kid from the flock 38:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was the firstborn of Canaan - ",
    "answer": "Sidon 10:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Joseph's master feel when he heard the words of his wife - ",
    "answer": "his wrath was kindled 39:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Into who's house was Sarai taken in Egypt - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh's 12:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the man saw that he prevailed not against him what did he do to Jacob - ",
    "answer": "he touched the hollow of his thigh 32:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob was a plain man dwelling in tents, what description was given of Esau - ",
    "answer": "cunning hunter, a man of the field 25:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of the well for which they strove not - ",
    "answer": "Rehoboth 26:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Thou art our sister be thou the mother of thousands of -- and let thy seed possess the gates of those that -- them - ",
    "answer": "millions, hate 24:60"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Before Jacob's arrival Laban's cattle was little what did it increased to - ",
    "answer": "a multitude 30:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many did Milcah bare to Nahaor - ",
    "answer": "eight 22:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "With what did Laban tell Jacob he would have sent him away - ",
    "answer": "mirth, songs, tabret, harp 31:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the men do while Lot lingered - ",
    "answer": "laid hold upon his hand, and upon the hand of his wife and upon the hand of his two daughters and brought them forth and set them without the city 19:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Let people -- thee and nations bow down to thee - ",
    "answer": "serve 27:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from forty to thirty to twenty what was the final number Abraham pleaded for to save the city - ",
    "answer": "ten 18:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the young man -- not to do the thing, because he had -- in Jacob's daughter and he was more -- than all his father's house - ",
    "answer": "deferred, delight, honorable 34:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And it came to pass that when the -- went down and it was -- , behold a smoking -- and a burning -- that passed between those pieces - ",
    "answer": "sun, dark, furnace, lamp 15:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which city in Mamre did Jacob come to his father - ",
    "answer": "Arbah 35:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they took all the goods of Sodom and Gomorrah and all their -- and went their way - ",
    "answer": "victuals 14:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many dukes came from Eliphaz - ",
    "answer": "seven 36:15-16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the lad grew and dwelt in the wilderness and became an -- - ",
    "answer": "archer 21:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Joseph's brethren saw him a far off what did conspire against him to do - ",
    "answer": "slay him 37:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Salah live after he begat Eber - ",
    "answer": "403 years 11:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what in the chief baker's dream represented three days - ",
    "answer": "the three baskets 40:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Cain say everyone that findeth him would do to him - ",
    "answer": "slay him 4:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the children also of --the son of Manasseh were brought up upon Joseph's knees - ",
    "answer": "Machir 50:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Israel give Joseph one portion above his brethren, from who's hand did he take it out and what did he use to do so - ",
    "answer": "hand of the Amorite, his sword and bow 48:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did these nations come from, Jebusite, Amorite, Girgashite, Hivite, Arkite, Sinite, Arvadite, Zemarite - ",
    "answer": "Canaan 10:15-18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The river Hiddekel goes to the east of this place - ",
    "answer": "Assyria 2:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "having sold themselves and their land, Joseph told the people when they sow the land the -- part of the increase was to be given to Pharaoh and the -- parts shall be theirs. - ",
    "answer": "fifth, four 47:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Repeat Gen 3:15 - ",
    "answer": "And I will put enmity between thee and the woman, and between thy seed and her seed; it shall bruise thy head and thou shall bruise his heel"
  },
  {
    "stem": "all the souls born to Jacob through Bilhah were how many - ",
    "answer": "seven 46:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "seas - ",
    "answer": "the gathering together of the waters 1:10"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph send to his father - ",
    "answer": "ten asses laden with the good things of Egypt, ten she assess laden with corn and bread and meat 45:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jared lived sixty and two years and begat this son - ",
    "answer": "Enoch 5:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is eating bread with Hebrews considered to be to the Egyptians - ",
    "answer": "an abomination 43:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the breadth of the ark - ",
    "answer": "fifty cubits 6:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did one open his sack to give his ass provender when he espied his money - ",
    "answer": "the inn 42:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"I have dreamed a dream and there is none that can interpret it, and I have heard say of thee, that thou can understand a dream to interpret it\" - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh to Joseph 41:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Noah build unto the Lord - ",
    "answer": "an altar 8:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because they entered the tent in this way Shem and Japheth saw not the nakedness of their father - ",
    "answer": "backward 9:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for what shall Zebulun be a haven - ",
    "answer": "for ships 49:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Eber when he begat Peleg - ",
    "answer": "34 years old 11:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After hearing the words of his wife, where did Joseph's master put him - ",
    "answer": "in prison 39:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From where was Isaac coming when he lifted up his eyes and saw the camels coming - ",
    "answer": "the way of the well of Lahai-roi"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Laban tell Jacob he has not suffered him to do to his sons and daughters - ",
    "answer": "kiss them 31:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of Nahor's firstborn - ",
    "answer": "Huz 22:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what pledge did Tamar ask of Judah - ",
    "answer": "his signet, bracelets and staff 38:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In which wilderness did Ishmael dwell - ",
    "answer": "wilderness of Paran 21:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "be lord over thy brethren and let thy -- sons bow down to thee - ",
    "answer": "mother's 27:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After they brought them forth what instructions did the men give to Lot, his wife and two daughters - ",
    "answer": "escape for thy life, look not behind thee, neither stay thou in the plain, escape to the mountains 19:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what among the flock was to be Jacob's hire - ",
    "answer": "speckled and spotted cattle 30:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord told Abram He will give the land to his seed, what two bodies of water forms the borders of the land - ",
    "answer": "river of Egypt, Euphrates 15:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because they strove not for the well Rehoboth, what did Isaac say the Lord had made for them, so that they will be fruitful in the land - ",
    "answer": "room 26:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did the kings take besides Lot - ",
    "answer": "his goods 14:12"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when the man touched the hollow of Jacob's thigh - ",
    "answer": "Jacob's thigh was out of joint 32:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did Pharaoh entreat Abram well - ",
    "answer": "for Sarai's sake 12:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Hamor and Shechem commune with the men of the city - ",
    "answer": "at the gate of the city 34:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did Isaac love Esau? - ",
    "answer": "because he did eat of his venison 25:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the city of Arbah is also called - ",
    "answer": "Hebron 35:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The border of Canaan was from -- to -- - ",
    "answer": "Sidon, Gaza"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what title did Teman, Omar, zepho, Kenaz, Korah, Gatam and Amalek have in common - ",
    "answer": "Dukes 36:15-16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What of the woman did the Lord say He would greatly multiply - ",
    "answer": "sorrow and conception 3:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they said one to another behold this -- cometh - ",
    "answer": "dreamer 37:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Noah awoke from his wine, what did he know - ",
    "answer": "what his younger son had done to him 9:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of prisoners were bound in the prison where Joseph was placed - ",
    "answer": "king's prisoners 39:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "give the name of the fourth river - ",
    "answer": "Euphrates 2:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "unto where shall Zebulun's border be - ",
    "answer": "unto Zidon 49:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God said let the -- bring forth grass, the herb yielding --, and the fruit tree yielding -- after his kind whose seed is in itself upon the --. - ",
    "answer": "earth, seed, fruit, earth 1:11"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what specifically was the four part given to the people be used for - ",
    "answer": "seed of the field, food for them, them of their household and little ones 47:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from what of the Lord did Cain say he shall be hid - ",
    "answer": "face of the Lord 4:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many souls came with Jacob into Egypt which came out of his loins - ",
    "answer": "three score and six (66) 46:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"see that ye fall not out by the way\" - ",
    "answer": "Joseph to his brethren 45:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long after he begat Enoch did Jared live - ",
    "answer": "eight hundred years 5:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "This dimension of the ark measured thirty cubits - ",
    "answer": "height 6:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they sat before him the firstborn according to his -- and the youngest according to his -- and the men -- one at another - ",
    "answer": "birthright, youth, marvelled 43:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Noah offer as burnt offerings on the altar - ",
    "answer": "every clean beast, and every clean fowl 8:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while at the inn, where in the sack did one espied his money - ",
    "answer": "sack's mouth 42:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but Rebekah loved -- - ",
    "answer": "Jacob 25:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "fill in the blank spoken by Joseph, It is not in me, God shall give Pharaoh an answer of -- - ",
    "answer": "peace 41:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Isaac go out in the field in eventide to do - ",
    "answer": "meditate 24:63"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph tell the chief baker would happen to him within three days - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh will lift off his head and shall hang him on a tree and the birds will eat his flesh off him 40:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the children of Nahor and Milcah - ",
    "answer": "Huzm Buz, Kemuel, Chesed, Hazo, Pildash, Jidlaph,Bethuel 22:21-22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is Machir's father - ",
    "answer": "Manasseh 50:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened when Judah came in unto Tamar - ",
    "answer": "she conceived by him 38:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From which land did Hagar take a wife for her son - ",
    "answer": "Egypt 21:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Lot tell the men he could not escape to the mountain - ",
    "answer": "lest some evil take him and he die 19:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"thou has done foolishly in so doing\" - ",
    "answer": "Laban to Jacob 31:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the great river also known as - ",
    "answer": "Euphrates 15:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph's conspired to slay him and cast him into this - ",
    "answer": "some pit 37:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who told Abram what had befallen Lot - ",
    "answer": "one that escaped 14:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- be everyone that curseth thee and -- be everyone that blesseth thee. - ",
    "answer": "cursed, blessed 27:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the animals Abram possessed - ",
    "answer": "sheep, oxen, he asses, she asses and camels 12:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what among the sheep was to be Jacob's hire - ",
    "answer": "all the brown cattle 30:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Places included in the border of Canaan - ",
    "answer": "Gerar, Sodom, Gomorrah, Admah, Zeboim, Lasha 10:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Isaac went from valley of Gerar to this place - ",
    "answer": "Beersheba 26:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Eber live after he begat Peleg - ",
    "answer": "430 years 11:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the response to this \"let me go for the day breaketh\" - ",
    "answer": "I will not let thee go except thou bless me 32:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord said the woman would do this in sorrow - ",
    "answer": "bring forth children 3:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what word did Hamor and Shechem use to describe how Jacob and his sons were to them - ",
    "answer": "peacable 34:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the curse Noah pronounced on Canaan - ",
    "answer": "a servant of servants shall he be to his brethren 9:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Isaac when he died? - ",
    "answer": "180 years old 35:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For what purpose did God put the man in the garden of Eden - ",
    "answer": "to dress it and keep it 2:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many dukes came from Reuel Esau's son - ",
    "answer": "four 36:17 (Nahath, Zerah, Shammah, Mizzah)"
  },
  {
    "stem": "on what day of creation did command the fruit trees and herbs and grass to appear? - ",
    "answer": "the third day 1:12,13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From whom did Joseph take an oath asking his bones to be carried from Egypt - ",
    "answer": "children of Israel 50:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To what proportion did the Lord say vengeance will be taken on whosoever slayeth Cain - ",
    "answer": "sevenfold 4:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To whom is this referring \"a strong ass couching down between two burdens\" - ",
    "answer": "Issachar 49:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Jared when he died - ",
    "answer": "nine hundred and sixty two 5:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And they said, thou has saved our lives, let us find grace in thy sight my lord and we will be Pharaoh's -- - ",
    "answer": "servants 47:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the measurement of the window in the ark - ",
    "answer": "a cubit 6:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where were the two sons born to Joseph - ",
    "answer": "in Egypt 46:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the Lord smelled a -- -- - ",
    "answer": "sweet savour 8:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Jacob was told Joseph was alive, his heart -- for he believed them not. - ",
    "answer": "fainted 45:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "as Jacob sod pottage, Esau came in from the field in this condition - ",
    "answer": "faint 25:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much more was Benjamin's mess compared to his brethren - ",
    "answer": "five times 43:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Into who's tent did Isaac bring Rebekah - ",
    "answer": "his mother Sarah's 24:67"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the response of the brethren to these words, \"my money is restored and lo it is even in my sack\" - ",
    "answer": "their heart failed them and they were afraid saying one to another, what is this that God has done to us 42:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And behold seven other kine came up after them, poor and ill favored and lean fleshed such as I never saw in all the land of Egypt for -- - ",
    "answer": "badness 41:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was Rebekah's father - ",
    "answer": "Bethuel 22:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the name of the chief captain of Abimelech's host - ",
    "answer": "Phichol 21:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "on the third day was Pharaoh's birthday what did he make unto all his servants - ",
    "answer": "a feast 40:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the city Lot escaped to - ",
    "answer": "Zoar 19:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by who's hand did Judah send the kid - ",
    "answer": "his friend the Adullamite 38:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abram's seed would possess the land of other nations, name the nations starting with the letter \"K\" - ",
    "answer": "Kenites, Kenizzites, Kadmonites 15:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while in prison, in whose sight did the Lord give Joseph favor - ",
    "answer": "in the sight of the keeper of the prison 39:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the father of Reu - ",
    "answer": "Peleg 11:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when did Laban tell Jacob the God of his father had spoken to him - ",
    "answer": "yesternight 31:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Why did the Lord plague Pharaoh and his house with great plagues - ",
    "answer": "because of Sarai Abram's wife 12:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the brethren purpose to say had devoured Joseph - ",
    "answer": "some evil beast 37:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker, \"let my father arise and eat of his son's venison that thy soul may bless me\" - ",
    "answer": "Esau 27:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where was Abram dwelling when he was told Lot was taken - ",
    "answer": "the plain of Mamre the Amorite 14:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Unto Shem the father of all the -- of Eber - ",
    "answer": "children 10:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what among the goats was to be Jacob's hire - ",
    "answer": "spotted and speckled 30:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from what age did the Lord say the imagination of man's heart is evil - ",
    "answer": "from his youth 8:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Isaac build in Beersheba - ",
    "answer": "an altar 26:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where in the ark was the door to be set - ",
    "answer": "in the side 6:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and He said thy name shall be called no more Jacob but Israel for as a -- has thou power with God and with men and hast prevailed - ",
    "answer": "prince 32:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Far from retiring Enoch was this age when he begat Methuselah - ",
    "answer": "sixty-five 5:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who hearkened unto Hamor and Shechem - ",
    "answer": "all that went out of the gate of the city 34:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did the Lord set a mark upon Cain - ",
    "answer": "lest any finding him should kill him 4:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who buried Isaac - ",
    "answer": "his sons Jacob and Esau 35:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and thy -- shall be to thy -- and he shall -- over thee - ",
    "answer": "desire, husband, rule 3:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the dukes that came from Aholibamah, Esau's wife - ",
    "answer": "Jeush, Jaalam, Korah 36:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what word did God use to tell man how he may eat of every tree of the garden - ",
    "answer": "freely 2:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Joseph when he died - ",
    "answer": "110 years old 50:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the purpose of the lights in the firmament - ",
    "answer": "to divide the day from the night, signs, seasons, days and years 1:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Of Issachar, he saw that -- was good and the land that it was -- and bowed his -- to bear and became a servant unto -- - ",
    "answer": "rest, pleasant, shoulder, tribute 49:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Upon blessing Shem who did Noah say would be his servant - ",
    "answer": "Canaan 9:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what law did Joseph make in Egypt - ",
    "answer": "that Pharaoh should have the fifth part except the land of the priests 47:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Peleg when he begat Reu - ",
    "answer": "30 years old 11:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "all the souls of the house of Jacob which came into Egypt were how many - ",
    "answer": "three score and ten (70) 46:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "because Esau asked Jacob to feed him with the red pottage what was his name called - ",
    "answer": "Edom 25:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Pharaoh restore the chief butler unto - ",
    "answer": "his butlership 40:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to Jacob when he saw the wagons Joseph had sent to carry him - ",
    "answer": "his spirit revived 45:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides himself who else did Abeimelech ask Abraham not to deal falsely with - ",
    "answer": "his son, and his son's son 21:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The -- was risen upon the earth when Lot entered Zoar - ",
    "answer": "sun 19:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they drank and were -- with him - ",
    "answer": "merry 43:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God told Abram his seed would posses the land of other nations, name the nations that does not begin with the letter \"K\" - ",
    "answer": "Hitties, Perizzites, Rephaims, Amorites, Canaanites, Girgashites, Jebusites 15:20,21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The man who is lord of the land spake roughly to us and took us for -- of the country - ",
    "answer": "spies 42:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What nationality was Mamre - ",
    "answer": "Amorite 14:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "according to Pharaoh what could not be known after the lean kine had eaten the fat kine and why - ",
    "answer": "that they had eaten them up, for they were still ill favored as at the beginning 41:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did Pharaoh command concerning Abram - ",
    "answer": "his men 12:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob called the name of the place Peniel for I have seen God -- to -- and my life is -- - ",
    "answer": "face, face, preserved 32:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who/what did the keeper of the prison commit to Joseph's hands - ",
    "answer": "all the prisoners that were in the prison 39:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was the name of Nahor's concubine - ",
    "answer": "Reumah 22:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many children did Shem have - ",
    "answer": "five 10:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Laban to Jacob, it is in the power of my hand to do you -- - ",
    "answer": "hurt 31:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord say He will not do anymore to the ground for man's sake - ",
    "answer": "curse it 8:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when asked about the harlot what did the men of the place tell Judah's friend - ",
    "answer": "there was no harlot in this place 38:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "name the stories of the ark - ",
    "answer": "lower, second and third 6:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what words describe how Isaac trembled when Esau came with venison for his blessing - ",
    "answer": "very exceedingly 27:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For how long after he begat Methuselah did Enoch walk with God - ",
    "answer": "three hundred years 5:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "So shall my -- answer for me in time to come when it shall come for my -- before thy face everyone that is not speckled or spotted among the goats and brown among the sheep that shall be counted -- with me - ",
    "answer": "righteousness, hire, stolen 30:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord set upon Cain - ",
    "answer": "a mark 4:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who accompanied Abimelech to go see Isaac - ",
    "answer": "Ahuzzath one of his friends, Phichol the chief captain of his army 26:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who of the city of Hamor was circumcised - ",
    "answer": "every male,all that went out of the gate of the city 34:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord curse for Adam's sake - ",
    "answer": "the ground 3:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was to divide the day from the night - ",
    "answer": "the lights in the firmament 1:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Isaac was gathered unto his people being old and full of -- - ",
    "answer": "days 35:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did God say would be the result if man ate of the tree of knowledge of good and evil - ",
    "answer": "shall surely die 2:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons did Seir the Horite have - ",
    "answer": "seven 36:20-21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God shall -- Japheth and he shall dwell in the -- of Shem and Canaan shall be his -- - ",
    "answer": "enlarge, tents, servant 9:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who delivered Joseph out of the hand of his brethren saying, let us not kill him - ",
    "answer": "Reuben 37:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Peleg live after he begat Reu - ",
    "answer": "209 years 11:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and whatsoever they did he was the -- of it - ",
    "answer": "doer 39:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"sell me this day thy birthright\" - ",
    "answer": "Jacob to Esau 25:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did they do to Joseph when he died - ",
    "answer": "embalmed him and put him in a coffin in Egypt 50:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who are the parents of Tebah, Gaham, Thasash, Maachah - ",
    "answer": "Nahor and Reumah 22:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- shall judge his people as one of the tribes of Israel - ",
    "answer": "Dan 49:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Abraham reprove Abimelech - ",
    "answer": "because of a well of water which his servants had violently taken away 21:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Joseph weep on his father's neck - ",
    "answer": "a good while 46:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did the Lord rain upon Sodom and Gomorrah - ",
    "answer": "brimstone and fire 19:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "identify the speaker \"it is enough Joseph my son is yet alive, I will go and see him before I die\" - ",
    "answer": "Israel 45:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who were the brothers of Mamre - ",
    "answer": "Eshcol, Aner 14:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And bring your -- brother unto me then I shall know ye are no -- but ye are true men so will I deliver your brother and ye shall -- in the land - ",
    "answer": "youngest, spies, traffick 42:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who to whom, \"what is this thou has done unto me, why did thou not tell me, that she was thy wife?\" - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh to Abram 12:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Joseph said unto Pharaoh the dream of Pharaoh is -- - ",
    "answer": "one 41:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while the earth remaineth -- and harvest, cold and -- summer and -- day and -- shall not cease - ",
    "answer": "seedtime, heat, winter, night 8:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Pharaoh do the chief baker - ",
    "answer": "hanged him 40:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the children of Shem - ",
    "answer": "Elam, Asshur, Arphaxad, Lud and Aram 10:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Israel dwelt in the land of -- in the country of Goshen and they had -- therein and grew and multiplied -- - ",
    "answer": "Egypt, possessions, exceedingly 47:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long after the flood did Noah live - ",
    "answer": "three hundred and fifty years 9:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and Judah said, let her take it lest we be -- - ",
    "answer": "shamed 38:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord told Noah He will bring a flood of water and destroy all flesh wherein is this, from under heaven - ",
    "answer": "breath of life 6:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the first king of Seir - ",
    "answer": "Bela 36:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were all the days of Enoch - ",
    "answer": "Three hundred and sixty five years 5:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "on what day of the men being sore did Simeon and Levi come upon the city - ",
    "answer": "third say 34:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Cain went out from the presence of the Lord and dwelt in this land - ",
    "answer": "Nod 4:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because He touched the hollow of Jacob's thigh in the sinew that shrank what do the children of Israel not do to this day - ",
    "answer": "eat of the sinew which shrank 32:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob tell Laban to do with whomsoever he finds his gods - ",
    "answer": "let him not live 31:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How was Adam to eat of the ground and for how long - ",
    "answer": "in sorrow, all the days of his life 3:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did God say about man being alone - ",
    "answer": "it is not good 2:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"wherefore come ye to me, seeing ye hate me and have sent me away from you - ",
    "answer": "Isaac 26:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how many great lights did God make - ",
    "answer": "two 1:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which of the he goats did Laban remove from the flock - ",
    "answer": "ringstraked and spotted 30:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who is the father of Uz, Hul, Gether, and Mash - ",
    "answer": "Aram 10:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Esau cry when he heard the words of his father - ",
    "answer": "great and exceeding bitter cry 27:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "behold I am at the point to -- and what profit shall this -- be to me - ",
    "answer": "die, birthright 25:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Reuben say, \"shed no blood, but cast him into this pit that is in the wilderness, and lay no hand upon him\" - ",
    "answer": "that he might rid him out of their hands to deliver him to his father again 37:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"I wot not who had done this thing, neither didst thou tell me, neither yet heard I of it , but today\" - ",
    "answer": "Abimelech 21:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Yet did not the chief -- remember Joseph but forgat him - ",
    "answer": "butler 40:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Last word in Genesis - ",
    "answer": "Egypt"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the Lord overthrew all those -- and all the -- and all the -- of the cites and that which -- upon the ground - ",
    "answer": "cities, plain, inhabitants, grew 19:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Mamre and his brothers were -- with Abram - ",
    "answer": "confederate 14:13"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Dan shall be -- by the way, an -- in the path - ",
    "answer": "serpent, adder 49:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the son Reu begat when he was thirty two years old - ",
    "answer": "Serug 11:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Jacob live in the land of Egypt - ",
    "answer": "seventeen years 47:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Noah when he died - ",
    "answer": "nine hundred and fifty years 9:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Egyptians consider this occupation to be an abomination - ",
    "answer": "shepherd 46:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what ruled the day - ",
    "answer": "the greater light 1:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the reaction of Jacob and his sons when they discovered every man's bundle of money was in his sack. - ",
    "answer": "they were afraid 42:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord tell Noah He would establish with him - ",
    "answer": "His covenant 6:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the seven good kine and seven ears represent - ",
    "answer": "seven years 41:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Give the scripture reference: and Enoch walked with God and he was not for God took him - ",
    "answer": "Gen 5:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the city of Bela king of Seir - ",
    "answer": "Dinhabah 36:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where was the land of Nod - ",
    "answer": "east of Eden 4:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many months after was it told Judah Tamar was with child - ",
    "answer": "about three months 38:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides thorns what else did the Lord tell Adam the ground will bring forth to him - ",
    "answer": "thistles 3:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph's brethren strip him of - ",
    "answer": "his coat of many colors 37:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because God concluded it was not good for man to be alone, who did He say He would make for him - ",
    "answer": "an help meet 2:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Simeon and Levi come upon the city and what did they do - ",
    "answer": "boldly, slew all the males 34:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "with what did Jacob purchase Esau's birthright - ",
    "answer": "bread and pottage of lentiles 25:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "upon what did Jacob halt - ",
    "answer": "his thigh 32:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Abraham took sheep and oxen and gave them to Abimelech and both of them made a -- - ",
    "answer": "covenant 21:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In whose tents did Laban search for the stolen gods - ",
    "answer": "Jacob's, Leah's, the two maidservants' and Rachel's 31:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Having looked back what happened to Lot's wife - ",
    "answer": "she became a pillar of salt 19:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "which of the she goats did Laban remove from the flock - ",
    "answer": "the speckled and spotted and everyone that had some white in it 30:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Abram do when he learnt Lot was taken - ",
    "answer": "he armed his trained servants born in his house, and pursued them unto Dan 14:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Thy brother came with -- and hath taken away thy blessing - ",
    "answer": "subtilty 27:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Reu live after he begat Serug - ",
    "answer": "207 years 11:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what Abimelech wanted an oath between him and Isaac and to make this - ",
    "answer": "a covenant 26:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was to enter the ark with Noah - ",
    "answer": "his sons, his wife and his sons wives 6:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many chapters in Genesis - ",
    "answer": "50"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did Arphaxad beget - ",
    "answer": "Salah 10:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The seven ill favored kine and the seven empty ears blasted with the east wind represented seven years of - ",
    "answer": "famine 41:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "that bite the horse heels so that his -- shall fall backward - ",
    "answer": "rider 49:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "This man was hundred eighty and seven years when he begat his son Lamech - ",
    "answer": "Methuselah 5:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of Cain's son - ",
    "answer": "Enoch 4:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In swearing he would not bury him in Egypt when he died where did Israel tell Joseph to place his hand - ",
    "answer": "under his thigh 47:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In eating of the tree the Lord told Adam he hearkened to this - ",
    "answer": "the voice of his wife 3:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Which part of Egypt did Joseph want his brethren to dwell - ",
    "answer": "land of Goshen 46:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "FTV, and whatsoever Adam called every living creature.. - ",
    "answer": "that was the name thereof 2:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Jacob their father said unto them, me have ye -- of my children Joseph is not -- is not and ye will take Benjamin away, all these things are -- me. - ",
    "answer": "bereaved, Simeon, against 42:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the lesser light rule - ",
    "answer": "the night 1:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Is he not rightly named Jacob for he had -- me these two times - ",
    "answer": "supplanted 27:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "thus Esau -- his birthright - ",
    "answer": "despised 25:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "It was told Judah, Tamar thy daughter in law hath played the -- and also behold she is with child by -- - ",
    "answer": "harlot, whoredom 38:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Simeon and Levi use to kill the men of the city - ",
    "answer": "swords 34:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Abraham tell Abimelech was the purpose of the seven ewe lambs - ",
    "answer": "that they may be a witness unto him that he had digged this well 21:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "As Abraham looked toward Sodom and Gomorrah and the plain the smoke of the country went up as this - ",
    "answer": "the smoke of a furnace 19:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where had Rachel put the images - ",
    "answer": "in the camel's furniture 31:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many trained servants did Abram have - ",
    "answer": "318, 14:14"
  },
  {
    "stem": "all the brown among this animal Laban removed from the flock - ",
    "answer": "sheep 30:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the father of Nahor - ",
    "answer": "Serug 11:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the terms of the covenant between Isaac and Abimelech - ",
    "answer": "that he would do them no hurt 26:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And of every living thing of all flesh, -- of every sort shalt thou bring into the ark - ",
    "answer": "two 6:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the state of the pit they cast Joseph into - ",
    "answer": "empty no water 37:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is the father of Eber - ",
    "answer": "Salah 10:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Hearing Tamar was with child by whoredom, what did Judah command concerning her - ",
    "answer": "bring her forth let her be burnt 38:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where were the stars, greater and lesser light placed and what was their purpose - ",
    "answer": "in the firmament of the heaven, to give light upon the earth, to rule over the day and night, and to divide the light from the darkness 1:16,17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "-- a troop shall overcome him but he shall overcome at the last - ",
    "answer": "Gad 49:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Methuselah live after he begat Lamech - ",
    "answer": "seven hundred and eighty two years 5:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "On which part of the bed did Israel bow himself - ",
    "answer": "the head 47:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "After who/what did Cain name the city he built - ",
    "answer": "his son Enoch 4:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"slay my two sons if I bring him not to thee\" - ",
    "answer": "Reuben 42:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "but for Adam there was not found a -- for him - ",
    "answer": "help meet 2:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph describes the first seven years that are coming throughout the land of Egypt as years of - ",
    "answer": "great plenty 41:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what of the field did the Lord tell Adam he would eat - ",
    "answer": "the herb 3:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Joseph's brethren sat down to eat bread they beheld a company of Ishmeelites with their camels that came from this place - ",
    "answer": "Gilead 37:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the scripture states the greater and lesser light as well as the stars where formed on this day of creation - ",
    "answer": "fourth 1:14-19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from where did Simeon and Levi take Dinah - ",
    "answer": "out of Shechem's house 34:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of sleep did the Lord God cause to fall upon Adam - ",
    "answer": "deep sleep 2:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Let it not displease my lord that I cannot rise up before thee, for the -- of women is upon me - ",
    "answer": "custom 31:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the -- of thy face shalt thou eat bread - ",
    "answer": "sweat 3:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To whom did Laban give the animals which he had removed from the flock - ",
    "answer": "his sons 30:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Methuselah died at this age - ",
    "answer": "nine hundred and sixty nine 5:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Isaac tell Esau his dwelling shall be - ",
    "answer": "the fatness of the earth, dew of heaven 27:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "of fowls after their -- and of cattle after their -- and of every creeping thing of the earth after his -- - ",
    "answer": "kind, kind, kind 6:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "as we have not touched thee, as we have done nothing to thee but good and have sent thee away in -- - ",
    "answer": "peace 26:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons were born unto Eber - ",
    "answer": "two 10:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Identify the speaker \"by the man whose these are, am I with child\" - ",
    "answer": "Tamar 38:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Out of Asher his bread shall be -- and he shall yield royal -- - ",
    "answer": "fat, dainties 49:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Serug when he begat Nahor - ",
    "answer": "30 years old 11:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where is Hobah - ",
    "answer": "on the left hand of Damascus 14:15"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Jacob live - ",
    "answer": "147 years, 47:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The scriptures says when God destroyed the cities of the plain that God remembered this person and sent Lot out of the midst of the overthrow - ",
    "answer": "Abraham 19:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If mischief befall him by the way in the which ye go, then shall ye bring down my gray hairs with sorrow to the -- - ",
    "answer": "grave 42:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Because both him and Abimelech sware what did Abraham call the place - ",
    "answer": "Beersheba 21:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to the interpretation what kind of years will come after the years of great plenty - ",
    "answer": "seven years of famine 41:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Esau do with his birthright? - ",
    "answer": "sold it to Jacob 25:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Jacob was wroth and -- with Laban - ",
    "answer": "chode 31:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the two wives of Lamech - ",
    "answer": "Adah, Zillah 4:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the company of Ishmeelites carrying down to Egypt - ",
    "answer": "spicery, balm and myrrh 37:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many days journey did Laban set between himself and Jacob - ",
    "answer": "three days 30:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides Lot who and what else did Abram bring back - ",
    "answer": "all the goods, women, people 14:16"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the two sons of Eber - ",
    "answer": "Peleg and Joktan 10:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "about whom \"and by the sword shall thou live and shall serve thy brother\" - ",
    "answer": "Esau 27:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Fearing to dwell in Zoar, Lot went to the mountains with his two daughters and dwelt in this - ",
    "answer": "a cave 19:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Isaac make for Abimelech and the others and what did they do - ",
    "answer": "a feast, eat and drink 26:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abraham plant in Beersheba - ",
    "answer": "a grove 21:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "be specific, Simeon and Levi slew Hamor and his son Shechem with this - ",
    "answer": "edge of the sword 34:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Serug live after he begat Nahor - ",
    "answer": "200 years 11:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's idea was it to sell Joseph to the Ishmeelites - ",
    "answer": "Judah 37:26-27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the mother of Jabal and Jubal - ",
    "answer": "Adah 4:20-21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Naphtali is a -- let loose, he giveth -- words - ",
    "answer": "hind, goodly 49:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And thou shall take unto thee all food that is -- - ",
    "answer": "eaten 6:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "all the -- shall be forgotten in the land of Egypt, and the -- shall consume the land - ",
    "answer": "plenty, famine 41:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "for -- thou art and unto -- shalt thou return - ",
    "answer": "dust, dust 3:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Judah acknowledge the signet, bracelet and staff , T or F - ",
    "answer": "true 38:25-26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what internal part did God remove from Adam as he slept - ",
    "answer": "one of his ribs 2:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is my trespass and what is my sin that thou has so -- pursued after me - ",
    "answer": "hotly 31:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From where did the moving creatures and fowls come forth - ",
    "answer": "the waters 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The sons of Jacob came upon the slain and -- the city because they had defiled their sister - ",
    "answer": "spoiled 34:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the father of Noah - ",
    "answer": "Lamech 5:28,29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "from which trees did Jacob take rods - ",
    "answer": "green poplar, hazel and chestnut 30:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what happened to the earth in the days of Peleg - ",
    "answer": "it was divided 10:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and it shall come to pass when thou shalt have the -- that thou shalt break his -- from off thy neck - ",
    "answer": "dominion, yoke 27:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what Isaac servants come and tell him concerning the well they had digged - ",
    "answer": "we have found water 26:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's name did Abraham call on in Beersheba - ",
    "answer": "the name of the Lord, the everlasting God 21:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"our father is old and there is not a man in the earth to come in unto us after the manner of all the earth\" - ",
    "answer": "Lot's firstborn to the younger 19:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph is a fruitful -- even a fruitful -- by a well, whose branches run over the -- - ",
    "answer": "bough, bough, wall 49:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Where did the king of Sodom go out to meet Abram - ",
    "answer": "valley of Shaveh 14:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what word did Joseph use to describe the famine that will follow the years of plenty - ",
    "answer": "grievous 41:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Nahor when he begat Terah - ",
    "answer": "29 years old 11:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \"she hath been more righteous than I, because that I gave her not to Shelah my son\" - ",
    "answer": "Judah 38:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Thus did Noah according to all that God -- him - ",
    "answer": "commanded 6:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Then there passed by -- merchantmen - ",
    "answer": "Midianites 37:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The two son of Jacob took of what was in the city as well as this place - ",
    "answer": "the field 34:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Lamech when he begat Noah - ",
    "answer": "one hundred and eighty two 5:28,29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jabal was the father of those that dwelt in these and have cattle - ",
    "answer": "tents 4:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob do to the rods of the trees - ",
    "answer": "pilled white strakes in them 30:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord tell Adam he would do in the sweat of his face - ",
    "answer": "eat bread 3:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How did Esau feel towards Jacob because of the blessing wherewith his father blessed him - ",
    "answer": "hated him 27:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did God do with the rib which He had taken from Adam - ",
    "answer": "He made a woman 2:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Isaac call the well where his servants had found water - ",
    "answer": "Shebah 26:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "how did the water bring forth the moving creatures and fowls - ",
    "answer": "abundantly 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "This -- years have I been with thee, thy -- and thy she -- have not cast their young and the -- of thy flock have I not eaten - ",
    "answer": "twenty, ewes, goats, rams 31:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many sons did Joktan beget - ",
    "answer": "thirteen 10:26-29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How much was Joseph sold for to the Ishmeelites - ",
    "answer": "twenty pieces of silver 37:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And for the dream was doubled unto Pharaoh --, it is because the thing is -- by God and God will shortly bring it to pass. - ",
    "answer": "twice, established 41:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To where did Abimelech and Phichol return - ",
    "answer": "to the land of the Philistines 21:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What is the valley of Shaveh - ",
    "answer": "the king's dale 14:17"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and it came to pass in the time of her travail, that behold -- were in her womb - ",
    "answer": "twins 38:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Nahor live after he begat Terah - ",
    "answer": "119 years 11:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what have the archers done to Joseph - ",
    "answer": "sorely grieved him, shot at him, hated him 49:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when Lot's firstborn daughter made him drink wine and laid with him, what did he not perceive - ",
    "answer": "when she lay down, nor when she arose 19:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the two sons of Jacob take from the city after they slew all the males - ",
    "answer": "sheep, oxen, asses,wealth 34:28-29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Lamech named his son Noah stating he shall comfort them concerning two things - ",
    "answer": "work, toil of our hands 5:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob told Laban the animals that were torn of beast he did not bring to Laban but instead did this - ",
    "answer": "bare the loss of it 31:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did Adam call his wife's name Eve - ",
    "answer": "because she was the mother of all living 3:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob pilled the rods so that this appeared in them - ",
    "answer": "the white 30:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what great sea animal was mentioned in Gen 1:21 - ",
    "answer": "whale"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who said this in his heart, \"the days of mourning for my father are at hand, then will I slay my brother Jacob\" - ",
    "answer": "Esau 27:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who brought the woman unto the man - ",
    "answer": "God 2:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is Shebah called to this day - ",
    "answer": "Beer-sheba 26:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was Jubal the father of - ",
    "answer": "all that handle the harp and organ 4:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Of Joseph, but his bow abode in -- - ",
    "answer": "strength 49:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "From where was the dwelling of the sons of Joktan - ",
    "answer": "Mesha 10:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of man did Joseph tell Pharaoh to set over the land of Egypt - ",
    "answer": "discreet and wise 41:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When after the firstborn of Lot laid with her father did the younger do the same - ",
    "answer": "on the morrow night 19:34-35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the midwife put on the hand of the twin - ",
    "answer": "scarlet thread 38:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the king of Salem - ",
    "answer": "Melchizedek 14:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Reuben do when he returned and Joseph was not in the pit - ",
    "answer": "he rent his clothes 37:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Terah lived seventy years and begat --, -- and --- - ",
    "answer": "Abram, Nahor, Haran 11:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did Simeon and Levi take captive from the city - ",
    "answer": "little ones, wives 34:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Abraham sojourn in the land of the Philistines - ",
    "answer": "many days 21:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "of my hand did thou require it whether stolen by -- or stolen by -- - ",
    "answer": "day, night 31:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Lamech live after he begat Noah - ",
    "answer": "five hundred and ninety five years 5:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jacob set the rods he had pilled and why - ",
    "answer": "before the flocks in the gutter in the water troughs, so the flocks would conceive when they came to drink 30:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the son Zillah bare to Lamech - ",
    "answer": "Tubal-cain 4:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "To where and to whom did Rebekah tell her son Jacob to flee - ",
    "answer": "Haran, Laban 27:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord make and clothed Adam and his wife - ",
    "answer": "coats of skin 3:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Esau was forty years old when he took two Hittite wives name them - ",
    "answer": "Judith, Bashemath 26:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who's speaking \" the child is not, and I, wither shall I go\" - ",
    "answer": "Reuben 37:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And Adam said this is now -- of my -- and -- of my -- she shall be called -- because she was taken out of Man - ",
    "answer": "bone, bone, flesh, flesh, woman 2:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and every -- fowl after his kind - ",
    "answer": "winged 1:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "by what means was the arms of Joseph hand made strong - ",
    "answer": "by the hands of the mighty God of Jacob 49:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Thus were both the daughters of Lot with child by their -- - ",
    "answer": "father 19:36"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph counseled Pharaoh to appoint officers over the land and take up this part of the land of Egypt in the seven plenteous years - ",
    "answer": "fifth part 41:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Melchizedek bring as he met Abram - ",
    "answer": "bread and wine 14:18"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what is the name of Tamar's older twin - ",
    "answer": "Pharez 38:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who was the father of Lot - ",
    "answer": "Haran 11:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Rebekah tell Jacob to tarry with her brother - ",
    "answer": "a few days 27:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was Sephar - ",
    "answer": "a mount of the east 10:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob told Simeon and Levi they have troubled him to make him -- among the inhabitants of the land - ",
    "answer": "stink 34:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what kind of cattle did the flocks that conceive before the rod bring forth - ",
    "answer": "ringstraked, speckled and spotted 30:39"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Lamech died at this age - ",
    "answer": "seven hundred seventy and seven years 5:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Tubal-cain was an instructer of every artificer in these metals - ",
    "answer": "brass and iron 4:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the state of mind of Isaac and Rebekah in regard to Esau's wives - ",
    "answer": "grief of mind 26:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the Lord God said, behold the -- is become as one of us to know -- and -- lest he put forth his -- and take also of the tree of -- and eat and live forever - ",
    "answer": "man, good, evil, hand, life 3:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "while keeping the flock what did Jacob say consumed in the day and in the night - ",
    "answer": "drought, frost 31:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Repeat Gen 2:24 - ",
    "answer": "Therefore shall a man leave his father and his mother and shall cleave unto his wife, and they shall be one flesh"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did they dip Joseph's blood in - ",
    "answer": "blood of the kid of the goats 37:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God said let the waters bring forth abundantly the moving creature that hath -- - ",
    "answer": "life 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who shall bless thee with the blessings of -- above, blessings of the the -- that lieth under blessings of the -- and of the womb - ",
    "answer": "heaven, deep, breasts 49:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Lot's firstborn name her son - ",
    "answer": "Moab 19:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of the twin on which the scarlet thread was placed on his hand - ",
    "answer": "Zarah 38:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "These are the sons of Shem after their -- after their -- in their lands after their nations - ",
    "answer": "families, tongues 10:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and lay up -- under the hand of Pharaoh and let them keep food in the -- - ",
    "answer": "corn, cities 41:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides being king Melchizedek had this role - ",
    "answer": "priest of the most high God 14:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides the Canaanites who were the other inhabitants of the land to which Jacob was referring - ",
    "answer": "Perizzites 34:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Which son of Terah died before he did - ",
    "answer": "Haran 11:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob say departed from his eyes - ",
    "answer": "his sleep 31:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "even though the man and his wife were in this physical state, they were not ashamed - ",
    "answer": "naked 2:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when the stronger cattle would conceive what did Jacob lay before their eyes in the gutter - ",
    "answer": "the rods 30:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Gen 5:32 states Noah was this age - ",
    "answer": "five hundred years old"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Rebekah told Jacob to tarry with her brother a few days until this is turned away - ",
    "answer": "his brother's fury/brother's anger 27:44,45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The Lord God sent the man forth from this place to till the ground from whence he was taken - ",
    "answer": "garden of Eden 3:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"I am weary of my life because of the daughters of Heth\" - ",
    "answer": "Rebekah to Isaac 27:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when these cattle conceived Jacob did not place the rods in the gutter - ",
    "answer": "feeble 30:41-42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where may the fowl fly - ",
    "answer": "above the earth in the open firmament of heaven 1:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name Tubal-cain's sister - ",
    "answer": "Naamah 4:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many years did Jacob serve Laban for his daughters - ",
    "answer": "fourteen 31:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and by these were the nations divided in the earth after the -- - ",
    "answer": "flood 10:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob told his two sons because he was this the inhabitants of the land shall gather themselves against him and slay him, and he his house shall be destroyed - ",
    "answer": "few in number 34:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is Moab the father of to this day - ",
    "answer": "the Moabites 19:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob rent his clothes and put this on his loins upon hearing of Joseph's death - ",
    "answer": "sackcloth 37:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Haran die - ",
    "answer": "in the land of his nativity, Ur of the Chaldees 11:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and the thing was good in the eyes of -- and in the eyes of all his -- - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh, servants 41:37"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The blessings of thy fathers have prevailed above the blessings of my -- unto the utmost bound of the everlasting -- they shall be on the head of Joseph and on the -- of the head of him who was separate from his -- - ",
    "answer": "progenitors, hills, crown, brethren 49:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who's speaking, \"blessed be Abram of the most high God, possessor of heaven and earth\" - ",
    "answer": "Melchizedek 14:19"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Name the sons of Noah - ",
    "answer": "Shem, Ham, Japheth 5:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \" can we find such a one as this, a man in whom the Spirit of God is \" - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh to his servants 41:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was the mother of Tubal-cain - ",
    "answer": "Zillah 4:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Shall ravin as a wolf, in the morning he shall devour the prey and at night he shall divide the spoil - ",
    "answer": "Benjamin 49:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who/what did the Lord place at the east of the garden of Eden - ",
    "answer": "Cherubims and a flaming sword 3:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "so the -- were Laban's and the --- Jacob's - ",
    "answer": "feebler, stronger 30:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God blessed them saying be fruitful and multiply and fill the waters in the -- - ",
    "answer": "seas 1:22"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How long did Jacob mourn for Joseph - ",
    "answer": "many days 37:34"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what day were the fowls and other sea creatures created - ",
    "answer": "fifth 1:20-23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How many yeas did Jacob serve Laban for the cattle - ",
    "answer": "six 31:41"
  },
  {
    "stem": "and they said should he deal with our sister as with a -- - ",
    "answer": "harlot 34:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For what purpose was the Cherubims and flaming sword placed at the east of Eden - ",
    "answer": "to keep the way of the tree of life 3:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"for I have slain a man to my wounding and a young man to my hurt\" - ",
    "answer": "Lamech to his wives 4:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Jacob increased exceedingly and had much - ",
    "answer": "cattle, maidservants, menservants, camels, asses 30:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was the name of Nahor's wife - ",
    "answer": "Milcah 11:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Except the God of Abraham and the fear of Isaac had been with him, how did Jacob say Laban would have sent him away - ",
    "answer": "empty 31:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Abram give to Melchizedek - ",
    "answer": "tithes of all 14:20"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob do when all his sons and all his daughters rose up to comfort him - ",
    "answer": "he refused to be comforted 37:35"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What did Lot's younger daughter name her son - ",
    "answer": "Ben-ammi 19:38"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Thou shall be over my -- and according unto thy -- shall all my people be ruled only in the -- will I be greater than thou - ",
    "answer": "house, word, throne 41:40"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who is Ben-ammi the father of - ",
    "answer": "the children of Ammon 19:8"
  },
  {
    "stem": "everyone according to his blessing he -- them - ",
    "answer": "blessed 49:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"give me the persons and take the goods to thyself\" - ",
    "answer": "king of Sodom to Abram 14:21"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Pharaoh place on Joseph's hand - ",
    "answer": "his ring 41:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was Milcah's father - ",
    "answer": "Haran 11:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where did Jacob request to be buried - ",
    "answer": "in the cave of Ephron the Hittite 49:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Hear my voice ye wives of Lamech and hearken to my -- - ",
    "answer": "speech 4:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did the Midianites sell Joseph to - ",
    "answer": "Potiphar an officer of Pharaoh and captain of the guard"
  },
  {
    "stem": "God commanded the earth to bring forth the beast of the earth on this day - ",
    "answer": "sixth 1:25-31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"God hath seen my affliction and the labor of my hands and rebuked thee yesternight' - ",
    "answer": "Jacob to Laban 31:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What kind of sword was placed at the east of Eden by the Lord - ",
    "answer": "flaming 3:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Laban told Jacob the covenant would be this between them - ",
    "answer": "witness 31:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God said let us make man in our -- after our -- - ",
    "answer": "image, likeness 1:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what did Pharaoh array Joseph - ",
    "answer": "vestures of fine linen 41:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where is the cave of Ephron - ",
    "answer": "in the field of Machpelah 49:230"
  },
  {
    "stem": "If Cain shall be avenged sevenfold, truly Lamech -- and -- - ",
    "answer": "seventy, sevenfold 4:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was the father of Iscah - ",
    "answer": "Haran 11:29"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did they do upon the heap of stones - ",
    "answer": "eat 31:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "So that he would not say this of Abram, Abram refused to take a thread even a shoelatchet from the king of Sodom - ",
    "answer": "I have made Abram rich 14:23"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Pharaoh place around Joseph's neck - ",
    "answer": "a gold chain 41:42"
  },
  {
    "stem": "But Sarai was -- she had no child - ",
    "answer": "barren 11:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "the field of Machpelah is before -- in the land of Canaan - ",
    "answer": "Mamre 49:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Besides what the young men had eaten who else did Abram allow to take a portion of the goods from the slaughter - ",
    "answer": "Aner, Eshcol and Mamre 14:24"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Laban called the heap of stones Jegar-sahadutha but Jacob called it -- - ",
    "answer": "Galeed 31:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "When Eve declared God hath appointed me another seed instead of Abel whom Cain slew who was she referring to - ",
    "answer": "Seth 4:25"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In what did Pharaoh make Joseph ride - ",
    "answer": "in the second chariot which he had 41:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "According to Gen 1:26 what was man given dominion over - ",
    "answer": "fish of the sea, fowl of the air, cattle of the earth, creeping thing"
  },
  {
    "stem": "For what kind of possession did Abraham buy the field - ",
    "answer": "a burying place 49:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "So God created man in His own image in the image of God created He him -- and -- created He them - ",
    "answer": "male, female 1:27"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Prior to Jacob who was buried in the cave in the field of Machpelah - ",
    "answer": "Abraham, Sarah, Isaac, Rebekah, Leah 49:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "What was the name of Seth's son - ",
    "answer": "Enos 4:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did cry saying before Joseph - ",
    "answer": "bow the knee 41:43"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Terah took his family left Ur of the Chaldees and went forth into Canaan and dwelt in this place - ",
    "answer": "Haran 11:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The heap of stones was for a witness between Jacob and Laban that they would not pass over to do this to each other - ",
    "answer": "harm 31:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And God said unto them be -- and multiply and -- the earth and subdue it. - ",
    "answer": "fruitful, replenish 1:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "where can this be found 'the Lord watch between me and thee, when we are absent one from another\" - ",
    "answer": "Genesis 31:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did men begin to do after the birth of Enos - ",
    "answer": "call upon the name of the Lord 4:26"
  },
  {
    "stem": "I am Pharaoh without thee shall no man lift up his -- or -- in all the land of Egypt - ",
    "answer": "hand, foot 41:44"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Who did Terah take with him into the land of Canaan - ",
    "answer": "Abram, Lot, Sarai, 11:31"
  },
  {
    "stem": "The field and the cave was purchased from the children of -- - ",
    "answer": "Heth 49:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did the Lord give man for meat - ",
    "answer": "herb bearing seed, every tree with fruit yielding seed 1:28"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what name did Pharaoh call Joseph - ",
    "answer": "Zaphnath-paaneah 41:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Terah died at this age in Haran - ",
    "answer": "205 years 11:32"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Jacob do after he had made an end of commanding his sons - ",
    "answer": "he gathered up his feet into his bed, and yielded up the ghost, and was gathered unto his people 49:33"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what were the beast of the earth, fowl of the air and creeping thing given for meat - ",
    "answer": "green herb 1:30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who did Pharaoh give to Joseph as wife - ",
    "answer": "Asenath 41:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what day was man created - ",
    "answer": "sixth day 1:27-30"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who was Asenath the daughter of - ",
    "answer": "Potiphera priest of On 41:45"
  },
  {
    "stem": "How old was Joseph when he stood before Pharaoh king of Egypt - ",
    "answer": "thirty years old 41:46"
  },
  {
    "stem": "In the seven plenteous years the earth brought forth by -- - ",
    "answer": "handfuls 41:47"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph gather as the sand of the sea - ",
    "answer": "corn 41:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph gathered corn as the sand of the sea, very much, until he left numbering what was the reason for this - ",
    "answer": "for it was without number 41:49"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what was the name of Joseph's first born - ",
    "answer": "Manasseh 41:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Joseph named his first born Manasseh, saying .. - ",
    "answer": "For God hath made me to forget all my toils and all my father's house 41:51"
  },
  {
    "stem": "Saying, God hath made me fruitful in the land of my affliction, Joseph named his second son - ",
    "answer": "Ephraim 41:52"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the seven years of plenteousness that was in the land of Egypt were --- - ",
    "answer": "ended 41:53"
  },
  {
    "stem": "And the seven years of -- began to come, according as Joseph had said and the -- was in all the lands but in the land of Egypt was -- - ",
    "answer": "dearth, dearth, bread 41:54"
  },
  {
    "stem": "when all the land of Egypt was famished who did the people cry to for bread - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh 41:55"
  },
  {
    "stem": "who to whom \"go unto Joseph what he saith to you do\" - ",
    "answer": "Pharaoh to the Egyptians 41:55"
  },
  {
    "stem": "what did Joseph open and sold unto the Egyptians - ",
    "answer": "all the the storehouses 41:56"
  },
  {
    "stem": "why did all the countries come into Egypt to Joseph to buy corn - ",
    "answer": "because the famine was so sore in all the lands 41:57"
  }
];